{"COLCAP": {"1": {"recess": "0.0057", "opposit": "0.0057", "lack": "0.0057", "protest": "0.0057", "surpass": "0.0114", "fear": "0.0057", "suffer": "0.0057", "fine": "0.0057", "accus": "0.0057", "cut": "0.0057", "depend": "0.0114", "except": "0.0057", "late": "0.0114", "arrest": "0.0057", "bailout": "0.0057", "volatil": "0.0057", "disrupt": "0.0057", "complaint": "0.0057", "good": "0.0114", "greater": "0.0057", "disclos": "0.0057", "rebound": "0.0057", "stop": "0.0057", "break": "0.0057", "worst": "0.0057", "know": "0.0057", "press": "0.0057", "loss": "0.0057", "bar": "0.0057", "success": "0.0057", "lost": "0.0057", "outperform": "0.0057", "drop": "0.0229", "negat": "0.0057", "resolv": "0.0057", "defens": "0.0057", "benefit": "0.0057", "integr": "0.0057", "lose": "0.0057", "popular": "0.0057", "collaps": "0.0057", "crisi": "0.0057", "prevent": "0.0057", "confid": "0.0057", "slower": "0.0057", "shut": "0.0057", "slowdown": "0.0057", "strongest": "0.0057", "cost": "0.0057", "opportun": "0.0057", "fail": "0.0057", "close": "0.0171", "precipit": "0.0057", "concern": "0.0114", "lead": "0.0057", "profit": "0.0057", "defend": "0.0057", "abl": "0.0057", "bad": "0.0057", "favor": "0.0057", "restructur": "0.0057", "outstand": "0.0057", "deficit": "0.0057", "progress": "0.0057", "boost": "0.0057", "correct": "0.0057", "encourag": "0.0057", "investig": "0.0057", "advanc": "0.0057", "weak": "0.0057", "ban": "0.0057", "slow": "0.0057", "excess": "0.0057", "disput": "0.0057", "strong": "0.0057", "great": "0.0057", "deterior": "0.0057", "unemploy": "0.0057", "contract": "0.0114", "threat": "0.0057", "improv": "0.0057", "allianc": "0.0057", "suspend": "0.0114", "effici": "0.0057", "declin": "0.0343", "win": "0.0057", "bankruptci": "0.0057", "shortag": "0.0057", "cancel": "0.0057", "stabl": "0.0114", "miss": "0.0114", "drought": "0.0057", "damag": "0.0114", "bolster": "0.0057", "better": "0.0057", "question": "0.0057", "construct": "0.0057", "doubt": "0.0057", "downgrad": "0.0057", "threaten": "0.0057", "unexpect": "0.0057", "forc": "0.0114", "hurt": "0.0114", "warn": "0.0057", "gain": "0.0114", "termin": "0.0057", "eas": "0.0057", "highest": "0.0057", "fraud": "0.0057", "default": "0.0057", "seiz": "0.0057", "will": "0.0057", "limit": "0.0114", "posit": "0.0114", "problem": "0.0057", "claim": "0.0057", "weaker": "0.0057", "advantag": "0.0057", "strengthen": "0.0057", "challeng": "0.0057", "premier": "0.0057", "worri": "0.0057", "alleg": "0.0057", "critic": "0.0057", "attract": "0.0057", "sever": "0.0057", "halt": "0.0057", "strength": "0.0057", "delay": "0.0057", "fire": "0.0057", "boom": "0.0057", "reject": "0.0057", "weaken": "0.0057", "difficult": "0.0057", "tighten": "0.0057", "effect": "0.0057", "resign": "0.0057", "alert": "0.0057", "quit": "0.0057", "refin": "0.0057", "postpon": "0.0057", "stabil": "0.0057", "stress": "0.0057", "liquid": "0.0057", "antitrust": "0.0057", "stronger": "0.0057", "su": "0.0057", "inform": "0.0057", "deni": "0.0057", "achiev": "0.0057"}, "2": {"recess": "0.0019", "opposit": "0.0075", "lack": "0.0019", "protest": "0.0019", "surpass": "0.0019", "fear": "0.0037", "suffer": "0.0019", "fine": "0.0093", "accus": "0.0019", "cut": "0.0187", "depend": "0.0037", "except": "0.0037", "late": "0.0075", "arrest": "0.0019", "bailout": "0.0019", "volatil": "0.0037", "disrupt": "0.0037", "complaint": "0.0019", "good": "0.0093", "greater": "0.0019", "disclos": "0.0019", "rebound": "0.0037", "stop": "0.0037", "break": "0.0019", "worst": "0.0224", "know": "0.0037", "press": "0.0075", "loss": "0.0149", "bar": "0.0019", "success": "0.0019", "lost": "0.0205", "outperform": "0.0037", "drop": "0.0578", "negat": "0.0056", "resolv": "0.0019", "defens": "0.0037", "benefit": "0.0149", "integr": "0.0019", "lose": "0.0019", "popular": "0.0019", "collaps": "0.0019", "crisi": "0.0037", "prevent": "0.0056", "confid": "0.0019", "slower": "0.0019", "shut": "0.0019", "slowdown": "0.0019", "strongest": "0.0019", "cost": "0.0299", "opportun": "0.0075", "fail": "0.0075", "close": "0.0168", "precipit": "0.0019", "concern": "0.0149", "lead": "0.0075", "profit": "0.0261", "defend": "0.0019", "abl": "0.0056", "bad": "0.0019", "favor": "0.0037", "restructur": "0.0037", "outstand": "0.0019", "deficit": "0.0056", "progress": "0.0019", "boost": "0.0149", "correct": "0.0037", "encourag": "0.0019", "investig": "0.0037", "advanc": "0.0224", "weak": "0.0019", "ban": "0.0019", "slow": "0.0093", "excess": "0.0019", "disput": "0.0056", "strong": "0.0019", "great": "0.0019", "deterior": "0.0019", "unemploy": "0.0019", "contract": "0.0280", "threat": "0.0019", "improv": "0.0075", "allianc": "0.0019", "suspend": "0.0056", "effici": "0.0037", "declin": "0.0728", "win": "0.0037", "bankruptci": "0.0019", "shortag": "0.0019", "cancel": "0.0037", "stabl": "0.0075", "miss": "0.0037", "drought": "0.0019", "damag": "0.0205", "bolster": "0.0056", "better": "0.0056", "question": "0.0019", "construct": "0.0093", "doubt": "0.0019", "downgrad": "0.0056", "threaten": "0.0019", "unexpect": "0.0037", "forc": "0.0075", "hurt": "0.0037", "warn": "0.0019", "gain": "0.0541", "termin": "0.0019", "eas": "0.0131", "highest": "0.0224", "fraud": "0.0019", "default": "0.0075", "seiz": "0.0019", "will": "0.0037", "limit": "0.0056", "posit": "0.0075", "problem": "0.0037", "claim": "0.0168", "weaker": "0.0019", "advantag": "0.0056", "strengthen": "0.0131", "challeng": "0.0019", "premier": "0.0019", "worri": "0.0019", "alleg": "0.0037", "critic": "0.0019", "attract": "0.0075", "sever": "0.0019", "halt": "0.0037", "strength": "0.0019", "delay": "0.0205", "fire": "0.0019", "boom": "0.0019", "reject": "0.0019", "weaken": "0.0187", "difficult": "0.0019", "tighten": "0.0019", "effect": "0.0019", "resign": "0.0019", "alert": "0.0019", "quit": "0.0037", "refin": "0.0019", "postpon": "0.0037", "stabil": "0.0019", "stress": "0.0037", "liquid": "0.0037", "antitrust": "0.0019", "stronger": "0.0056", "su": "0.0019", "inform": "0.0075", "deni": "0.0056", "achiev": "0.0037"}, "3": {"recess": "0.0058", "opposit": "0.0041", "lack": "0.0033", "protest": "0.0058", "surpass": "0.0033", "fear": "0.0025", "suffer": "0.0008", "fine": "0.0041", "accus": "0.0008", "cut": "0.0256", "depend": "0.0041", "except": "0.0008", "late": "0.0124", "arrest": "0.0033", "bailout": "0.0017", "volatil": "0.0017", "disrupt": "0.0025", "complaint": "0.0008", "good": "0.0099", "greater": "0.0041", "disclos": "0.0017", "rebound": "0.0033", "stop": "0.0025", "break": "0.0025", "worst": "0.0116", "know": "0.0017", "press": "0.0058", "loss": "0.0091", "bar": "0.0008", "success": "0.0017", "lost": "0.0116", "outperform": "0.0017", "drop": "0.0562", "negat": "0.0025", "resolv": "0.0017", "defens": "0.0033", "benefit": "0.0108", "integr": "0.0132", "lose": "0.0066", "popular": "0.0025", "collaps": "0.0008", "crisi": "0.0074", "prevent": "0.0058", "confid": "0.0050", "slower": "0.0025", "shut": "0.0017", "slowdown": "0.0008", "strongest": "0.0025", "cost": "0.0289", "opportun": "0.0041", "fail": "0.0033", "close": "0.0281", "precipit": "0.0008", "concern": "0.0223", "lead": "0.0058", "profit": "0.0298", "defend": "0.0008", "abl": "0.0033", "bad": "0.0008", "favor": "0.0041", "restructur": "0.0017", "outstand": "0.0025", "deficit": "0.0124", "progress": "0.0033", "boost": "0.0273", "correct": "0.0041", "encourag": "0.0017", "investig": "0.0025", "advanc": "0.0232", "weak": "0.0008", "ban": "0.0050", "slow": "0.0074", "excess": "0.0033", "disput": "0.0025", "strong": "0.0116", "great": "0.0025", "deterior": "0.0008", "unemploy": "0.0066", "contract": "0.0174", "threat": "0.0025", "improv": "0.0132", "allianc": "0.0017", "suspend": "0.0066", "effici": "0.0041", "declin": "0.0529", "win": "0.0033", "bankruptci": "0.0008", "shortag": "0.0008", "cancel": "0.0025", "stabl": "0.0041", "miss": "0.0041", "drought": "0.0008", "damag": "0.0165", "bolster": "0.0041", "better": "0.0041", "question": "0.0025", "construct": "0.0116", "doubt": "0.0008", "downgrad": "0.0008", "threaten": "0.0025", "unexpect": "0.0008", "forc": "0.0050", "hurt": "0.0083", "warn": "0.0008", "gain": "0.0852", "termin": "0.0074", "eas": "0.0132", "highest": "0.0356", "fraud": "0.0008", "default": "0.0058", "seiz": "0.0017", "will": "0.0017", "limit": "0.0074", "posit": "0.0108", "problem": "0.0033", "claim": "0.0050", "weaker": "0.0017", "advantag": "0.0025", "strengthen": "0.0116", "challeng": "0.0017", "premier": "0.0008", "worri": "0.0008", "alleg": "0.0017", "critic": "0.0025", "attract": "0.0116", "sever": "0.0017", "halt": "0.0017", "strength": "0.0008", "delay": "0.0149", "fire": "0.0041", "boom": "0.0017", "reject": "0.0008", "weaken": "0.0074", "difficult": "0.0017", "tighten": "0.0008", "effect": "0.0041", "resign": "0.0008", "alert": "0.0008", "quit": "0.0025", "refin": "0.0025", "postpon": "0.0033", "stabil": "0.0083", "stress": "0.0025", "liquid": "0.0083", "antitrust": "0.0008", "stronger": "0.0066", "su": "0.0017", "inform": "0.0058", "deni": "0.0017", "achiev": "0.0033"}, "4": {"recess": "0.0056", "opposit": "0.0028", "lack": "0.0028", "protest": "0.0169", "surpass": "0.0085", "fear": "0.0028", "suffer": "0.0028", "fine": "0.0028", "accus": "0.0028", "cut": "0.0169", "depend": "0.0141", "except": "0.0028", "late": "0.0056", "arrest": "0.0028", "bailout": "0.0028", "volatil": "0.0028", "disrupt": "0.0028", "complaint": "0.0028", "good": "0.0141", "greater": "0.0056", "disclos": "0.0056", "rebound": "0.0056", "stop": "0.0085", "break": "0.0028", "worst": "0.0056", "know": "0.0028", "press": "0.0113", "loss": "0.0056", "bar": "0.0028", "success": "0.0028", "lost": "0.0028", "outperform": "0.0056", "drop": "0.0366", "negat": "0.0028", "resolv": "0.0056", "defens": "0.0056", "benefit": "0.0056", "integr": "0.0338", "lose": "0.0056", "popular": "0.0085", "collaps": "0.0028", "crisi": "0.0113", "prevent": "0.0028", "confid": "0.0028", "slower": "0.0028", "shut": "0.0028", "slowdown": "0.0028", "strongest": "0.0028", "cost": "0.0169", "opportun": "0.0028", "fail": "0.0141", "close": "0.0141", "precipit": "0.0028", "concern": "0.0056", "lead": "0.0113", "profit": "0.0254", "defend": "0.0028", "abl": "0.0028", "bad": "0.0028", "favor": "0.0028", "restructur": "0.0028", "outstand": "0.0028", "deficit": "0.0141", "progress": "0.0028", "boost": "0.0282", "correct": "0.0085", "encourag": "0.0085", "investig": "0.0056", "advanc": "0.0056", "weak": "0.0028", "ban": "0.0028", "slow": "0.0085", "excess": "0.0028", "disput": "0.0056", "strong": "0.0113", "great": "0.0028", "deterior": "0.0028", "unemploy": "0.0028", "contract": "0.0169", "threat": "0.0028", "improv": "0.0085", "allianc": "0.0113", "suspend": "0.0028", "effici": "0.0028", "declin": "0.0394", "win": "0.0141", "bankruptci": "0.0028", "shortag": "0.0028", "cancel": "0.0056", "stabl": "0.0056", "miss": "0.0028", "drought": "0.0028", "damag": "0.0085", "bolster": "0.0028", "better": "0.0028", "question": "0.0085", "construct": "0.0056", "doubt": "0.0028", "downgrad": "0.0028", "threaten": "0.0028", "unexpect": "0.0056", "forc": "0.0085", "hurt": "0.0028", "warn": "0.0028", "gain": "0.0648", "termin": "0.0056", "eas": "0.0028", "highest": "0.0085", "fraud": "0.0028", "default": "0.0141", "seiz": "0.0028", "will": "0.0028", "limit": "0.0028", "posit": "0.0141", "problem": "0.0141", "claim": "0.0028", "weaker": "0.0028", "advantag": "0.0056", "strengthen": "0.0028", "challeng": "0.0028", "premier": "0.0028", "worri": "0.0028", "alleg": "0.0028", "critic": "0.0028", "attract": "0.0141", "sever": "0.0028", "halt": "0.0028", "strength": "0.0028", "delay": "0.0085", "fire": "0.0056", "boom": "0.0028", "reject": "0.0028", "weaken": "0.0085", "difficult": "0.0028", "tighten": "0.0028", "effect": "0.0028", "resign": "0.0028", "alert": "0.0028", "quit": "0.0056", "refin": "0.0056", "postpon": "0.0028", "stabil": "0.0028", "stress": "0.0085", "liquid": "0.0085", "antitrust": "0.0028", "stronger": "0.0028", "su": "0.0028", "inform": "0.0028", "deni": "0.0028", "achiev": "0.0028"}, "5": {"recess": "0.0023", "opposit": "0.0023", "lack": "0.0023", "protest": "0.0023", "surpass": "0.0115", "fear": "0.0023", "suffer": "0.0023", "fine": "0.0023", "accus": "0.0023", "cut": "0.0230", "depend": "0.0092", "except": "0.0023", "late": "0.0046", "arrest": "0.0023", "bailout": "0.0046", "volatil": "0.0023", "disrupt": "0.0069", "complaint": "0.0023", "good": "0.0184", "greater": "0.0046", "disclos": "0.0023", "rebound": "0.0069", "stop": "0.0046", "break": "0.0046", "worst": "0.0046", "know": "0.0023", "press": "0.0023", "loss": "0.0069", "bar": "0.0023", "success": "0.0023", "lost": "0.0138", "outperform": "0.0023", "drop": "0.0253", "negat": "0.0023", "resolv": "0.0023", "defens": "0.0023", "benefit": "0.0092", "integr": "0.0046", "lose": "0.0023", "popular": "0.0023", "collaps": "0.0023", "crisi": "0.0092", "prevent": "0.0069", "confid": "0.0092", "slower": "0.0023", "shut": "0.0023", "slowdown": "0.0023", "strongest": "0.0023", "cost": "0.0345", "opportun": "0.0023", "fail": "0.0023", "close": "0.0184", "precipit": "0.0023", "concern": "0.0115", "lead": "0.0069", "profit": "0.0138", "defend": "0.0023", "abl": "0.0046", "bad": "0.0023", "favor": "0.0046", "restructur": "0.0023", "outstand": "0.0023", "deficit": "0.0069", "progress": "0.0023", "boost": "0.0345", "correct": "0.0023", "encourag": "0.0046", "investig": "0.0023", "advanc": "0.0437", "weak": "0.0069", "ban": "0.0023", "slow": "0.0023", "excess": "0.0069", "disput": "0.0023", "strong": "0.0023", "great": "0.0023", "deterior": "0.0023", "unemploy": "0.0115", "contract": "0.0184", "threat": "0.0023", "improv": "0.0115", "allianc": "0.0023", "suspend": "0.0046", "effici": "0.0023", "declin": "0.0299", "win": "0.0023", "bankruptci": "0.0023", "shortag": "0.0023", "cancel": "0.0023", "stabl": "0.0069", "miss": "0.0046", "drought": "0.0023", "damag": "0.0069", "bolster": "0.0046", "better": "0.0023", "question": "0.0046", "construct": "0.0092", "doubt": "0.0023", "downgrad": "0.0023", "threaten": "0.0069", "unexpect": "0.0023", "forc": "0.0092", "hurt": "0.0092", "warn": "0.0046", "gain": "0.1195", "termin": "0.0023", "eas": "0.0230", "highest": "0.0069", "fraud": "0.0023", "default": "0.0023", "seiz": "0.0023", "will": "0.0023", "limit": "0.0092", "posit": "0.0207", "problem": "0.0023", "claim": "0.0092", "weaker": "0.0069", "advantag": "0.0046", "strengthen": "0.0161", "challeng": "0.0023", "premier": "0.0023", "worri": "0.0023", "alleg": "0.0023", "critic": "0.0023", "attract": "0.0115", "sever": "0.0023", "halt": "0.0023", "strength": "0.0023", "delay": "0.0023", "fire": "0.0023", "boom": "0.0023", "reject": "0.0023", "weaken": "0.0092", "difficult": "0.0046", "tighten": "0.0023", "effect": "0.0069", "resign": "0.0046", "alert": "0.0023", "quit": "0.0069", "refin": "0.0023", "postpon": "0.0023", "stabil": "0.0069", "stress": "0.0023", "liquid": "0.0046", "antitrust": "0.0023", "stronger": "0.0023", "su": "0.0046", "inform": "0.0023", "deni": "0.0023", "achiev": "0.0046"}, "6": {"recess": "0.0066", "opposit": "0.0066", "lack": "0.0066", "protest": "0.0066", "surpass": "0.0066", "fear": "0.0066", "suffer": "0.0066", "fine": "0.0066", "accus": "0.0066", "cut": "0.0066", "depend": "0.0066", "except": "0.0066", "late": "0.0066", "arrest": "0.0066", "bailout": "0.0066", "volatil": "0.0066", "disrupt": "0.0066", "complaint": "0.0066", "good": "0.0066", "greater": "0.0066", "disclos": "0.0066", "rebound": "0.0066", "stop": "0.0066", "break": "0.0066", "worst": "0.0066", "know": "0.0066", "press": "0.0066", "loss": "0.0066", "bar": "0.0066", "success": "0.0066", "lost": "0.0066", "outperform": "0.0066", "drop": "0.0066", "negat": "0.0066", "resolv": "0.0066", "defens": "0.0066", "benefit": "0.0066", "integr": "0.0066", "lose": "0.0066", "popular": "0.0066", "collaps": "0.0066", "crisi": "0.0066", "prevent": "0.0066", "confid": "0.0066", "slower": "0.0066", "shut": "0.0066", "slowdown": "0.0066", "strongest": "0.0066", "cost": "0.0066", "opportun": "0.0066", "fail": "0.0066", "close": "0.0066", "precipit": "0.0066", "concern": "0.0066", "lead": "0.0066", "profit": "0.0066", "defend": "0.0066", "abl": "0.0066", "bad": "0.0066", "favor": "0.0066", "restructur": "0.0066", "outstand": "0.0066", "deficit": "0.0066", "progress": "0.0066", "boost": "0.0132", "correct": "0.0066", "encourag": "0.0066", "investig": "0.0066", "advanc": "0.0066", "weak": "0.0066", "ban": "0.0066", "slow": "0.0066", "excess": "0.0066", "disput": "0.0066", "strong": "0.0066", "great": "0.0066", "deterior": "0.0066", "unemploy": "0.0066", "contract": "0.0066", "threat": "0.0066", "improv": "0.0066", "allianc": "0.0066", "suspend": "0.0066", "effici": "0.0066", "declin": "0.0066", "win": "0.0066", "bankruptci": "0.0066", "shortag": "0.0066", "cancel": "0.0066", "stabl": "0.0066", "miss": "0.0066", "drought": "0.0066", "damag": "0.0066", "bolster": "0.0066", "better": "0.0066", "question": "0.0066", "construct": "0.0066", "doubt": "0.0066", "downgrad": "0.0066", "threaten": "0.0066", "unexpect": "0.0066", "forc": "0.0066", "hurt": "0.0066", "warn": "0.0066", "gain": "0.0066", "termin": "0.0066", "eas": "0.0066", "highest": "0.0066", "fraud": "0.0066", "default": "0.0066", "seiz": "0.0066", "will": "0.0066", "limit": "0.0066", "posit": "0.0066", "problem": "0.0066", "claim": "0.0066", "weaker": "0.0066", "advantag": "0.0066", "strengthen": "0.0066", "challeng": "0.0066", "premier": "0.0066", "worri": "0.0066", "alleg": "0.0066", "critic": "0.0066", "attract": "0.0066", "sever": "0.0066", "halt": "0.0066", "strength": "0.0066", "delay": "0.0066", "fire": "0.0066", "boom": "0.0066", "reject": "0.0066", "weaken": "0.0066", "difficult": "0.0066", "tighten": "0.0066", "effect": "0.0066", "resign": "0.0066", "alert": "0.0066", "quit": "0.0066", "refin": "0.0066", "postpon": "0.0066", "stabil": "0.0066", "stress": "0.0066", "liquid": "0.0066", "antitrust": "0.0066", "stronger": "0.0066", "su": "0.0066", "inform": "0.0066", "deni": "0.0066", "achiev": "0.0066"}, "7": {"recess": "0.0079", "opposit": "0.0047", "lack": "0.0032", "protest": "0.0032", "surpass": "0.0016", "fear": "0.0079", "suffer": "0.0016", "fine": "0.0016", "accus": "0.0016", "cut": "0.0300", "depend": "0.0016", "except": "0.0032", "late": "0.0047", "arrest": "0.0016", "bailout": "0.0016", "volatil": "0.0063", "disrupt": "0.0016", "complaint": "0.0016", "good": "0.0126", "greater": "0.0016", "disclos": "0.0032", "rebound": "0.0063", "stop": "0.0016", "break": "0.0016", "worst": "0.0047", "know": "0.0032", "press": "0.0032", "loss": "0.0284", "bar": "0.0016", "success": "0.0032", "lost": "0.0237", "outperform": "0.0032", "drop": "0.0741", "negat": "0.0063", "resolv": "0.0032", "defens": "0.0032", "benefit": "0.0063", "integr": "0.0016", "lose": "0.0032", "popular": "0.0016", "collaps": "0.0016", "crisi": "0.0063", "prevent": "0.0016", "confid": "0.0032", "slower": "0.0016", "shut": "0.0063", "slowdown": "0.0016", "strongest": "0.0047", "cost": "0.0174", "opportun": "0.0079", "fail": "0.0095", "close": "0.0221", "precipit": "0.0016", "concern": "0.0237", "lead": "0.0047", "profit": "0.0410", "defend": "0.0016", "abl": "0.0032", "bad": "0.0032", "favor": "0.0063", "restructur": "0.0016", "outstand": "0.0047", "deficit": "0.0095", "progress": "0.0032", "boost": "0.0126", "correct": "0.0032", "encourag": "0.0016", "investig": "0.0016", "advanc": "0.0268", "weak": "0.0016", "ban": "0.0095", "slow": "0.0079", "excess": "0.0032", "disput": "0.0016", "strong": "0.0032", "great": "0.0016", "deterior": "0.0016", "unemploy": "0.0032", "contract": "0.0142", "threat": "0.0032", "improv": "0.0110", "allianc": "0.0079", "suspend": "0.0047", "effici": "0.0016", "declin": "0.0694", "win": "0.0016", "bankruptci": "0.0016", "shortag": "0.0016", "cancel": "0.0032", "stabl": "0.0032", "miss": "0.0032", "drought": "0.0016", "damag": "0.0032", "bolster": "0.0063", "better": "0.0063", "question": "0.0032", "construct": "0.0047", "doubt": "0.0016", "downgrad": "0.0047", "threaten": "0.0016", "unexpect": "0.0032", "forc": "0.0016", "hurt": "0.0032", "warn": "0.0016", "gain": "0.0883", "termin": "0.0110", "eas": "0.0079", "highest": "0.0252", "fraud": "0.0016", "default": "0.0032", "seiz": "0.0016", "will": "0.0016", "limit": "0.0063", "posit": "0.0110", "problem": "0.0032", "claim": "0.0016", "weaker": "0.0016", "advantag": "0.0032", "strengthen": "0.0079", "challeng": "0.0016", "premier": "0.0016", "worri": "0.0016", "alleg": "0.0016", "critic": "0.0032", "attract": "0.0095", "sever": "0.0047", "halt": "0.0032", "strength": "0.0032", "delay": "0.0095", "fire": "0.0016", "boom": "0.0016", "reject": "0.0032", "weaken": "0.0079", "difficult": "0.0032", "tighten": "0.0016", "effect": "0.0016", "resign": "0.0016", "alert": "0.0016", "quit": "0.0063", "refin": "0.0032", "postpon": "0.0047", "stabil": "0.0063", "stress": "0.0016", "liquid": "0.0063", "antitrust": "0.0016", "stronger": "0.0063", "su": "0.0032", "inform": "0.0016", "deni": "0.0016", "achiev": "0.0016"}, "8": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "9": {"recess": "0.0045", "opposit": "0.0045", "lack": "0.0182", "protest": "0.0045", "surpass": "0.0045", "fear": "0.0045", "suffer": "0.0045", "fine": "0.0045", "accus": "0.0045", "cut": "0.0091", "depend": "0.0045", "except": "0.0045", "late": "0.0091", "arrest": "0.0045", "bailout": "0.0045", "volatil": "0.0045", "disrupt": "0.0045", "complaint": "0.0045", "good": "0.0045", "greater": "0.0045", "disclos": "0.0045", "rebound": "0.0045", "stop": "0.0091", "break": "0.0045", "worst": "0.0045", "know": "0.0045", "press": "0.0045", "loss": "0.0045", "bar": "0.0045", "success": "0.0091", "lost": "0.0045", "outperform": "0.0091", "drop": "0.0455", "negat": "0.0045", "resolv": "0.0045", "defens": "0.0045", "benefit": "0.0045", "integr": "0.0136", "lose": "0.0045", "popular": "0.0045", "collaps": "0.0045", "crisi": "0.0045", "prevent": "0.0045", "confid": "0.0182", "slower": "0.0045", "shut": "0.0045", "slowdown": "0.0045", "strongest": "0.0045", "cost": "0.0045", "opportun": "0.0091", "fail": "0.0091", "close": "0.0182", "precipit": "0.0045", "concern": "0.0136", "lead": "0.0045", "profit": "0.0045", "defend": "0.0045", "abl": "0.0045", "bad": "0.0045", "favor": "0.0045", "restructur": "0.0045", "outstand": "0.0045", "deficit": "0.0091", "progress": "0.0045", "boost": "0.0182", "correct": "0.0045", "encourag": "0.0045", "investig": "0.0045", "advanc": "0.0045", "weak": "0.0091", "ban": "0.0045", "slow": "0.0045", "excess": "0.0045", "disput": "0.0045", "strong": "0.0045", "great": "0.0045", "deterior": "0.0045", "unemploy": "0.0045", "contract": "0.0091", "threat": "0.0045", "improv": "0.0045", "allianc": "0.0045", "suspend": "0.0045", "effici": "0.0045", "declin": "0.0136", "win": "0.0136", "bankruptci": "0.0045", "shortag": "0.0045", "cancel": "0.0045", "stabl": "0.0045", "miss": "0.0045", "drought": "0.0045", "damag": "0.0045", "bolster": "0.0045", "better": "0.0045", "question": "0.0045", "construct": "0.0136", "doubt": "0.0045", "downgrad": "0.0045", "threaten": "0.0136", "unexpect": "0.0045", "forc": "0.0045", "hurt": "0.0045", "warn": "0.0045", "gain": "0.0455", "termin": "0.0045", "eas": "0.0045", "highest": "0.0091", "fraud": "0.0045", "default": "0.0045", "seiz": "0.0091", "will": "0.0045", "limit": "0.0045", "posit": "0.0091", "problem": "0.0045", "claim": "0.0045", "weaker": "0.0045", "advantag": "0.0045", "strengthen": "0.0182", "challeng": "0.0045", "premier": "0.0045", "worri": "0.0045", "alleg": "0.0045", "critic": "0.0045", "attract": "0.0136", "sever": "0.0045", "halt": "0.0045", "strength": "0.0045", "delay": "0.0227", "fire": "0.0045", "boom": "0.0045", "reject": "0.0045", "weaken": "0.0091", "difficult": "0.0091", "tighten": "0.0045", "effect": "0.0045", "resign": "0.0045", "alert": "0.0045", "quit": "0.0045", "refin": "0.0045", "postpon": "0.0045", "stabil": "0.0045", "stress": "0.0045", "liquid": "0.0091", "antitrust": "0.0045", "stronger": "0.0045", "su": "0.0045", "inform": "0.0136", "deni": "0.0045", "achiev": "0.0091"}, "10": {"recess": "0.0066", "opposit": "0.0066", "lack": "0.0022", "protest": "0.0044", "surpass": "0.0022", "fear": "0.0087", "suffer": "0.0022", "fine": "0.0022", "accus": "0.0022", "cut": "0.0087", "depend": "0.0044", "except": "0.0022", "late": "0.0044", "arrest": "0.0022", "bailout": "0.0087", "volatil": "0.0022", "disrupt": "0.0044", "complaint": "0.0022", "good": "0.0197", "greater": "0.0066", "disclos": "0.0044", "rebound": "0.0022", "stop": "0.0022", "break": "0.0022", "worst": "0.0044", "know": "0.0022", "press": "0.0066", "loss": "0.0044", "bar": "0.0022", "success": "0.0022", "lost": "0.0197", "outperform": "0.0044", "drop": "0.0808", "negat": "0.0044", "resolv": "0.0022", "defens": "0.0044", "benefit": "0.0153", "integr": "0.0109", "lose": "0.0066", "popular": "0.0022", "collaps": "0.0022", "crisi": "0.0044", "prevent": "0.0044", "confid": "0.0066", "slower": "0.0044", "shut": "0.0066", "slowdown": "0.0022", "strongest": "0.0044", "cost": "0.0306", "opportun": "0.0044", "fail": "0.0087", "close": "0.0197", "precipit": "0.0022", "concern": "0.0197", "lead": "0.0044", "profit": "0.0131", "defend": "0.0022", "abl": "0.0087", "bad": "0.0022", "favor": "0.0022", "restructur": "0.0022", "outstand": "0.0022", "deficit": "0.0109", "progress": "0.0044", "boost": "0.0175", "correct": "0.0066", "encourag": "0.0044", "investig": "0.0066", "advanc": "0.0306", "weak": "0.0044", "ban": "0.0022", "slow": "0.0066", "excess": "0.0044", "disput": "0.0022", "strong": "0.0022", "great": "0.0022", "deterior": "0.0022", "unemploy": "0.0066", "contract": "0.0087", "threat": "0.0022", "improv": "0.0044", "allianc": "0.0087", "suspend": "0.0044", "effici": "0.0022", "declin": "0.0524", "win": "0.0044", "bankruptci": "0.0022", "shortag": "0.0022", "cancel": "0.0022", "stabl": "0.0022", "miss": "0.0022", "drought": "0.0022", "damag": "0.0022", "bolster": "0.0022", "better": "0.0044", "question": "0.0044", "construct": "0.0044", "doubt": "0.0044", "downgrad": "0.0022", "threaten": "0.0066", "unexpect": "0.0022", "forc": "0.0109", "hurt": "0.0022", "warn": "0.0022", "gain": "0.0721", "termin": "0.0022", "eas": "0.0131", "highest": "0.0306", "fraud": "0.0022", "default": "0.0022", "seiz": "0.0022", "will": "0.0022", "limit": "0.0109", "posit": "0.0131", "problem": "0.0022", "claim": "0.0022", "weaker": "0.0022", "advantag": "0.0022", "strengthen": "0.0087", "challeng": "0.0022", "premier": "0.0022", "worri": "0.0022", "alleg": "0.0022", "critic": "0.0022", "attract": "0.0066", "sever": "0.0066", "halt": "0.0022", "strength": "0.0022", "delay": "0.0218", "fire": "0.0022", "boom": "0.0044", "reject": "0.0022", "weaken": "0.0066", "difficult": "0.0022", "tighten": "0.0044", "effect": "0.0022", "resign": "0.0022", "alert": "0.0022", "quit": "0.0022", "refin": "0.0022", "postpon": "0.0044", "stabil": "0.0044", "stress": "0.0022", "liquid": "0.0066", "antitrust": "0.0022", "stronger": "0.0044", "su": "0.0022", "inform": "0.0087", "deni": "0.0044", "achiev": "0.0044"}, "11": {"recess": "0.0079", "opposit": "0.0089", "lack": "0.0030", "protest": "0.0059", "surpass": "0.0040", "fear": "0.0020", "suffer": "0.0010", "fine": "0.0010", "accus": "0.0030", "cut": "0.0227", "depend": "0.0099", "except": "0.0020", "late": "0.0069", "arrest": "0.0020", "bailout": "0.0010", "volatil": "0.0020", "disrupt": "0.0020", "complaint": "0.0010", "good": "0.0099", "greater": "0.0099", "disclos": "0.0010", "rebound": "0.0020", "stop": "0.0049", "break": "0.0059", "worst": "0.0059", "know": "0.0049", "press": "0.0049", "loss": "0.0109", "bar": "0.0010", "success": "0.0059", "lost": "0.0099", "outperform": "0.0030", "drop": "0.0484", "negat": "0.0030", "resolv": "0.0030", "defens": "0.0059", "benefit": "0.0079", "integr": "0.0188", "lose": "0.0109", "popular": "0.0069", "collaps": "0.0010", "crisi": "0.0040", "prevent": "0.0030", "confid": "0.0049", "slower": "0.0040", "shut": "0.0010", "slowdown": "0.0010", "strongest": "0.0020", "cost": "0.0217", "opportun": "0.0040", "fail": "0.0099", "close": "0.0296", "precipit": "0.0010", "concern": "0.0109", "lead": "0.0049", "profit": "0.0296", "defend": "0.0020", "abl": "0.0049", "bad": "0.0010", "favor": "0.0030", "restructur": "0.0020", "outstand": "0.0020", "deficit": "0.0178", "progress": "0.0010", "boost": "0.0375", "correct": "0.0049", "encourag": "0.0020", "investig": "0.0030", "advanc": "0.0198", "weak": "0.0020", "ban": "0.0020", "slow": "0.0079", "excess": "0.0040", "disput": "0.0049", "strong": "0.0049", "great": "0.0010", "deterior": "0.0010", "unemploy": "0.0020", "contract": "0.0128", "threat": "0.0020", "improv": "0.0158", "allianc": "0.0089", "suspend": "0.0059", "effici": "0.0049", "declin": "0.0613", "win": "0.0089", "bankruptci": "0.0079", "shortag": "0.0020", "cancel": "0.0010", "stabl": "0.0010", "miss": "0.0020", "drought": "0.0010", "damag": "0.0049", "bolster": "0.0059", "better": "0.0040", "question": "0.0020", "construct": "0.0178", "doubt": "0.0030", "downgrad": "0.0010", "threaten": "0.0049", "unexpect": "0.0010", "forc": "0.0069", "hurt": "0.0049", "warn": "0.0020", "gain": "0.0731", "termin": "0.0010", "eas": "0.0119", "highest": "0.0217", "fraud": "0.0010", "default": "0.0049", "seiz": "0.0020", "will": "0.0030", "limit": "0.0069", "posit": "0.0079", "problem": "0.0049", "claim": "0.0049", "weaker": "0.0020", "advantag": "0.0040", "strengthen": "0.0079", "challeng": "0.0020", "premier": "0.0010", "worri": "0.0010", "alleg": "0.0030", "critic": "0.0030", "attract": "0.0128", "sever": "0.0030", "halt": "0.0010", "strength": "0.0010", "delay": "0.0138", "fire": "0.0049", "boom": "0.0059", "reject": "0.0010", "weaken": "0.0109", "difficult": "0.0020", "tighten": "0.0020", "effect": "0.0010", "resign": "0.0030", "alert": "0.0030", "quit": "0.0030", "refin": "0.0010", "postpon": "0.0049", "stabil": "0.0030", "stress": "0.0020", "liquid": "0.0069", "antitrust": "0.0010", "stronger": "0.0040", "su": "0.0010", "inform": "0.0069", "deni": "0.0030", "achiev": "0.0040"}, "12": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "13": {"recess": "0.0061", "opposit": "0.0061", "lack": "0.0061", "protest": "0.0061", "surpass": "0.0061", "fear": "0.0061", "suffer": "0.0061", "fine": "0.0061", "accus": "0.0061", "cut": "0.0121", "depend": "0.0061", "except": "0.0061", "late": "0.0061", "arrest": "0.0061", "bailout": "0.0061", "volatil": "0.0061", "disrupt": "0.0061", "complaint": "0.0061", "good": "0.0061", "greater": "0.0061", "disclos": "0.0061", "rebound": "0.0121", "stop": "0.0061", "break": "0.0061", "worst": "0.0061", "know": "0.0061", "press": "0.0061", "loss": "0.0061", "bar": "0.0061", "success": "0.0061", "lost": "0.0061", "outperform": "0.0061", "drop": "0.0182", "negat": "0.0061", "resolv": "0.0061", "defens": "0.0061", "benefit": "0.0061", "integr": "0.0061", "lose": "0.0061", "popular": "0.0061", "collaps": "0.0061", "crisi": "0.0061", "prevent": "0.0061", "confid": "0.0061", "slower": "0.0061", "shut": "0.0061", "slowdown": "0.0061", "strongest": "0.0061", "cost": "0.0061", "opportun": "0.0061", "fail": "0.0061", "close": "0.0061", "precipit": "0.0061", "concern": "0.0121", "lead": "0.0061", "profit": "0.0303", "defend": "0.0061", "abl": "0.0061", "bad": "0.0061", "favor": "0.0061", "restructur": "0.0061", "outstand": "0.0061", "deficit": "0.0061", "progress": "0.0061", "boost": "0.0121", "correct": "0.0061", "encourag": "0.0061", "investig": "0.0061", "advanc": "0.0061", "weak": "0.0061", "ban": "0.0061", "slow": "0.0061", "excess": "0.0061", "disput": "0.0061", "strong": "0.0061", "great": "0.0061", "deterior": "0.0061", "unemploy": "0.0121", "contract": "0.0061", "threat": "0.0061", "improv": "0.0061", "allianc": "0.0061", "suspend": "0.0061", "effici": "0.0061", "declin": "0.0061", "win": "0.0061", "bankruptci": "0.0061", "shortag": "0.0061", "cancel": "0.0061", "stabl": "0.0061", "miss": "0.0061", "drought": "0.0061", "damag": "0.0121", "bolster": "0.0061", "better": "0.0061", "question": "0.0061", "construct": "0.0061", "doubt": "0.0061", "downgrad": "0.0061", "threaten": "0.0061", "unexpect": "0.0121", "forc": "0.0061", "hurt": "0.0061", "warn": "0.0061", "gain": "0.0182", "termin": "0.0061", "eas": "0.0061", "highest": "0.0061", "fraud": "0.0061", "default": "0.0061", "seiz": "0.0061", "will": "0.0061", "limit": "0.0061", "posit": "0.0061", "problem": "0.0061", "claim": "0.0061", "weaker": "0.0061", "advantag": "0.0061", "strengthen": "0.0061", "challeng": "0.0061", "premier": "0.0061", "worri": "0.0061", "alleg": "0.0061", "critic": "0.0061", "attract": "0.0061", "sever": "0.0061", "halt": "0.0061", "strength": "0.0061", "delay": "0.0061", "fire": "0.0061", "boom": "0.0061", "reject": "0.0061", "weaken": "0.0061", "difficult": "0.0061", "tighten": "0.0061", "effect": "0.0061", "resign": "0.0061", "alert": "0.0061", "quit": "0.0061", "refin": "0.0061", "postpon": "0.0061", "stabil": "0.0061", "stress": "0.0061", "liquid": "0.0061", "antitrust": "0.0061", "stronger": "0.0061", "su": "0.0061", "inform": "0.0061", "deni": "0.0061", "achiev": "0.0061"}, "14": {"recess": "0.0186", "opposit": "0.0013", "lack": "0.0040", "protest": "0.0013", "surpass": "0.0053", "fear": "0.0013", "suffer": "0.0013", "fine": "0.0013", "accus": "0.0013", "cut": "0.0279", "depend": "0.0013", "except": "0.0013", "late": "0.0066", "arrest": "0.0027", "bailout": "0.0027", "volatil": "0.0027", "disrupt": "0.0040", "complaint": "0.0013", "good": "0.0040", "greater": "0.0040", "disclos": "0.0013", "rebound": "0.0053", "stop": "0.0027", "break": "0.0027", "worst": "0.0053", "know": "0.0027", "press": "0.0040", "loss": "0.0093", "bar": "0.0013", "success": "0.0027", "lost": "0.0146", "outperform": "0.0013", "drop": "0.0424", "negat": "0.0027", "resolv": "0.0053", "defens": "0.0027", "benefit": "0.0066", "integr": "0.0080", "lose": "0.0053", "popular": "0.0066", "collaps": "0.0013", "crisi": "0.0053", "prevent": "0.0040", "confid": "0.0066", "slower": "0.0066", "shut": "0.0013", "slowdown": "0.0027", "strongest": "0.0027", "cost": "0.0212", "opportun": "0.0027", "fail": "0.0080", "close": "0.0305", "precipit": "0.0013", "concern": "0.0159", "lead": "0.0027", "profit": "0.0279", "defend": "0.0027", "abl": "0.0040", "bad": "0.0027", "favor": "0.0013", "restructur": "0.0027", "outstand": "0.0013", "deficit": "0.0159", "progress": "0.0013", "boost": "0.0318", "correct": "0.0013", "encourag": "0.0013", "investig": "0.0027", "advanc": "0.0199", "weak": "0.0027", "ban": "0.0013", "slow": "0.0106", "excess": "0.0013", "disput": "0.0040", "strong": "0.0053", "great": "0.0040", "deterior": "0.0013", "unemploy": "0.0106", "contract": "0.0146", "threat": "0.0040", "improv": "0.0106", "allianc": "0.0013", "suspend": "0.0119", "effici": "0.0013", "declin": "0.0557", "win": "0.0080", "bankruptci": "0.0053", "shortag": "0.0080", "cancel": "0.0013", "stabl": "0.0080", "miss": "0.0013", "drought": "0.0027", "damag": "0.0225", "bolster": "0.0040", "better": "0.0040", "question": "0.0027", "construct": "0.0252", "doubt": "0.0027", "downgrad": "0.0013", "threaten": "0.0040", "unexpect": "0.0027", "forc": "0.0252", "hurt": "0.0040", "warn": "0.0053", "gain": "0.0782", "termin": "0.0027", "eas": "0.0053", "highest": "0.0225", "fraud": "0.0013", "default": "0.0013", "seiz": "0.0013", "will": "0.0040", "limit": "0.0040", "posit": "0.0133", "problem": "0.0053", "claim": "0.0106", "weaker": "0.0013", "advantag": "0.0053", "strengthen": "0.0080", "challeng": "0.0040", "premier": "0.0013", "worri": "0.0013", "alleg": "0.0013", "critic": "0.0013", "attract": "0.0080", "sever": "0.0040", "halt": "0.0013", "strength": "0.0040", "delay": "0.0066", "fire": "0.0053", "boom": "0.0027", "reject": "0.0013", "weaken": "0.0066", "difficult": "0.0013", "tighten": "0.0027", "effect": "0.0013", "resign": "0.0053", "alert": "0.0027", "quit": "0.0013", "refin": "0.0013", "postpon": "0.0027", "stabil": "0.0106", "stress": "0.0013", "liquid": "0.0040", "antitrust": "0.0013", "stronger": "0.0027", "su": "0.0013", "inform": "0.0066", "deni": "0.0027", "achiev": "0.0027"}, "15": {"recess": "0.0036", "opposit": "0.0024", "lack": "0.0012", "protest": "0.0024", "surpass": "0.0048", "fear": "0.0012", "suffer": "0.0024", "fine": "0.0012", "accus": "0.0024", "cut": "0.0193", "depend": "0.0072", "except": "0.0012", "late": "0.0109", "arrest": "0.0024", "bailout": "0.0012", "volatil": "0.0012", "disrupt": "0.0012", "complaint": "0.0012", "good": "0.0121", "greater": "0.0036", "disclos": "0.0012", "rebound": "0.0036", "stop": "0.0024", "break": "0.0060", "worst": "0.0072", "know": "0.0036", "press": "0.0024", "loss": "0.0012", "bar": "0.0012", "success": "0.0072", "lost": "0.0133", "outperform": "0.0036", "drop": "0.0676", "negat": "0.0024", "resolv": "0.0012", "defens": "0.0072", "benefit": "0.0097", "integr": "0.0133", "lose": "0.0133", "popular": "0.0085", "collaps": "0.0024", "crisi": "0.0072", "prevent": "0.0036", "confid": "0.0060", "slower": "0.0024", "shut": "0.0012", "slowdown": "0.0012", "strongest": "0.0048", "cost": "0.0254", "opportun": "0.0060", "fail": "0.0072", "close": "0.0290", "precipit": "0.0012", "concern": "0.0181", "lead": "0.0085", "profit": "0.0193", "defend": "0.0024", "abl": "0.0036", "bad": "0.0012", "favor": "0.0072", "restructur": "0.0012", "outstand": "0.0012", "deficit": "0.0072", "progress": "0.0012", "boost": "0.0229", "correct": "0.0024", "encourag": "0.0024", "investig": "0.0048", "advanc": "0.0266", "weak": "0.0036", "ban": "0.0024", "slow": "0.0085", "excess": "0.0012", "disput": "0.0048", "strong": "0.0109", "great": "0.0012", "deterior": "0.0012", "unemploy": "0.0048", "contract": "0.0072", "threat": "0.0048", "improv": "0.0133", "allianc": "0.0072", "suspend": "0.0012", "effici": "0.0024", "declin": "0.0616", "win": "0.0036", "bankruptci": "0.0024", "shortag": "0.0024", "cancel": "0.0012", "stabl": "0.0024", "miss": "0.0036", "drought": "0.0012", "damag": "0.0205", "bolster": "0.0048", "better": "0.0085", "question": "0.0036", "construct": "0.0181", "doubt": "0.0036", "downgrad": "0.0036", "threaten": "0.0072", "unexpect": "0.0012", "forc": "0.0229", "hurt": "0.0060", "warn": "0.0012", "gain": "0.0616", "termin": "0.0012", "eas": "0.0157", "highest": "0.0242", "fraud": "0.0012", "default": "0.0012", "seiz": "0.0024", "will": "0.0060", "limit": "0.0085", "posit": "0.0157", "problem": "0.0085", "claim": "0.0012", "weaker": "0.0024", "advantag": "0.0048", "strengthen": "0.0072", "challeng": "0.0048", "premier": "0.0012", "worri": "0.0012", "alleg": "0.0024", "critic": "0.0024", "attract": "0.0097", "sever": "0.0012", "halt": "0.0012", "strength": "0.0012", "delay": "0.0036", "fire": "0.0048", "boom": "0.0024", "reject": "0.0012", "weaken": "0.0109", "difficult": "0.0024", "tighten": "0.0012", "effect": "0.0024", "resign": "0.0024", "alert": "0.0012", "quit": "0.0024", "refin": "0.0024", "postpon": "0.0036", "stabil": "0.0012", "stress": "0.0036", "liquid": "0.0060", "antitrust": "0.0012", "stronger": "0.0036", "su": "0.0012", "inform": "0.0072", "deni": "0.0012", "achiev": "0.0036"}, "16": {"recess": "0.0037", "opposit": "0.0012", "lack": "0.0049", "protest": "0.0012", "surpass": "0.0049", "fear": "0.0012", "suffer": "0.0012", "fine": "0.0049", "accus": "0.0025", "cut": "0.0209", "depend": "0.0086", "except": "0.0025", "late": "0.0086", "arrest": "0.0012", "bailout": "0.0025", "volatil": "0.0037", "disrupt": "0.0012", "complaint": "0.0012", "good": "0.0172", "greater": "0.0025", "disclos": "0.0049", "rebound": "0.0025", "stop": "0.0049", "break": "0.0025", "worst": "0.0110", "know": "0.0025", "press": "0.0049", "loss": "0.0074", "bar": "0.0012", "success": "0.0025", "lost": "0.0061", "outperform": "0.0025", "drop": "0.0748", "negat": "0.0012", "resolv": "0.0012", "defens": "0.0074", "benefit": "0.0074", "integr": "0.0086", "lose": "0.0049", "popular": "0.0012", "collaps": "0.0012", "crisi": "0.0037", "prevent": "0.0037", "confid": "0.0074", "slower": "0.0037", "shut": "0.0012", "slowdown": "0.0037", "strongest": "0.0049", "cost": "0.0294", "opportun": "0.0049", "fail": "0.0135", "close": "0.0319", "precipit": "0.0012", "concern": "0.0135", "lead": "0.0037", "profit": "0.0356", "defend": "0.0012", "abl": "0.0061", "bad": "0.0012", "favor": "0.0037", "restructur": "0.0012", "outstand": "0.0012", "deficit": "0.0123", "progress": "0.0025", "boost": "0.0209", "correct": "0.0025", "encourag": "0.0012", "investig": "0.0012", "advanc": "0.0172", "weak": "0.0037", "ban": "0.0012", "slow": "0.0025", "excess": "0.0012", "disput": "0.0061", "strong": "0.0061", "great": "0.0012", "deterior": "0.0012", "unemploy": "0.0061", "contract": "0.0135", "threat": "0.0025", "improv": "0.0061", "allianc": "0.0025", "suspend": "0.0049", "effici": "0.0025", "declin": "0.0417", "win": "0.0049", "bankruptci": "0.0012", "shortag": "0.0012", "cancel": "0.0012", "stabl": "0.0012", "miss": "0.0025", "drought": "0.0012", "damag": "0.0221", "bolster": "0.0049", "better": "0.0025", "question": "0.0025", "construct": "0.0160", "doubt": "0.0025", "downgrad": "0.0012", "threaten": "0.0049", "unexpect": "0.0012", "forc": "0.0098", "hurt": "0.0037", "warn": "0.0025", "gain": "0.0883", "termin": "0.0012", "eas": "0.0147", "highest": "0.0344", "fraud": "0.0012", "default": "0.0049", "seiz": "0.0025", "will": "0.0025", "limit": "0.0123", "posit": "0.0135", "problem": "0.0025", "claim": "0.0110", "weaker": "0.0012", "advantag": "0.0025", "strengthen": "0.0160", "challeng": "0.0025", "premier": "0.0012", "worri": "0.0012", "alleg": "0.0037", "critic": "0.0025", "attract": "0.0135", "sever": "0.0025", "halt": "0.0012", "strength": "0.0012", "delay": "0.0135", "fire": "0.0025", "boom": "0.0012", "reject": "0.0025", "weaken": "0.0160", "difficult": "0.0025", "tighten": "0.0012", "effect": "0.0049", "resign": "0.0012", "alert": "0.0012", "quit": "0.0012", "refin": "0.0012", "postpon": "0.0012", "stabil": "0.0025", "stress": "0.0012", "liquid": "0.0025", "antitrust": "0.0012", "stronger": "0.0049", "su": "0.0012", "inform": "0.0086", "deni": "0.0012", "achiev": "0.0074"}, "17": {"recess": "0.0035", "opposit": "0.0018", "lack": "0.0018", "protest": "0.0018", "surpass": "0.0071", "fear": "0.0018", "suffer": "0.0018", "fine": "0.0018", "accus": "0.0035", "cut": "0.0195", "depend": "0.0142", "except": "0.0018", "late": "0.0035", "arrest": "0.0018", "bailout": "0.0035", "volatil": "0.0053", "disrupt": "0.0018", "complaint": "0.0018", "good": "0.0159", "greater": "0.0053", "disclos": "0.0035", "rebound": "0.0071", "stop": "0.0053", "break": "0.0018", "worst": "0.0035", "know": "0.0088", "press": "0.0053", "loss": "0.0177", "bar": "0.0018", "success": "0.0018", "lost": "0.0071", "outperform": "0.0018", "drop": "0.0389", "negat": "0.0035", "resolv": "0.0018", "defens": "0.0018", "benefit": "0.0106", "integr": "0.0142", "lose": "0.0053", "popular": "0.0053", "collaps": "0.0018", "crisi": "0.0035", "prevent": "0.0035", "confid": "0.0053", "slower": "0.0018", "shut": "0.0018", "slowdown": "0.0018", "strongest": "0.0035", "cost": "0.0265", "opportun": "0.0071", "fail": "0.0071", "close": "0.0336", "precipit": "0.0018", "concern": "0.0088", "lead": "0.0053", "profit": "0.0195", "defend": "0.0018", "abl": "0.0053", "bad": "0.0018", "favor": "0.0053", "restructur": "0.0018", "outstand": "0.0018", "deficit": "0.0053", "progress": "0.0035", "boost": "0.0336", "correct": "0.0018", "encourag": "0.0035", "investig": "0.0035", "advanc": "0.0319", "weak": "0.0053", "ban": "0.0018", "slow": "0.0053", "excess": "0.0053", "disput": "0.0053", "strong": "0.0124", "great": "0.0018", "deterior": "0.0018", "unemploy": "0.0018", "contract": "0.0071", "threat": "0.0035", "improv": "0.0142", "allianc": "0.0035", "suspend": "0.0018", "effici": "0.0018", "declin": "0.0336", "win": "0.0035", "bankruptci": "0.0053", "shortag": "0.0018", "cancel": "0.0035", "stabl": "0.0035", "miss": "0.0035", "drought": "0.0018", "damag": "0.0071", "bolster": "0.0035", "better": "0.0018", "question": "0.0035", "construct": "0.0035", "doubt": "0.0018", "downgrad": "0.0018", "threaten": "0.0035", "unexpect": "0.0018", "forc": "0.0265", "hurt": "0.0088", "warn": "0.0018", "gain": "0.0832", "termin": "0.0035", "eas": "0.0195", "highest": "0.0159", "fraud": "0.0018", "default": "0.0088", "seiz": "0.0018", "will": "0.0018", "limit": "0.0071", "posit": "0.0212", "problem": "0.0035", "claim": "0.0018", "weaker": "0.0053", "advantag": "0.0071", "strengthen": "0.0142", "challeng": "0.0035", "premier": "0.0018", "worri": "0.0018", "alleg": "0.0018", "critic": "0.0035", "attract": "0.0248", "sever": "0.0053", "halt": "0.0018", "strength": "0.0035", "delay": "0.0035", "fire": "0.0018", "boom": "0.0035", "reject": "0.0035", "weaken": "0.0142", "difficult": "0.0053", "tighten": "0.0018", "effect": "0.0035", "resign": "0.0053", "alert": "0.0035", "quit": "0.0053", "refin": "0.0018", "postpon": "0.0018", "stabil": "0.0106", "stress": "0.0018", "liquid": "0.0018", "antitrust": "0.0018", "stronger": "0.0035", "su": "0.0018", "inform": "0.0018", "deni": "0.0018", "achiev": "0.0018"}, "18": {"recess": "0.0085", "opposit": "0.0043", "lack": "0.0043", "protest": "0.0043", "surpass": "0.0043", "fear": "0.0085", "suffer": "0.0043", "fine": "0.0043", "accus": "0.0043", "cut": "0.0043", "depend": "0.0043", "except": "0.0043", "late": "0.0043", "arrest": "0.0043", "bailout": "0.0043", "volatil": "0.0043", "disrupt": "0.0043", "complaint": "0.0043", "good": "0.0043", "greater": "0.0043", "disclos": "0.0043", "rebound": "0.0043", "stop": "0.0043", "break": "0.0085", "worst": "0.0170", "know": "0.0043", "press": "0.0085", "loss": "0.0085", "bar": "0.0043", "success": "0.0043", "lost": "0.0128", "outperform": "0.0043", "drop": "0.0213", "negat": "0.0043", "resolv": "0.0043", "defens": "0.0043", "benefit": "0.0043", "integr": "0.0043", "lose": "0.0128", "popular": "0.0128", "collaps": "0.0043", "crisi": "0.0170", "prevent": "0.0085", "confid": "0.0128", "slower": "0.0043", "shut": "0.0043", "slowdown": "0.0043", "strongest": "0.0043", "cost": "0.0170", "opportun": "0.0043", "fail": "0.0255", "close": "0.0170", "precipit": "0.0043", "concern": "0.0255", "lead": "0.0043", "profit": "0.0085", "defend": "0.0043", "abl": "0.0043", "bad": "0.0043", "favor": "0.0043", "restructur": "0.0043", "outstand": "0.0043", "deficit": "0.0043", "progress": "0.0043", "boost": "0.0170", "correct": "0.0043", "encourag": "0.0043", "investig": "0.0085", "advanc": "0.0085", "weak": "0.0043", "ban": "0.0043", "slow": "0.0043", "excess": "0.0043", "disput": "0.0043", "strong": "0.0043", "great": "0.0043", "deterior": "0.0043", "unemploy": "0.0043", "contract": "0.0170", "threat": "0.0085", "improv": "0.0128", "allianc": "0.0043", "suspend": "0.0170", "effici": "0.0043", "declin": "0.0511", "win": "0.0128", "bankruptci": "0.0043", "shortag": "0.0043", "cancel": "0.0043", "stabl": "0.0043", "miss": "0.0043", "drought": "0.0043", "damag": "0.0043", "bolster": "0.0043", "better": "0.0043", "question": "0.0043", "construct": "0.0085", "doubt": "0.0043", "downgrad": "0.0043", "threaten": "0.0085", "unexpect": "0.0043", "forc": "0.0043", "hurt": "0.0170", "warn": "0.0043", "gain": "0.0213", "termin": "0.0043", "eas": "0.0043", "highest": "0.0128", "fraud": "0.0043", "default": "0.0085", "seiz": "0.0043", "will": "0.0043", "limit": "0.0043", "posit": "0.0043", "problem": "0.0085", "claim": "0.0043", "weaker": "0.0043", "advantag": "0.0043", "strengthen": "0.0085", "challeng": "0.0043", "premier": "0.0043", "worri": "0.0043", "alleg": "0.0043", "critic": "0.0043", "attract": "0.0043", "sever": "0.0043", "halt": "0.0043", "strength": "0.0043", "delay": "0.0043", "fire": "0.0043", "boom": "0.0043", "reject": "0.0043", "weaken": "0.0085", "difficult": "0.0043", "tighten": "0.0043", "effect": "0.0043", "resign": "0.0043", "alert": "0.0043", "quit": "0.0043", "refin": "0.0043", "postpon": "0.0043", "stabil": "0.0043", "stress": "0.0128", "liquid": "0.0043", "antitrust": "0.0043", "stronger": "0.0043", "su": "0.0043", "inform": "0.0043", "deni": "0.0043", "achiev": "0.0043"}, "19": {"recess": "0.0038", "opposit": "0.0038", "lack": "0.0038", "protest": "0.0038", "surpass": "0.0076", "fear": "0.0038", "suffer": "0.0038", "fine": "0.0038", "accus": "0.0038", "cut": "0.0114", "depend": "0.0038", "except": "0.0038", "late": "0.0076", "arrest": "0.0038", "bailout": "0.0038", "volatil": "0.0038", "disrupt": "0.0038", "complaint": "0.0038", "good": "0.0076", "greater": "0.0038", "disclos": "0.0076", "rebound": "0.0038", "stop": "0.0038", "break": "0.0038", "worst": "0.0114", "know": "0.0038", "press": "0.0076", "loss": "0.0038", "bar": "0.0038", "success": "0.0038", "lost": "0.0114", "outperform": "0.0038", "drop": "0.0530", "negat": "0.0038", "resolv": "0.0038", "defens": "0.0076", "benefit": "0.0038", "integr": "0.0038", "lose": "0.0114", "popular": "0.0038", "collaps": "0.0038", "crisi": "0.0076", "prevent": "0.0038", "confid": "0.0038", "slower": "0.0038", "shut": "0.0038", "slowdown": "0.0038", "strongest": "0.0038", "cost": "0.0227", "opportun": "0.0038", "fail": "0.0038", "close": "0.0227", "precipit": "0.0038", "concern": "0.0303", "lead": "0.0114", "profit": "0.0492", "defend": "0.0038", "abl": "0.0076", "bad": "0.0038", "favor": "0.0038", "restructur": "0.0076", "outstand": "0.0038", "deficit": "0.0038", "progress": "0.0038", "boost": "0.0076", "correct": "0.0038", "encourag": "0.0038", "investig": "0.0038", "advanc": "0.0265", "weak": "0.0076", "ban": "0.0038", "slow": "0.0038", "excess": "0.0038", "disput": "0.0038", "strong": "0.0038", "great": "0.0038", "deterior": "0.0038", "unemploy": "0.0038", "contract": "0.0076", "threat": "0.0038", "improv": "0.0038", "allianc": "0.0038", "suspend": "0.0038", "effici": "0.0038", "declin": "0.0682", "win": "0.0038", "bankruptci": "0.0076", "shortag": "0.0038", "cancel": "0.0038", "stabl": "0.0038", "miss": "0.0076", "drought": "0.0038", "damag": "0.0076", "bolster": "0.0038", "better": "0.0076", "question": "0.0038", "construct": "0.0076", "doubt": "0.0038", "downgrad": "0.0038", "threaten": "0.0038", "unexpect": "0.0076", "forc": "0.0152", "hurt": "0.0038", "warn": "0.0038", "gain": "0.0265", "termin": "0.0038", "eas": "0.0038", "highest": "0.0189", "fraud": "0.0038", "default": "0.0038", "seiz": "0.0038", "will": "0.0076", "limit": "0.0038", "posit": "0.0038", "problem": "0.0038", "claim": "0.0038", "weaker": "0.0038", "advantag": "0.0076", "strengthen": "0.0038", "challeng": "0.0038", "premier": "0.0038", "worri": "0.0038", "alleg": "0.0038", "critic": "0.0038", "attract": "0.0076", "sever": "0.0076", "halt": "0.0038", "strength": "0.0038", "delay": "0.0038", "fire": "0.0038", "boom": "0.0038", "reject": "0.0038", "weaken": "0.0076", "difficult": "0.0038", "tighten": "0.0038", "effect": "0.0038", "resign": "0.0076", "alert": "0.0038", "quit": "0.0038", "refin": "0.0038", "postpon": "0.0038", "stabil": "0.0038", "stress": "0.0038", "liquid": "0.0076", "antitrust": "0.0038", "stronger": "0.0038", "su": "0.0038", "inform": "0.0076", "deni": "0.0038", "achiev": "0.0038"}, "20": {"recess": "0.0039", "opposit": "0.0019", "lack": "0.0039", "protest": "0.0019", "surpass": "0.0058", "fear": "0.0019", "suffer": "0.0039", "fine": "0.0019", "accus": "0.0039", "cut": "0.0234", "depend": "0.0058", "except": "0.0019", "late": "0.0039", "arrest": "0.0019", "bailout": "0.0019", "volatil": "0.0019", "disrupt": "0.0039", "complaint": "0.0019", "good": "0.0097", "greater": "0.0078", "disclos": "0.0058", "rebound": "0.0039", "stop": "0.0058", "break": "0.0058", "worst": "0.0019", "know": "0.0019", "press": "0.0039", "loss": "0.0058", "bar": "0.0019", "success": "0.0019", "lost": "0.0136", "outperform": "0.0039", "drop": "0.0741", "negat": "0.0019", "resolv": "0.0019", "defens": "0.0058", "benefit": "0.0097", "integr": "0.0175", "lose": "0.0097", "popular": "0.0019", "collaps": "0.0019", "crisi": "0.0058", "prevent": "0.0039", "confid": "0.0117", "slower": "0.0039", "shut": "0.0019", "slowdown": "0.0019", "strongest": "0.0058", "cost": "0.0097", "opportun": "0.0019", "fail": "0.0058", "close": "0.0234", "precipit": "0.0019", "concern": "0.0195", "lead": "0.0019", "profit": "0.0156", "defend": "0.0019", "abl": "0.0019", "bad": "0.0019", "favor": "0.0019", "restructur": "0.0019", "outstand": "0.0058", "deficit": "0.0019", "progress": "0.0039", "boost": "0.0253", "correct": "0.0039", "encourag": "0.0019", "investig": "0.0058", "advanc": "0.0390", "weak": "0.0058", "ban": "0.0019", "slow": "0.0097", "excess": "0.0039", "disput": "0.0039", "strong": "0.0039", "great": "0.0019", "deterior": "0.0019", "unemploy": "0.0019", "contract": "0.0019", "threat": "0.0058", "improv": "0.0136", "allianc": "0.0039", "suspend": "0.0019", "effici": "0.0019", "declin": "0.0604", "win": "0.0097", "bankruptci": "0.0019", "shortag": "0.0019", "cancel": "0.0019", "stabl": "0.0039", "miss": "0.0039", "drought": "0.0019", "damag": "0.0019", "bolster": "0.0097", "better": "0.0039", "question": "0.0039", "construct": "0.0175", "doubt": "0.0019", "downgrad": "0.0058", "threaten": "0.0058", "unexpect": "0.0039", "forc": "0.0019", "hurt": "0.0039", "warn": "0.0039", "gain": "0.0858", "termin": "0.0019", "eas": "0.0058", "highest": "0.0273", "fraud": "0.0019", "default": "0.0078", "seiz": "0.0039", "will": "0.0019", "limit": "0.0058", "posit": "0.0156", "problem": "0.0058", "claim": "0.0019", "weaker": "0.0039", "advantag": "0.0078", "strengthen": "0.0117", "challeng": "0.0019", "premier": "0.0019", "worri": "0.0019", "alleg": "0.0019", "critic": "0.0019", "attract": "0.0156", "sever": "0.0019", "halt": "0.0019", "strength": "0.0019", "delay": "0.0078", "fire": "0.0019", "boom": "0.0019", "reject": "0.0019", "weaken": "0.0058", "difficult": "0.0039", "tighten": "0.0039", "effect": "0.0019", "resign": "0.0058", "alert": "0.0019", "quit": "0.0019", "refin": "0.0039", "postpon": "0.0039", "stabil": "0.0019", "stress": "0.0019", "liquid": "0.0039", "antitrust": "0.0019", "stronger": "0.0039", "su": "0.0039", "inform": "0.0039", "deni": "0.0058", "achiev": "0.0039"}}, "CRSMBCT": {"1": {"recess": "0.0043", "opposit": "0.0043", "lack": "0.0043", "protest": "0.0128", "surpass": "0.0043", "fear": "0.0043", "suffer": "0.0043", "fine": "0.0043", "accus": "0.0128", "cut": "0.0043", "depend": "0.0043", "except": "0.0043", "late": "0.0085", "arrest": "0.0043", "bailout": "0.0043", "volatil": "0.0043", "disrupt": "0.0043", "complaint": "0.0043", "good": "0.0043", "greater": "0.0043", "disclos": "0.0043", "rebound": "0.0043", "stop": "0.0171", "break": "0.0043", "worst": "0.0043", "know": "0.0214", "press": "0.0085", "loss": "0.0043", "bar": "0.0043", "success": "0.0043", "lost": "0.0171", "outperform": "0.0043", "drop": "0.0043", "negat": "0.0043", "resolv": "0.0085", "defens": "0.0043", "benefit": "0.0128", "integr": "0.0043", "lose": "0.0043", "popular": "0.0043", "collaps": "0.0043", "crisi": "0.0043", "prevent": "0.0043", "confid": "0.0043", "slower": "0.0043", "shut": "0.0128", "slowdown": "0.0043", "strongest": "0.0043", "cost": "0.0085", "opportun": "0.0043", "fail": "0.0128", "close": "0.0043", "precipit": "0.0043", "concern": "0.0043", "lead": "0.0128", "profit": "0.0128", "defend": "0.0043", "abl": "0.0043", "bad": "0.0043", "favor": "0.0043", "restructur": "0.0085", "outstand": "0.0128", "deficit": "0.0043", "progress": "0.0043", "boost": "0.0128", "correct": "0.0043", "encourag": "0.0085", "investig": "0.0085", "advanc": "0.0043", "weak": "0.0043", "ban": "0.0043", "slow": "0.0043", "excess": "0.0043", "disput": "0.0214", "strong": "0.0043", "great": "0.0043", "deterior": "0.0043", "unemploy": "0.0043", "contract": "0.0299", "threat": "0.0043", "improv": "0.0128", "allianc": "0.0085", "suspend": "0.0171", "effici": "0.0043", "declin": "0.0043", "win": "0.0299", "bankruptci": "0.0043", "shortag": "0.0128", "cancel": "0.0043", "stabl": "0.0043", "miss": "0.0043", "drought": "0.0043", "damag": "0.0043", "bolster": "0.0043", "better": "0.0043", "question": "0.0128", "construct": "0.0043", "doubt": "0.0128", "downgrad": "0.0043", "threaten": "0.0128", "unexpect": "0.0043", "forc": "0.0214", "hurt": "0.0043", "warn": "0.0043", "gain": "0.0043", "termin": "0.0043", "eas": "0.0043", "highest": "0.0043", "fraud": "0.0043", "default": "0.0128", "seiz": "0.0043", "will": "0.0043", "limit": "0.0171", "posit": "0.0043", "problem": "0.0128", "claim": "0.0043", "weaker": "0.0043", "advantag": "0.0043", "strengthen": "0.0043", "challeng": "0.0043", "premier": "0.0043", "worri": "0.0043", "alleg": "0.0043", "critic": "0.0043", "attract": "0.0085", "sever": "0.0043", "halt": "0.0128", "strength": "0.0043", "delay": "0.0085", "fire": "0.0043", "boom": "0.0043", "reject": "0.0043", "weaken": "0.0043", "difficult": "0.0043", "tighten": "0.0043", "effect": "0.0043", "resign": "0.0085", "alert": "0.0043", "quit": "0.0043", "refin": "0.0043", "postpon": "0.0085", "stabil": "0.0043", "stress": "0.0043", "liquid": "0.0043", "antitrust": "0.0043", "stronger": "0.0043", "su": "0.0043", "inform": "0.0128", "deni": "0.0043", "achiev": "0.0043"}, "2": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "3": {"recess": "0.0065", "opposit": "0.0065", "lack": "0.0065", "protest": "0.0065", "surpass": "0.0065", "fear": "0.0065", "suffer": "0.0065", "fine": "0.0065", "accus": "0.0065", "cut": "0.0065", "depend": "0.0065", "except": "0.0065", "late": "0.0065", "arrest": "0.0065", "bailout": "0.0065", "volatil": "0.0065", "disrupt": "0.0065", "complaint": "0.0065", "good": "0.0065", "greater": "0.0065", "disclos": "0.0065", "rebound": "0.0065", "stop": "0.0065", "break": "0.0065", "worst": "0.0065", "know": "0.0065", "press": "0.0065", "loss": "0.0065", "bar": "0.0065", "success": "0.0065", "lost": "0.0065", "outperform": "0.0065", "drop": "0.0065", "negat": "0.0065", "resolv": "0.0065", "defens": "0.0065", "benefit": "0.0065", "integr": "0.0065", "lose": "0.0065", "popular": "0.0065", "collaps": "0.0065", "crisi": "0.0065", "prevent": "0.0065", "confid": "0.0065", "slower": "0.0065", "shut": "0.0065", "slowdown": "0.0065", "strongest": "0.0065", "cost": "0.0065", "opportun": "0.0065", "fail": "0.0065", "close": "0.0065", "precipit": "0.0065", "concern": "0.0065", "lead": "0.0065", "profit": "0.0065", "defend": "0.0065", "abl": "0.0065", "bad": "0.0065", "favor": "0.0065", "restructur": "0.0065", "outstand": "0.0065", "deficit": "0.0065", "progress": "0.0065", "boost": "0.0065", "correct": "0.0065", "encourag": "0.0065", "investig": "0.0194", "advanc": "0.0065", "weak": "0.0065", "ban": "0.0065", "slow": "0.0065", "excess": "0.0065", "disput": "0.0065", "strong": "0.0065", "great": "0.0065", "deterior": "0.0065", "unemploy": "0.0065", "contract": "0.0065", "threat": "0.0065", "improv": "0.0065", "allianc": "0.0065", "suspend": "0.0065", "effici": "0.0065", "declin": "0.0129", "win": "0.0065", "bankruptci": "0.0065", "shortag": "0.0065", "cancel": "0.0065", "stabl": "0.0065", "miss": "0.0065", "drought": "0.0065", "damag": "0.0129", "bolster": "0.0065", "better": "0.0065", "question": "0.0065", "construct": "0.0065", "doubt": "0.0065", "downgrad": "0.0065", "threaten": "0.0065", "unexpect": "0.0065", "forc": "0.0065", "hurt": "0.0065", "warn": "0.0065", "gain": "0.0065", "termin": "0.0065", "eas": "0.0065", "highest": "0.0065", "fraud": "0.0065", "default": "0.0065", "seiz": "0.0065", "will": "0.0065", "limit": "0.0065", "posit": "0.0065", "problem": "0.0065", "claim": "0.0065", "weaker": "0.0065", "advantag": "0.0065", "strengthen": "0.0065", "challeng": "0.0065", "premier": "0.0065", "worri": "0.0065", "alleg": "0.0065", "critic": "0.0065", "attract": "0.0065", "sever": "0.0065", "halt": "0.0065", "strength": "0.0065", "delay": "0.0065", "fire": "0.0065", "boom": "0.0065", "reject": "0.0065", "weaken": "0.0065", "difficult": "0.0065", "tighten": "0.0065", "effect": "0.0065", "resign": "0.0065", "alert": "0.0065", "quit": "0.0065", "refin": "0.0065", "postpon": "0.0065", "stabil": "0.0065", "stress": "0.0065", "liquid": "0.0065", "antitrust": "0.0065", "stronger": "0.0065", "su": "0.0065", "inform": "0.0129", "deni": "0.0065", "achiev": "0.0065"}, "4": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "5": {"recess": "0.0065", "opposit": "0.0065", "lack": "0.0065", "protest": "0.0065", "surpass": "0.0065", "fear": "0.0065", "suffer": "0.0065", "fine": "0.0065", "accus": "0.0065", "cut": "0.0065", "depend": "0.0065", "except": "0.0065", "late": "0.0065", "arrest": "0.0065", "bailout": "0.0065", "volatil": "0.0065", "disrupt": "0.0065", "complaint": "0.0065", "good": "0.0065", "greater": "0.0065", "disclos": "0.0065", "rebound": "0.0065", "stop": "0.0065", "break": "0.0065", "worst": "0.0065", "know": "0.0065", "press": "0.0065", "loss": "0.0065", "bar": "0.0065", "success": "0.0065", "lost": "0.0065", "outperform": "0.0065", "drop": "0.0065", "negat": "0.0065", "resolv": "0.0065", "defens": "0.0065", "benefit": "0.0065", "integr": "0.0065", "lose": "0.0065", "popular": "0.0065", "collaps": "0.0065", "crisi": "0.0065", "prevent": "0.0065", "confid": "0.0065", "slower": "0.0065", "shut": "0.0065", "slowdown": "0.0065", "strongest": "0.0065", "cost": "0.0065", "opportun": "0.0065", "fail": "0.0065", "close": "0.0065", "precipit": "0.0065", "concern": "0.0065", "lead": "0.0065", "profit": "0.0065", "defend": "0.0065", "abl": "0.0065", "bad": "0.0065", "favor": "0.0065", "restructur": "0.0065", "outstand": "0.0065", "deficit": "0.0065", "progress": "0.0065", "boost": "0.0065", "correct": "0.0065", "encourag": "0.0065", "investig": "0.0065", "advanc": "0.0065", "weak": "0.0065", "ban": "0.0065", "slow": "0.0065", "excess": "0.0065", "disput": "0.0065", "strong": "0.0065", "great": "0.0065", "deterior": "0.0065", "unemploy": "0.0065", "contract": "0.0065", "threat": "0.0065", "improv": "0.0065", "allianc": "0.0065", "suspend": "0.0196", "effici": "0.0065", "declin": "0.0065", "win": "0.0065", "bankruptci": "0.0065", "shortag": "0.0065", "cancel": "0.0131", "stabl": "0.0065", "miss": "0.0065", "drought": "0.0065", "damag": "0.0065", "bolster": "0.0065", "better": "0.0065", "question": "0.0065", "construct": "0.0065", "doubt": "0.0065", "downgrad": "0.0065", "threaten": "0.0065", "unexpect": "0.0065", "forc": "0.0065", "hurt": "0.0065", "warn": "0.0065", "gain": "0.0065", "termin": "0.0065", "eas": "0.0065", "highest": "0.0065", "fraud": "0.0065", "default": "0.0065", "seiz": "0.0065", "will": "0.0065", "limit": "0.0065", "posit": "0.0065", "problem": "0.0065", "claim": "0.0065", "weaker": "0.0065", "advantag": "0.0065", "strengthen": "0.0065", "challeng": "0.0065", "premier": "0.0065", "worri": "0.0065", "alleg": "0.0065", "critic": "0.0065", "attract": "0.0065", "sever": "0.0065", "halt": "0.0065", "strength": "0.0065", "delay": "0.0065", "fire": "0.0065", "boom": "0.0065", "reject": "0.0065", "weaken": "0.0065", "difficult": "0.0065", "tighten": "0.0065", "effect": "0.0065", "resign": "0.0065", "alert": "0.0065", "quit": "0.0065", "refin": "0.0065", "postpon": "0.0065", "stabil": "0.0065", "stress": "0.0065", "liquid": "0.0065", "antitrust": "0.0065", "stronger": "0.0065", "su": "0.0065", "inform": "0.0065", "deni": "0.0065", "achiev": "0.0065"}, "6": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "7": {"recess": "0.0062", "opposit": "0.0062", "lack": "0.0062", "protest": "0.0062", "surpass": "0.0062", "fear": "0.0062", "suffer": "0.0062", "fine": "0.0124", "accus": "0.0124", "cut": "0.0062", "depend": "0.0062", "except": "0.0062", "late": "0.0062", "arrest": "0.0062", "bailout": "0.0062", "volatil": "0.0062", "disrupt": "0.0062", "complaint": "0.0062", "good": "0.0062", "greater": "0.0062", "disclos": "0.0124", "rebound": "0.0062", "stop": "0.0062", "break": "0.0062", "worst": "0.0062", "know": "0.0062", "press": "0.0062", "loss": "0.0062", "bar": "0.0062", "success": "0.0062", "lost": "0.0062", "outperform": "0.0062", "drop": "0.0062", "negat": "0.0062", "resolv": "0.0062", "defens": "0.0062", "benefit": "0.0062", "integr": "0.0062", "lose": "0.0062", "popular": "0.0062", "collaps": "0.0062", "crisi": "0.0062", "prevent": "0.0062", "confid": "0.0062", "slower": "0.0062", "shut": "0.0062", "slowdown": "0.0062", "strongest": "0.0062", "cost": "0.0062", "opportun": "0.0062", "fail": "0.0062", "close": "0.0062", "precipit": "0.0062", "concern": "0.0062", "lead": "0.0062", "profit": "0.0062", "defend": "0.0062", "abl": "0.0062", "bad": "0.0062", "favor": "0.0062", "restructur": "0.0062", "outstand": "0.0062", "deficit": "0.0062", "progress": "0.0062", "boost": "0.0062", "correct": "0.0062", "encourag": "0.0062", "investig": "0.0062", "advanc": "0.0062", "weak": "0.0062", "ban": "0.0062", "slow": "0.0062", "excess": "0.0062", "disput": "0.0062", "strong": "0.0062", "great": "0.0062", "deterior": "0.0062", "unemploy": "0.0062", "contract": "0.0062", "threat": "0.0062", "improv": "0.0062", "allianc": "0.0062", "suspend": "0.0062", "effici": "0.0062", "declin": "0.0062", "win": "0.0062", "bankruptci": "0.0062", "shortag": "0.0062", "cancel": "0.0062", "stabl": "0.0062", "miss": "0.0062", "drought": "0.0062", "damag": "0.0062", "bolster": "0.0062", "better": "0.0062", "question": "0.0124", "construct": "0.0062", "doubt": "0.0062", "downgrad": "0.0062", "threaten": "0.0062", "unexpect": "0.0062", "forc": "0.0062", "hurt": "0.0062", "warn": "0.0062", "gain": "0.0062", "termin": "0.0062", "eas": "0.0062", "highest": "0.0062", "fraud": "0.0062", "default": "0.0124", "seiz": "0.0062", "will": "0.0062", "limit": "0.0062", "posit": "0.0062", "problem": "0.0062", "claim": "0.0062", "weaker": "0.0062", "advantag": "0.0062", "strengthen": "0.0062", "challeng": "0.0062", "premier": "0.0062", "worri": "0.0062", "alleg": "0.0062", "critic": "0.0124", "attract": "0.0062", "sever": "0.0062", "halt": "0.0062", "strength": "0.0062", "delay": "0.0062", "fire": "0.0062", "boom": "0.0062", "reject": "0.0186", "weaken": "0.0062", "difficult": "0.0062", "tighten": "0.0062", "effect": "0.0062", "resign": "0.0062", "alert": "0.0062", "quit": "0.0124", "refin": "0.0062", "postpon": "0.0062", "stabil": "0.0062", "stress": "0.0062", "liquid": "0.0062", "antitrust": "0.0062", "stronger": "0.0062", "su": "0.0062", "inform": "0.0186", "deni": "0.0062", "achiev": "0.0062"}, "8": {"recess": "0.0065", "opposit": "0.0065", "lack": "0.0065", "protest": "0.0065", "surpass": "0.0065", "fear": "0.0065", "suffer": "0.0065", "fine": "0.0065", "accus": "0.0065", "cut": "0.0065", "depend": "0.0065", "except": "0.0065", "late": "0.0065", "arrest": "0.0065", "bailout": "0.0065", "volatil": "0.0065", "disrupt": "0.0065", "complaint": "0.0065", "good": "0.0065", "greater": "0.0065", "disclos": "0.0065", "rebound": "0.0065", "stop": "0.0065", "break": "0.0065", "worst": "0.0065", "know": "0.0065", "press": "0.0065", "loss": "0.0065", "bar": "0.0065", "success": "0.0065", "lost": "0.0065", "outperform": "0.0065", "drop": "0.0065", "negat": "0.0065", "resolv": "0.0065", "defens": "0.0065", "benefit": "0.0065", "integr": "0.0065", "lose": "0.0065", "popular": "0.0065", "collaps": "0.0065", "crisi": "0.0065", "prevent": "0.0065", "confid": "0.0065", "slower": "0.0065", "shut": "0.0065", "slowdown": "0.0065", "strongest": "0.0065", "cost": "0.0065", "opportun": "0.0065", "fail": "0.0065", "close": "0.0065", "precipit": "0.0065", "concern": "0.0065", "lead": "0.0065", "profit": "0.0065", "defend": "0.0065", "abl": "0.0065", "bad": "0.0065", "favor": "0.0065", "restructur": "0.0065", "outstand": "0.0065", "deficit": "0.0065", "progress": "0.0065", "boost": "0.0131", "correct": "0.0065", "encourag": "0.0065", "investig": "0.0065", "advanc": "0.0065", "weak": "0.0065", "ban": "0.0065", "slow": "0.0196", "excess": "0.0065", "disput": "0.0065", "strong": "0.0065", "great": "0.0065", "deterior": "0.0065", "unemploy": "0.0065", "contract": "0.0065", "threat": "0.0065", "improv": "0.0065", "allianc": "0.0065", "suspend": "0.0065", "effici": "0.0065", "declin": "0.0065", "win": "0.0065", "bankruptci": "0.0065", "shortag": "0.0065", "cancel": "0.0065", "stabl": "0.0065", "miss": "0.0065", "drought": "0.0065", "damag": "0.0065", "bolster": "0.0065", "better": "0.0065", "question": "0.0065", "construct": "0.0065", "doubt": "0.0065", "downgrad": "0.0065", "threaten": "0.0065", "unexpect": "0.0065", "forc": "0.0065", "hurt": "0.0065", "warn": "0.0065", "gain": "0.0065", "termin": "0.0065", "eas": "0.0065", "highest": "0.0065", "fraud": "0.0065", "default": "0.0065", "seiz": "0.0065", "will": "0.0065", "limit": "0.0065", "posit": "0.0065", "problem": "0.0065", "claim": "0.0065", "weaker": "0.0065", "advantag": "0.0065", "strengthen": "0.0065", "challeng": "0.0065", "premier": "0.0065", "worri": "0.0065", "alleg": "0.0065", "critic": "0.0065", "attract": "0.0065", "sever": "0.0065", "halt": "0.0065", "strength": "0.0065", "delay": "0.0065", "fire": "0.0065", "boom": "0.0065", "reject": "0.0065", "weaken": "0.0065", "difficult": "0.0065", "tighten": "0.0065", "effect": "0.0065", "resign": "0.0065", "alert": "0.0065", "quit": "0.0065", "refin": "0.0065", "postpon": "0.0065", "stabil": "0.0065", "stress": "0.0065", "liquid": "0.0065", "antitrust": "0.0065", "stronger": "0.0065", "su": "0.0065", "inform": "0.0065", "deni": "0.0065", "achiev": "0.0065"}, "9": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "10": {"recess": "0.0059", "opposit": "0.0059", "lack": "0.0059", "protest": "0.0059", "surpass": "0.0059", "fear": "0.0059", "suffer": "0.0059", "fine": "0.0059", "accus": "0.0059", "cut": "0.0059", "depend": "0.0059", "except": "0.0059", "late": "0.0118", "arrest": "0.0059", "bailout": "0.0059", "volatil": "0.0059", "disrupt": "0.0059", "complaint": "0.0059", "good": "0.0059", "greater": "0.0059", "disclos": "0.0059", "rebound": "0.0059", "stop": "0.0059", "break": "0.0059", "worst": "0.0059", "know": "0.0178", "press": "0.0059", "loss": "0.0059", "bar": "0.0059", "success": "0.0059", "lost": "0.0237", "outperform": "0.0059", "drop": "0.0059", "negat": "0.0059", "resolv": "0.0059", "defens": "0.0059", "benefit": "0.0059", "integr": "0.0059", "lose": "0.0059", "popular": "0.0059", "collaps": "0.0059", "crisi": "0.0059", "prevent": "0.0059", "confid": "0.0059", "slower": "0.0059", "shut": "0.0059", "slowdown": "0.0059", "strongest": "0.0059", "cost": "0.0118", "opportun": "0.0059", "fail": "0.0059", "close": "0.0059", "precipit": "0.0059", "concern": "0.0059", "lead": "0.0059", "profit": "0.0059", "defend": "0.0059", "abl": "0.0059", "bad": "0.0059", "favor": "0.0059", "restructur": "0.0059", "outstand": "0.0059", "deficit": "0.0059", "progress": "0.0059", "boost": "0.0118", "correct": "0.0059", "encourag": "0.0059", "investig": "0.0059", "advanc": "0.0059", "weak": "0.0059", "ban": "0.0059", "slow": "0.0178", "excess": "0.0059", "disput": "0.0059", "strong": "0.0059", "great": "0.0059", "deterior": "0.0059", "unemploy": "0.0059", "contract": "0.0118", "threat": "0.0059", "improv": "0.0059", "allianc": "0.0059", "suspend": "0.0059", "effici": "0.0059", "declin": "0.0059", "win": "0.0355", "bankruptci": "0.0059", "shortag": "0.0059", "cancel": "0.0059", "stabl": "0.0059", "miss": "0.0059", "drought": "0.0059", "damag": "0.0059", "bolster": "0.0059", "better": "0.0059", "question": "0.0059", "construct": "0.0059", "doubt": "0.0059", "downgrad": "0.0059", "threaten": "0.0059", "unexpect": "0.0059", "forc": "0.0059", "hurt": "0.0059", "warn": "0.0059", "gain": "0.0059", "termin": "0.0059", "eas": "0.0059", "highest": "0.0059", "fraud": "0.0059", "default": "0.0059", "seiz": "0.0059", "will": "0.0059", "limit": "0.0059", "posit": "0.0059", "problem": "0.0059", "claim": "0.0059", "weaker": "0.0059", "advantag": "0.0059", "strengthen": "0.0059", "challeng": "0.0059", "premier": "0.0059", "worri": "0.0059", "alleg": "0.0059", "critic": "0.0059", "attract": "0.0059", "sever": "0.0059", "halt": "0.0059", "strength": "0.0059", "delay": "0.0118", "fire": "0.0059", "boom": "0.0059", "reject": "0.0059", "weaken": "0.0059", "difficult": "0.0059", "tighten": "0.0059", "effect": "0.0059", "resign": "0.0118", "alert": "0.0059", "quit": "0.0059", "refin": "0.0059", "postpon": "0.0118", "stabil": "0.0059", "stress": "0.0059", "liquid": "0.0059", "antitrust": "0.0059", "stronger": "0.0059", "su": "0.0059", "inform": "0.0059", "deni": "0.0059", "achiev": "0.0059"}, "11": {"recess": "0.0058", "opposit": "0.0174", "lack": "0.0058", "protest": "0.0058", "surpass": "0.0116", "fear": "0.0058", "suffer": "0.0116", "fine": "0.0058", "accus": "0.0058", "cut": "0.0116", "depend": "0.0174", "except": "0.0058", "late": "0.0058", "arrest": "0.0058", "bailout": "0.0058", "volatil": "0.0058", "disrupt": "0.0058", "complaint": "0.0058", "good": "0.0058", "greater": "0.0058", "disclos": "0.0058", "rebound": "0.0058", "stop": "0.0058", "break": "0.0058", "worst": "0.0116", "know": "0.0058", "press": "0.0058", "loss": "0.0058", "bar": "0.0058", "success": "0.0058", "lost": "0.0058", "outperform": "0.0058", "drop": "0.0116", "negat": "0.0058", "resolv": "0.0058", "defens": "0.0058", "benefit": "0.0058", "integr": "0.0058", "lose": "0.0058", "popular": "0.0058", "collaps": "0.0058", "crisi": "0.0058", "prevent": "0.0058", "confid": "0.0058", "slower": "0.0058", "shut": "0.0058", "slowdown": "0.0058", "strongest": "0.0058", "cost": "0.0058", "opportun": "0.0058", "fail": "0.0116", "close": "0.0116", "precipit": "0.0058", "concern": "0.0058", "lead": "0.0058", "profit": "0.0058", "defend": "0.0058", "abl": "0.0058", "bad": "0.0058", "favor": "0.0116", "restructur": "0.0058", "outstand": "0.0058", "deficit": "0.0058", "progress": "0.0058", "boost": "0.0058", "correct": "0.0058", "encourag": "0.0058", "investig": "0.0058", "advanc": "0.0058", "weak": "0.0058", "ban": "0.0058", "slow": "0.0116", "excess": "0.0058", "disput": "0.0058", "strong": "0.0058", "great": "0.0058", "deterior": "0.0058", "unemploy": "0.0058", "contract": "0.0174", "threat": "0.0058", "improv": "0.0058", "allianc": "0.0058", "suspend": "0.0058", "effici": "0.0058", "declin": "0.0058", "win": "0.0058", "bankruptci": "0.0058", "shortag": "0.0058", "cancel": "0.0058", "stabl": "0.0058", "miss": "0.0058", "drought": "0.0116", "damag": "0.0058", "bolster": "0.0058", "better": "0.0058", "question": "0.0058", "construct": "0.0058", "doubt": "0.0058", "downgrad": "0.0058", "threaten": "0.0058", "unexpect": "0.0058", "forc": "0.0116", "hurt": "0.0058", "warn": "0.0058", "gain": "0.0058", "termin": "0.0058", "eas": "0.0058", "highest": "0.0116", "fraud": "0.0058", "default": "0.0116", "seiz": "0.0058", "will": "0.0058", "limit": "0.0058", "posit": "0.0058", "problem": "0.0058", "claim": "0.0058", "weaker": "0.0058", "advantag": "0.0058", "strengthen": "0.0058", "challeng": "0.0058", "premier": "0.0058", "worri": "0.0058", "alleg": "0.0058", "critic": "0.0116", "attract": "0.0116", "sever": "0.0058", "halt": "0.0058", "strength": "0.0058", "delay": "0.0058", "fire": "0.0058", "boom": "0.0058", "reject": "0.0058", "weaken": "0.0058", "difficult": "0.0058", "tighten": "0.0058", "effect": "0.0058", "resign": "0.0058", "alert": "0.0058", "quit": "0.0058", "refin": "0.0058", "postpon": "0.0058", "stabil": "0.0058", "stress": "0.0058", "liquid": "0.0058", "antitrust": "0.0058", "stronger": "0.0058", "su": "0.0058", "inform": "0.0058", "deni": "0.0116", "achiev": "0.0058"}, "12": {"recess": "0.0065", "opposit": "0.0065", "lack": "0.0065", "protest": "0.0065", "surpass": "0.0065", "fear": "0.0065", "suffer": "0.0065", "fine": "0.0065", "accus": "0.0065", "cut": "0.0065", "depend": "0.0065", "except": "0.0065", "late": "0.0065", "arrest": "0.0065", "bailout": "0.0065", "volatil": "0.0065", "disrupt": "0.0065", "complaint": "0.0065", "good": "0.0065", "greater": "0.0065", "disclos": "0.0065", "rebound": "0.0065", "stop": "0.0065", "break": "0.0065", "worst": "0.0065", "know": "0.0065", "press": "0.0065", "loss": "0.0065", "bar": "0.0065", "success": "0.0065", "lost": "0.0065", "outperform": "0.0065", "drop": "0.0065", "negat": "0.0065", "resolv": "0.0065", "defens": "0.0065", "benefit": "0.0065", "integr": "0.0065", "lose": "0.0065", "popular": "0.0065", "collaps": "0.0065", "crisi": "0.0065", "prevent": "0.0065", "confid": "0.0065", "slower": "0.0065", "shut": "0.0065", "slowdown": "0.0065", "strongest": "0.0065", "cost": "0.0065", "opportun": "0.0065", "fail": "0.0065", "close": "0.0065", "precipit": "0.0065", "concern": "0.0065", "lead": "0.0065", "profit": "0.0065", "defend": "0.0065", "abl": "0.0065", "bad": "0.0065", "favor": "0.0065", "restructur": "0.0065", "outstand": "0.0065", "deficit": "0.0065", "progress": "0.0065", "boost": "0.0065", "correct": "0.0065", "encourag": "0.0065", "investig": "0.0065", "advanc": "0.0065", "weak": "0.0065", "ban": "0.0065", "slow": "0.0065", "excess": "0.0065", "disput": "0.0065", "strong": "0.0065", "great": "0.0065", "deterior": "0.0065", "unemploy": "0.0065", "contract": "0.0065", "threat": "0.0065", "improv": "0.0065", "allianc": "0.0065", "suspend": "0.0196", "effici": "0.0065", "declin": "0.0065", "win": "0.0065", "bankruptci": "0.0065", "shortag": "0.0065", "cancel": "0.0131", "stabl": "0.0065", "miss": "0.0065", "drought": "0.0065", "damag": "0.0065", "bolster": "0.0065", "better": "0.0065", "question": "0.0065", "construct": "0.0065", "doubt": "0.0065", "downgrad": "0.0065", "threaten": "0.0065", "unexpect": "0.0065", "forc": "0.0065", "hurt": "0.0065", "warn": "0.0065", "gain": "0.0065", "termin": "0.0065", "eas": "0.0065", "highest": "0.0065", "fraud": "0.0065", "default": "0.0065", "seiz": "0.0065", "will": "0.0065", "limit": "0.0065", "posit": "0.0065", "problem": "0.0065", "claim": "0.0065", "weaker": "0.0065", "advantag": "0.0065", "strengthen": "0.0065", "challeng": "0.0065", "premier": "0.0065", "worri": "0.0065", "alleg": "0.0065", "critic": "0.0065", "attract": "0.0065", "sever": "0.0065", "halt": "0.0065", "strength": "0.0065", "delay": "0.0065", "fire": "0.0065", "boom": "0.0065", "reject": "0.0065", "weaken": "0.0065", "difficult": "0.0065", "tighten": "0.0065", "effect": "0.0065", "resign": "0.0065", "alert": "0.0065", "quit": "0.0065", "refin": "0.0065", "postpon": "0.0065", "stabil": "0.0065", "stress": "0.0065", "liquid": "0.0065", "antitrust": "0.0065", "stronger": "0.0065", "su": "0.0065", "inform": "0.0065", "deni": "0.0065", "achiev": "0.0065"}, "13": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "14": {"recess": "0.0062", "opposit": "0.0062", "lack": "0.0062", "protest": "0.0062", "surpass": "0.0062", "fear": "0.0062", "suffer": "0.0062", "fine": "0.0062", "accus": "0.0062", "cut": "0.0247", "depend": "0.0062", "except": "0.0062", "late": "0.0062", "arrest": "0.0062", "bailout": "0.0062", "volatil": "0.0062", "disrupt": "0.0062", "complaint": "0.0062", "good": "0.0062", "greater": "0.0062", "disclos": "0.0062", "rebound": "0.0062", "stop": "0.0062", "break": "0.0062", "worst": "0.0062", "know": "0.0062", "press": "0.0062", "loss": "0.0062", "bar": "0.0062", "success": "0.0185", "lost": "0.0123", "outperform": "0.0062", "drop": "0.0062", "negat": "0.0062", "resolv": "0.0062", "defens": "0.0062", "benefit": "0.0062", "integr": "0.0062", "lose": "0.0062", "popular": "0.0062", "collaps": "0.0062", "crisi": "0.0062", "prevent": "0.0062", "confid": "0.0062", "slower": "0.0062", "shut": "0.0062", "slowdown": "0.0062", "strongest": "0.0062", "cost": "0.0062", "opportun": "0.0062", "fail": "0.0062", "close": "0.0062", "precipit": "0.0062", "concern": "0.0062", "lead": "0.0062", "profit": "0.0062", "defend": "0.0062", "abl": "0.0123", "bad": "0.0062", "favor": "0.0062", "restructur": "0.0185", "outstand": "0.0062", "deficit": "0.0062", "progress": "0.0062", "boost": "0.0062", "correct": "0.0062", "encourag": "0.0062", "investig": "0.0062", "advanc": "0.0062", "weak": "0.0062", "ban": "0.0062", "slow": "0.0062", "excess": "0.0062", "disput": "0.0062", "strong": "0.0062", "great": "0.0062", "deterior": "0.0062", "unemploy": "0.0062", "contract": "0.0062", "threat": "0.0062", "improv": "0.0062", "allianc": "0.0062", "suspend": "0.0062", "effici": "0.0062", "declin": "0.0062", "win": "0.0062", "bankruptci": "0.0062", "shortag": "0.0062", "cancel": "0.0062", "stabl": "0.0062", "miss": "0.0062", "drought": "0.0062", "damag": "0.0062", "bolster": "0.0062", "better": "0.0062", "question": "0.0062", "construct": "0.0062", "doubt": "0.0062", "downgrad": "0.0062", "threaten": "0.0062", "unexpect": "0.0062", "forc": "0.0062", "hurt": "0.0062", "warn": "0.0062", "gain": "0.0062", "termin": "0.0062", "eas": "0.0062", "highest": "0.0062", "fraud": "0.0062", "default": "0.0185", "seiz": "0.0062", "will": "0.0062", "limit": "0.0062", "posit": "0.0062", "problem": "0.0062", "claim": "0.0062", "weaker": "0.0062", "advantag": "0.0062", "strengthen": "0.0062", "challeng": "0.0062", "premier": "0.0062", "worri": "0.0062", "alleg": "0.0062", "critic": "0.0062", "attract": "0.0062", "sever": "0.0062", "halt": "0.0062", "strength": "0.0062", "delay": "0.0062", "fire": "0.0062", "boom": "0.0062", "reject": "0.0062", "weaken": "0.0062", "difficult": "0.0062", "tighten": "0.0062", "effect": "0.0062", "resign": "0.0062", "alert": "0.0062", "quit": "0.0062", "refin": "0.0062", "postpon": "0.0062", "stabil": "0.0062", "stress": "0.0062", "liquid": "0.0123", "antitrust": "0.0062", "stronger": "0.0062", "su": "0.0062", "inform": "0.0062", "deni": "0.0062", "achiev": "0.0062"}, "15": {"recess": "0.0061", "opposit": "0.0061", "lack": "0.0061", "protest": "0.0061", "surpass": "0.0061", "fear": "0.0061", "suffer": "0.0061", "fine": "0.0061", "accus": "0.0061", "cut": "0.0061", "depend": "0.0061", "except": "0.0061", "late": "0.0061", "arrest": "0.0061", "bailout": "0.0061", "volatil": "0.0061", "disrupt": "0.0061", "complaint": "0.0061", "good": "0.0061", "greater": "0.0122", "disclos": "0.0061", "rebound": "0.0061", "stop": "0.0061", "break": "0.0061", "worst": "0.0122", "know": "0.0061", "press": "0.0061", "loss": "0.0061", "bar": "0.0061", "success": "0.0061", "lost": "0.0061", "outperform": "0.0061", "drop": "0.0122", "negat": "0.0061", "resolv": "0.0061", "defens": "0.0061", "benefit": "0.0061", "integr": "0.0061", "lose": "0.0061", "popular": "0.0061", "collaps": "0.0061", "crisi": "0.0061", "prevent": "0.0122", "confid": "0.0122", "slower": "0.0061", "shut": "0.0061", "slowdown": "0.0122", "strongest": "0.0061", "cost": "0.0061", "opportun": "0.0061", "fail": "0.0061", "close": "0.0061", "precipit": "0.0061", "concern": "0.0061", "lead": "0.0061", "profit": "0.0061", "defend": "0.0061", "abl": "0.0061", "bad": "0.0061", "favor": "0.0061", "restructur": "0.0061", "outstand": "0.0061", "deficit": "0.0061", "progress": "0.0061", "boost": "0.0061", "correct": "0.0061", "encourag": "0.0061", "investig": "0.0061", "advanc": "0.0122", "weak": "0.0061", "ban": "0.0061", "slow": "0.0061", "excess": "0.0061", "disput": "0.0061", "strong": "0.0061", "great": "0.0061", "deterior": "0.0061", "unemploy": "0.0061", "contract": "0.0122", "threat": "0.0061", "improv": "0.0061", "allianc": "0.0061", "suspend": "0.0061", "effici": "0.0061", "declin": "0.0183", "win": "0.0061", "bankruptci": "0.0061", "shortag": "0.0061", "cancel": "0.0061", "stabl": "0.0061", "miss": "0.0061", "drought": "0.0061", "damag": "0.0061", "bolster": "0.0061", "better": "0.0061", "question": "0.0061", "construct": "0.0061", "doubt": "0.0061", "downgrad": "0.0061", "threaten": "0.0061", "unexpect": "0.0061", "forc": "0.0061", "hurt": "0.0061", "warn": "0.0061", "gain": "0.0183", "termin": "0.0061", "eas": "0.0061", "highest": "0.0061", "fraud": "0.0061", "default": "0.0122", "seiz": "0.0061", "will": "0.0061", "limit": "0.0061", "posit": "0.0061", "problem": "0.0061", "claim": "0.0061", "weaker": "0.0061", "advantag": "0.0061", "strengthen": "0.0061", "challeng": "0.0122", "premier": "0.0061", "worri": "0.0061", "alleg": "0.0061", "critic": "0.0061", "attract": "0.0061", "sever": "0.0061", "halt": "0.0061", "strength": "0.0061", "delay": "0.0061", "fire": "0.0061", "boom": "0.0061", "reject": "0.0061", "weaken": "0.0061", "difficult": "0.0061", "tighten": "0.0061", "effect": "0.0061", "resign": "0.0061", "alert": "0.0061", "quit": "0.0061", "refin": "0.0061", "postpon": "0.0061", "stabil": "0.0061", "stress": "0.0061", "liquid": "0.0061", "antitrust": "0.0061", "stronger": "0.0061", "su": "0.0061", "inform": "0.0061", "deni": "0.0061", "achiev": "0.0061"}, "16": {"recess": "0.0066", "opposit": "0.0066", "lack": "0.0066", "protest": "0.0066", "surpass": "0.0066", "fear": "0.0066", "suffer": "0.0066", "fine": "0.0066", "accus": "0.0132", "cut": "0.0066", "depend": "0.0066", "except": "0.0066", "late": "0.0066", "arrest": "0.0066", "bailout": "0.0066", "volatil": "0.0066", "disrupt": "0.0066", "complaint": "0.0066", "good": "0.0066", "greater": "0.0066", "disclos": "0.0066", "rebound": "0.0066", "stop": "0.0066", "break": "0.0066", "worst": "0.0066", "know": "0.0066", "press": "0.0066", "loss": "0.0066", "bar": "0.0066", "success": "0.0066", "lost": "0.0066", "outperform": "0.0066", "drop": "0.0066", "negat": "0.0066", "resolv": "0.0066", "defens": "0.0066", "benefit": "0.0066", "integr": "0.0066", "lose": "0.0066", "popular": "0.0066", "collaps": "0.0066", "crisi": "0.0066", "prevent": "0.0066", "confid": "0.0066", "slower": "0.0066", "shut": "0.0066", "slowdown": "0.0066", "strongest": "0.0066", "cost": "0.0066", "opportun": "0.0066", "fail": "0.0066", "close": "0.0066", "precipit": "0.0066", "concern": "0.0066", "lead": "0.0066", "profit": "0.0066", "defend": "0.0066", "abl": "0.0066", "bad": "0.0066", "favor": "0.0066", "restructur": "0.0066", "outstand": "0.0066", "deficit": "0.0066", "progress": "0.0066", "boost": "0.0066", "correct": "0.0066", "encourag": "0.0066", "investig": "0.0066", "advanc": "0.0066", "weak": "0.0066", "ban": "0.0066", "slow": "0.0066", "excess": "0.0066", "disput": "0.0066", "strong": "0.0066", "great": "0.0066", "deterior": "0.0066", "unemploy": "0.0066", "contract": "0.0066", "threat": "0.0066", "improv": "0.0066", "allianc": "0.0066", "suspend": "0.0066", "effici": "0.0066", "declin": "0.0066", "win": "0.0066", "bankruptci": "0.0066", "shortag": "0.0066", "cancel": "0.0066", "stabl": "0.0066", "miss": "0.0066", "drought": "0.0066", "damag": "0.0066", "bolster": "0.0066", "better": "0.0066", "question": "0.0066", "construct": "0.0066", "doubt": "0.0066", "downgrad": "0.0066", "threaten": "0.0066", "unexpect": "0.0066", "forc": "0.0066", "hurt": "0.0066", "warn": "0.0066", "gain": "0.0066", "termin": "0.0066", "eas": "0.0066", "highest": "0.0066", "fraud": "0.0066", "default": "0.0066", "seiz": "0.0066", "will": "0.0066", "limit": "0.0066", "posit": "0.0066", "problem": "0.0066", "claim": "0.0066", "weaker": "0.0066", "advantag": "0.0066", "strengthen": "0.0066", "challeng": "0.0066", "premier": "0.0066", "worri": "0.0066", "alleg": "0.0066", "critic": "0.0066", "attract": "0.0066", "sever": "0.0066", "halt": "0.0066", "strength": "0.0066", "delay": "0.0066", "fire": "0.0066", "boom": "0.0066", "reject": "0.0066", "weaken": "0.0066", "difficult": "0.0066", "tighten": "0.0066", "effect": "0.0066", "resign": "0.0066", "alert": "0.0066", "quit": "0.0066", "refin": "0.0066", "postpon": "0.0066", "stabil": "0.0066", "stress": "0.0066", "liquid": "0.0066", "antitrust": "0.0066", "stronger": "0.0066", "su": "0.0066", "inform": "0.0066", "deni": "0.0066", "achiev": "0.0066"}, "17": {"recess": "0.0066", "opposit": "0.0066", "lack": "0.0066", "protest": "0.0066", "surpass": "0.0066", "fear": "0.0066", "suffer": "0.0066", "fine": "0.0066", "accus": "0.0066", "cut": "0.0066", "depend": "0.0066", "except": "0.0066", "late": "0.0066", "arrest": "0.0066", "bailout": "0.0066", "volatil": "0.0066", "disrupt": "0.0066", "complaint": "0.0066", "good": "0.0066", "greater": "0.0066", "disclos": "0.0066", "rebound": "0.0066", "stop": "0.0066", "break": "0.0066", "worst": "0.0066", "know": "0.0066", "press": "0.0066", "loss": "0.0066", "bar": "0.0066", "success": "0.0066", "lost": "0.0066", "outperform": "0.0066", "drop": "0.0066", "negat": "0.0066", "resolv": "0.0066", "defens": "0.0066", "benefit": "0.0066", "integr": "0.0066", "lose": "0.0066", "popular": "0.0066", "collaps": "0.0066", "crisi": "0.0066", "prevent": "0.0066", "confid": "0.0066", "slower": "0.0066", "shut": "0.0066", "slowdown": "0.0066", "strongest": "0.0066", "cost": "0.0066", "opportun": "0.0066", "fail": "0.0066", "close": "0.0066", "precipit": "0.0066", "concern": "0.0066", "lead": "0.0066", "profit": "0.0066", "defend": "0.0066", "abl": "0.0066", "bad": "0.0066", "favor": "0.0066", "restructur": "0.0066", "outstand": "0.0066", "deficit": "0.0066", "progress": "0.0066", "boost": "0.0066", "correct": "0.0066", "encourag": "0.0066", "investig": "0.0066", "advanc": "0.0066", "weak": "0.0066", "ban": "0.0066", "slow": "0.0066", "excess": "0.0066", "disput": "0.0066", "strong": "0.0066", "great": "0.0066", "deterior": "0.0066", "unemploy": "0.0066", "contract": "0.0066", "threat": "0.0066", "improv": "0.0066", "allianc": "0.0132", "suspend": "0.0066", "effici": "0.0066", "declin": "0.0066", "win": "0.0132", "bankruptci": "0.0066", "shortag": "0.0066", "cancel": "0.0066", "stabl": "0.0066", "miss": "0.0066", "drought": "0.0066", "damag": "0.0066", "bolster": "0.0066", "better": "0.0066", "question": "0.0066", "construct": "0.0066", "doubt": "0.0066", "downgrad": "0.0066", "threaten": "0.0066", "unexpect": "0.0066", "forc": "0.0066", "hurt": "0.0066", "warn": "0.0066", "gain": "0.0066", "termin": "0.0066", "eas": "0.0066", "highest": "0.0066", "fraud": "0.0066", "default": "0.0066", "seiz": "0.0066", "will": "0.0066", "limit": "0.0066", "posit": "0.0066", "problem": "0.0066", "claim": "0.0066", "weaker": "0.0066", "advantag": "0.0066", "strengthen": "0.0066", "challeng": "0.0066", "premier": "0.0066", "worri": "0.0066", "alleg": "0.0066", "critic": "0.0066", "attract": "0.0066", "sever": "0.0066", "halt": "0.0066", "strength": "0.0066", "delay": "0.0066", "fire": "0.0066", "boom": "0.0066", "reject": "0.0066", "weaken": "0.0066", "difficult": "0.0066", "tighten": "0.0066", "effect": "0.0066", "resign": "0.0066", "alert": "0.0066", "quit": "0.0066", "refin": "0.0066", "postpon": "0.0066", "stabil": "0.0066", "stress": "0.0066", "liquid": "0.0066", "antitrust": "0.0066", "stronger": "0.0066", "su": "0.0066", "inform": "0.0066", "deni": "0.0066", "achiev": "0.0066"}, "18": {"recess": "0.0062", "opposit": "0.0062", "lack": "0.0062", "protest": "0.0062", "surpass": "0.0062", "fear": "0.0062", "suffer": "0.0062", "fine": "0.0062", "accus": "0.0062", "cut": "0.0247", "depend": "0.0062", "except": "0.0062", "late": "0.0062", "arrest": "0.0062", "bailout": "0.0062", "volatil": "0.0062", "disrupt": "0.0062", "complaint": "0.0062", "good": "0.0062", "greater": "0.0062", "disclos": "0.0062", "rebound": "0.0062", "stop": "0.0062", "break": "0.0062", "worst": "0.0062", "know": "0.0062", "press": "0.0062", "loss": "0.0062", "bar": "0.0062", "success": "0.0185", "lost": "0.0123", "outperform": "0.0062", "drop": "0.0062", "negat": "0.0062", "resolv": "0.0062", "defens": "0.0062", "benefit": "0.0062", "integr": "0.0062", "lose": "0.0062", "popular": "0.0062", "collaps": "0.0062", "crisi": "0.0062", "prevent": "0.0062", "confid": "0.0062", "slower": "0.0062", "shut": "0.0062", "slowdown": "0.0062", "strongest": "0.0062", "cost": "0.0062", "opportun": "0.0062", "fail": "0.0062", "close": "0.0062", "precipit": "0.0062", "concern": "0.0062", "lead": "0.0062", "profit": "0.0062", "defend": "0.0062", "abl": "0.0123", "bad": "0.0062", "favor": "0.0062", "restructur": "0.0185", "outstand": "0.0062", "deficit": "0.0062", "progress": "0.0062", "boost": "0.0062", "correct": "0.0062", "encourag": "0.0062", "investig": "0.0062", "advanc": "0.0062", "weak": "0.0062", "ban": "0.0062", "slow": "0.0062", "excess": "0.0062", "disput": "0.0062", "strong": "0.0062", "great": "0.0062", "deterior": "0.0062", "unemploy": "0.0062", "contract": "0.0062", "threat": "0.0062", "improv": "0.0062", "allianc": "0.0062", "suspend": "0.0062", "effici": "0.0062", "declin": "0.0062", "win": "0.0062", "bankruptci": "0.0062", "shortag": "0.0062", "cancel": "0.0062", "stabl": "0.0062", "miss": "0.0062", "drought": "0.0062", "damag": "0.0062", "bolster": "0.0062", "better": "0.0062", "question": "0.0062", "construct": "0.0062", "doubt": "0.0062", "downgrad": "0.0062", "threaten": "0.0062", "unexpect": "0.0062", "forc": "0.0062", "hurt": "0.0062", "warn": "0.0062", "gain": "0.0062", "termin": "0.0062", "eas": "0.0062", "highest": "0.0062", "fraud": "0.0062", "default": "0.0185", "seiz": "0.0062", "will": "0.0062", "limit": "0.0062", "posit": "0.0062", "problem": "0.0062", "claim": "0.0062", "weaker": "0.0062", "advantag": "0.0062", "strengthen": "0.0062", "challeng": "0.0062", "premier": "0.0062", "worri": "0.0062", "alleg": "0.0062", "critic": "0.0062", "attract": "0.0062", "sever": "0.0062", "halt": "0.0062", "strength": "0.0062", "delay": "0.0062", "fire": "0.0062", "boom": "0.0062", "reject": "0.0062", "weaken": "0.0062", "difficult": "0.0062", "tighten": "0.0062", "effect": "0.0062", "resign": "0.0062", "alert": "0.0062", "quit": "0.0062", "refin": "0.0062", "postpon": "0.0062", "stabil": "0.0062", "stress": "0.0062", "liquid": "0.0123", "antitrust": "0.0062", "stronger": "0.0062", "su": "0.0062", "inform": "0.0062", "deni": "0.0062", "achiev": "0.0062"}, "19": {"recess": "0.0061", "opposit": "0.0061", "lack": "0.0061", "protest": "0.0061", "surpass": "0.0061", "fear": "0.0061", "suffer": "0.0061", "fine": "0.0122", "accus": "0.0122", "cut": "0.0061", "depend": "0.0061", "except": "0.0061", "late": "0.0061", "arrest": "0.0061", "bailout": "0.0061", "volatil": "0.0061", "disrupt": "0.0061", "complaint": "0.0061", "good": "0.0061", "greater": "0.0061", "disclos": "0.0122", "rebound": "0.0061", "stop": "0.0061", "break": "0.0061", "worst": "0.0061", "know": "0.0061", "press": "0.0061", "loss": "0.0061", "bar": "0.0061", "success": "0.0061", "lost": "0.0061", "outperform": "0.0061", "drop": "0.0061", "negat": "0.0061", "resolv": "0.0061", "defens": "0.0061", "benefit": "0.0061", "integr": "0.0061", "lose": "0.0061", "popular": "0.0061", "collaps": "0.0061", "crisi": "0.0061", "prevent": "0.0061", "confid": "0.0061", "slower": "0.0061", "shut": "0.0061", "slowdown": "0.0061", "strongest": "0.0061", "cost": "0.0061", "opportun": "0.0061", "fail": "0.0061", "close": "0.0061", "precipit": "0.0061", "concern": "0.0061", "lead": "0.0061", "profit": "0.0122", "defend": "0.0061", "abl": "0.0061", "bad": "0.0061", "favor": "0.0061", "restructur": "0.0061", "outstand": "0.0061", "deficit": "0.0061", "progress": "0.0061", "boost": "0.0061", "correct": "0.0061", "encourag": "0.0061", "investig": "0.0061", "advanc": "0.0061", "weak": "0.0061", "ban": "0.0061", "slow": "0.0061", "excess": "0.0061", "disput": "0.0061", "strong": "0.0061", "great": "0.0061", "deterior": "0.0061", "unemploy": "0.0061", "contract": "0.0122", "threat": "0.0061", "improv": "0.0061", "allianc": "0.0061", "suspend": "0.0061", "effici": "0.0061", "declin": "0.0183", "win": "0.0061", "bankruptci": "0.0061", "shortag": "0.0061", "cancel": "0.0122", "stabl": "0.0061", "miss": "0.0061", "drought": "0.0061", "damag": "0.0061", "bolster": "0.0061", "better": "0.0061", "question": "0.0061", "construct": "0.0061", "doubt": "0.0061", "downgrad": "0.0061", "threaten": "0.0061", "unexpect": "0.0061", "forc": "0.0061", "hurt": "0.0061", "warn": "0.0061", "gain": "0.0244", "termin": "0.0061", "eas": "0.0061", "highest": "0.0122", "fraud": "0.0061", "default": "0.0061", "seiz": "0.0061", "will": "0.0061", "limit": "0.0061", "posit": "0.0061", "problem": "0.0061", "claim": "0.0061", "weaker": "0.0061", "advantag": "0.0061", "strengthen": "0.0061", "challeng": "0.0061", "premier": "0.0061", "worri": "0.0061", "alleg": "0.0061", "critic": "0.0061", "attract": "0.0061", "sever": "0.0061", "halt": "0.0061", "strength": "0.0061", "delay": "0.0061", "fire": "0.0061", "boom": "0.0061", "reject": "0.0061", "weaken": "0.0061", "difficult": "0.0061", "tighten": "0.0061", "effect": "0.0061", "resign": "0.0061", "alert": "0.0061", "quit": "0.0061", "refin": "0.0061", "postpon": "0.0061", "stabil": "0.0061", "stress": "0.0061", "liquid": "0.0061", "antitrust": "0.0061", "stronger": "0.0061", "su": "0.0061", "inform": "0.0183", "deni": "0.0061", "achiev": "0.0061"}, "20": {"recess": "0.0021", "opposit": "0.0205", "lack": "0.0062", "protest": "0.0062", "surpass": "0.0041", "fear": "0.0082", "suffer": "0.0041", "fine": "0.0021", "accus": "0.0144", "cut": "0.0082", "depend": "0.0082", "except": "0.0041", "late": "0.0082", "arrest": "0.0021", "bailout": "0.0021", "volatil": "0.0021", "disrupt": "0.0021", "complaint": "0.0062", "good": "0.0041", "greater": "0.0041", "disclos": "0.0021", "rebound": "0.0021", "stop": "0.0082", "break": "0.0021", "worst": "0.0062", "know": "0.0123", "press": "0.0144", "loss": "0.0021", "bar": "0.0021", "success": "0.0021", "lost": "0.0103", "outperform": "0.0041", "drop": "0.0082", "negat": "0.0021", "resolv": "0.0041", "defens": "0.0021", "benefit": "0.0082", "integr": "0.0021", "lose": "0.0041", "popular": "0.0103", "collaps": "0.0021", "crisi": "0.0041", "prevent": "0.0062", "confid": "0.0062", "slower": "0.0041", "shut": "0.0082", "slowdown": "0.0021", "strongest": "0.0021", "cost": "0.0144", "opportun": "0.0021", "fail": "0.0185", "close": "0.0062", "precipit": "0.0021", "concern": "0.0185", "lead": "0.0123", "profit": "0.0082", "defend": "0.0062", "abl": "0.0062", "bad": "0.0021", "favor": "0.0144", "restructur": "0.0103", "outstand": "0.0062", "deficit": "0.0021", "progress": "0.0021", "boost": "0.0185", "correct": "0.0021", "encourag": "0.0041", "investig": "0.0082", "advanc": "0.0062", "weak": "0.0021", "ban": "0.0041", "slow": "0.0246", "excess": "0.0041", "disput": "0.0103", "strong": "0.0041", "great": "0.0021", "deterior": "0.0021", "unemploy": "0.0021", "contract": "0.0267", "threat": "0.0021", "improv": "0.0103", "allianc": "0.0021", "suspend": "0.0164", "effici": "0.0021", "declin": "0.0205", "win": "0.0246", "bankruptci": "0.0021", "shortag": "0.0205", "cancel": "0.0062", "stabl": "0.0021", "miss": "0.0021", "drought": "0.0041", "damag": "0.0041", "bolster": "0.0041", "better": "0.0041", "question": "0.0144", "construct": "0.0021", "doubt": "0.0082", "downgrad": "0.0021", "threaten": "0.0062", "unexpect": "0.0041", "forc": "0.0164", "hurt": "0.0021", "warn": "0.0021", "gain": "0.0329", "termin": "0.0021", "eas": "0.0062", "highest": "0.0185", "fraud": "0.0021", "default": "0.0329", "seiz": "0.0062", "will": "0.0082", "limit": "0.0185", "posit": "0.0041", "problem": "0.0103", "claim": "0.0103", "weaker": "0.0021", "advantag": "0.0021", "strengthen": "0.0062", "challeng": "0.0021", "premier": "0.0021", "worri": "0.0041", "alleg": "0.0021", "critic": "0.0144", "attract": "0.0062", "sever": "0.0082", "halt": "0.0062", "strength": "0.0021", "delay": "0.0041", "fire": "0.0041", "boom": "0.0021", "reject": "0.0103", "weaken": "0.0041", "difficult": "0.0021", "tighten": "0.0062", "effect": "0.0041", "resign": "0.0041", "alert": "0.0021", "quit": "0.0041", "refin": "0.0021", "postpon": "0.0062", "stabil": "0.0021", "stress": "0.0021", "liquid": "0.0021", "antitrust": "0.0021", "stronger": "0.0021", "su": "0.0062", "inform": "0.0103", "deni": "0.0062", "achiev": "0.0021"}}, "IBVC": {}, "IGBVL": {"1": {"recess": "0.0019", "opposit": "0.0056", "lack": "0.0037", "protest": "0.0130", "surpass": "0.0056", "fear": "0.0112", "suffer": "0.0037", "fine": "0.0019", "accus": "0.0112", "cut": "0.0167", "depend": "0.0037", "except": "0.0019", "late": "0.0037", "arrest": "0.0019", "bailout": "0.0019", "volatil": "0.0037", "disrupt": "0.0019", "complaint": "0.0019", "good": "0.0037", "greater": "0.0056", "disclos": "0.0019", "rebound": "0.0093", "stop": "0.0037", "break": "0.0019", "worst": "0.0037", "know": "0.0056", "press": "0.0019", "loss": "0.0074", "bar": "0.0019", "success": "0.0019", "lost": "0.0242", "outperform": "0.0037", "drop": "0.0762", "negat": "0.0074", "resolv": "0.0037", "defens": "0.0019", "benefit": "0.0093", "integr": "0.0112", "lose": "0.0074", "popular": "0.0019", "collaps": "0.0074", "crisi": "0.0037", "prevent": "0.0093", "confid": "0.0019", "slower": "0.0037", "shut": "0.0019", "slowdown": "0.0019", "strongest": "0.0037", "cost": "0.0242", "opportun": "0.0019", "fail": "0.0056", "close": "0.0074", "precipit": "0.0019", "concern": "0.0353", "lead": "0.0483", "profit": "0.0037", "defend": "0.0074", "abl": "0.0056", "bad": "0.0019", "favor": "0.0074", "restructur": "0.0019", "outstand": "0.0019", "deficit": "0.0037", "progress": "0.0056", "boost": "0.0093", "correct": "0.0019", "encourag": "0.0037", "investig": "0.0019", "advanc": "0.0130", "weak": "0.0019", "ban": "0.0019", "slow": "0.0130", "excess": "0.0019", "disput": "0.0019", "strong": "0.0093", "great": "0.0056", "deterior": "0.0019", "unemploy": "0.0037", "contract": "0.0112", "threat": "0.0019", "improv": "0.0037", "allianc": "0.0074", "suspend": "0.0093", "effici": "0.0019", "declin": "0.0632", "win": "0.0223", "bankruptci": "0.0019", "shortag": "0.0019", "cancel": "0.0019", "stabl": "0.0019", "miss": "0.0019", "drought": "0.0019", "damag": "0.0019", "bolster": "0.0019", "better": "0.0037", "question": "0.0056", "construct": "0.0056", "doubt": "0.0056", "downgrad": "0.0019", "threaten": "0.0019", "unexpect": "0.0037", "forc": "0.0093", "hurt": "0.0019", "warn": "0.0056", "gain": "0.0372", "termin": "0.0037", "eas": "0.0056", "highest": "0.0149", "fraud": "0.0019", "default": "0.0056", "seiz": "0.0167", "will": "0.0019", "limit": "0.0074", "posit": "0.0056", "problem": "0.0093", "claim": "0.0242", "weaker": "0.0019", "advantag": "0.0037", "strengthen": "0.0074", "challeng": "0.0019", "premier": "0.0019", "worri": "0.0037", "alleg": "0.0019", "critic": "0.0019", "attract": "0.0056", "sever": "0.0037", "halt": "0.0037", "strength": "0.0019", "delay": "0.0093", "fire": "0.0019", "boom": "0.0186", "reject": "0.0056", "weaken": "0.0056", "difficult": "0.0074", "tighten": "0.0019", "effect": "0.0019", "resign": "0.0019", "alert": "0.0019", "quit": "0.0037", "refin": "0.0037", "postpon": "0.0037", "stabil": "0.0019", "stress": "0.0019", "liquid": "0.0037", "antitrust": "0.0019", "stronger": "0.0019", "su": "0.0037", "inform": "0.0037", "deni": "0.0019", "achiev": "0.0019"}, "2": {"recess": "0.0034", "opposit": "0.0137", "lack": "0.0068", "protest": "0.0137", "surpass": "0.0034", "fear": "0.0068", "suffer": "0.0034", "fine": "0.0034", "accus": "0.0034", "cut": "0.0137", "depend": "0.0068", "except": "0.0034", "late": "0.0068", "arrest": "0.0034", "bailout": "0.0034", "volatil": "0.0034", "disrupt": "0.0034", "complaint": "0.0034", "good": "0.0068", "greater": "0.0102", "disclos": "0.0034", "rebound": "0.0034", "stop": "0.0137", "break": "0.0034", "worst": "0.0205", "know": "0.0034", "press": "0.0034", "loss": "0.0034", "bar": "0.0034", "success": "0.0034", "lost": "0.0137", "outperform": "0.0034", "drop": "0.0478", "negat": "0.0034", "resolv": "0.0034", "defens": "0.0034", "benefit": "0.0034", "integr": "0.0034", "lose": "0.0171", "popular": "0.0102", "collaps": "0.0034", "crisi": "0.0034", "prevent": "0.0137", "confid": "0.0034", "slower": "0.0068", "shut": "0.0034", "slowdown": "0.0034", "strongest": "0.0034", "cost": "0.0273", "opportun": "0.0068", "fail": "0.0137", "close": "0.0137", "precipit": "0.0034", "concern": "0.0171", "lead": "0.0137", "profit": "0.0034", "defend": "0.0034", "abl": "0.0034", "bad": "0.0034", "favor": "0.0102", "restructur": "0.0034", "outstand": "0.0068", "deficit": "0.0034", "progress": "0.0034", "boost": "0.0068", "correct": "0.0068", "encourag": "0.0034", "investig": "0.0034", "advanc": "0.0034", "weak": "0.0034", "ban": "0.0171", "slow": "0.0102", "excess": "0.0034", "disput": "0.0034", "strong": "0.0205", "great": "0.0034", "deterior": "0.0034", "unemploy": "0.0034", "contract": "0.0068", "threat": "0.0068", "improv": "0.0034", "allianc": "0.0034", "suspend": "0.0034", "effici": "0.0034", "declin": "0.0375", "win": "0.0205", "bankruptci": "0.0034", "shortag": "0.0034", "cancel": "0.0034", "stabl": "0.0034", "miss": "0.0034", "drought": "0.0034", "damag": "0.0034", "bolster": "0.0068", "better": "0.0034", "question": "0.0034", "construct": "0.0034", "doubt": "0.0034", "downgrad": "0.0034", "threaten": "0.0034", "unexpect": "0.0034", "forc": "0.0137", "hurt": "0.0034", "warn": "0.0034", "gain": "0.0205", "termin": "0.0034", "eas": "0.0034", "highest": "0.0137", "fraud": "0.0034", "default": "0.0137", "seiz": "0.0137", "will": "0.0034", "limit": "0.0102", "posit": "0.0034", "problem": "0.0034", "claim": "0.0034", "weaker": "0.0034", "advantag": "0.0034", "strengthen": "0.0034", "challeng": "0.0034", "premier": "0.0034", "worri": "0.0102", "alleg": "0.0034", "critic": "0.0034", "attract": "0.0034", "sever": "0.0034", "halt": "0.0034", "strength": "0.0034", "delay": "0.0034", "fire": "0.0034", "boom": "0.0137", "reject": "0.0068", "weaken": "0.0034", "difficult": "0.0068", "tighten": "0.0171", "effect": "0.0102", "resign": "0.0034", "alert": "0.0034", "quit": "0.0034", "refin": "0.0068", "postpon": "0.0034", "stabil": "0.0102", "stress": "0.0034", "liquid": "0.0034", "antitrust": "0.0034", "stronger": "0.0068", "su": "0.0034", "inform": "0.0102", "deni": "0.0034", "achiev": "0.0034"}, "3": {"recess": "0.0038", "opposit": "0.0038", "lack": "0.0038", "protest": "0.0038", "surpass": "0.0038", "fear": "0.0038", "suffer": "0.0038", "fine": "0.0038", "accus": "0.0038", "cut": "0.0038", "depend": "0.0077", "except": "0.0038", "late": "0.0038", "arrest": "0.0038", "bailout": "0.0038", "volatil": "0.0038", "disrupt": "0.0038", "complaint": "0.0038", "good": "0.0038", "greater": "0.0038", "disclos": "0.0038", "rebound": "0.0115", "stop": "0.0038", "break": "0.0038", "worst": "0.0038", "know": "0.0077", "press": "0.0038", "loss": "0.0038", "bar": "0.0038", "success": "0.0038", "lost": "0.0038", "outperform": "0.0038", "drop": "0.0462", "negat": "0.0038", "resolv": "0.0038", "defens": "0.0038", "benefit": "0.0038", "integr": "0.0038", "lose": "0.0115", "popular": "0.0038", "collaps": "0.0038", "crisi": "0.0115", "prevent": "0.0038", "confid": "0.0038", "slower": "0.0077", "shut": "0.0038", "slowdown": "0.0038", "strongest": "0.0038", "cost": "0.0192", "opportun": "0.0038", "fail": "0.0038", "close": "0.0077", "precipit": "0.0038", "concern": "0.0269", "lead": "0.0192", "profit": "0.0038", "defend": "0.0038", "abl": "0.0038", "bad": "0.0038", "favor": "0.0077", "restructur": "0.0038", "outstand": "0.0038", "deficit": "0.0038", "progress": "0.0038", "boost": "0.0038", "correct": "0.0077", "encourag": "0.0038", "investig": "0.0038", "advanc": "0.0346", "weak": "0.0038", "ban": "0.0038", "slow": "0.0231", "excess": "0.0038", "disput": "0.0038", "strong": "0.0077", "great": "0.0038", "deterior": "0.0038", "unemploy": "0.0038", "contract": "0.0115", "threat": "0.0038", "improv": "0.0038", "allianc": "0.0038", "suspend": "0.0038", "effici": "0.0038", "declin": "0.0462", "win": "0.0115", "bankruptci": "0.0038", "shortag": "0.0038", "cancel": "0.0038", "stabl": "0.0038", "miss": "0.0038", "drought": "0.0038", "damag": "0.0038", "bolster": "0.0038", "better": "0.0038", "question": "0.0038", "construct": "0.0038", "doubt": "0.0077", "downgrad": "0.0038", "threaten": "0.0038", "unexpect": "0.0038", "forc": "0.0038", "hurt": "0.0038", "warn": "0.0038", "gain": "0.0769", "termin": "0.0038", "eas": "0.0115", "highest": "0.0115", "fraud": "0.0038", "default": "0.0038", "seiz": "0.0038", "will": "0.0038", "limit": "0.0269", "posit": "0.0115", "problem": "0.0038", "claim": "0.0038", "weaker": "0.0038", "advantag": "0.0038", "strengthen": "0.0115", "challeng": "0.0038", "premier": "0.0038", "worri": "0.0038", "alleg": "0.0038", "critic": "0.0038", "attract": "0.0038", "sever": "0.0038", "halt": "0.0038", "strength": "0.0038", "delay": "0.0077", "fire": "0.0038", "boom": "0.0038", "reject": "0.0038", "weaken": "0.0038", "difficult": "0.0038", "tighten": "0.0269", "effect": "0.0038", "resign": "0.0038", "alert": "0.0077", "quit": "0.0038", "refin": "0.0077", "postpon": "0.0077", "stabil": "0.0038", "stress": "0.0038", "liquid": "0.0038", "antitrust": "0.0038", "stronger": "0.0038", "su": "0.0038", "inform": "0.0038", "deni": "0.0038", "achiev": "0.0038"}, "4": {"recess": "0.0028", "opposit": "0.0169", "lack": "0.0056", "protest": "0.0169", "surpass": "0.0056", "fear": "0.0028", "suffer": "0.0028", "fine": "0.0028", "accus": "0.0056", "cut": "0.0056", "depend": "0.0028", "except": "0.0028", "late": "0.0056", "arrest": "0.0028", "bailout": "0.0028", "volatil": "0.0056", "disrupt": "0.0028", "complaint": "0.0028", "good": "0.0028", "greater": "0.0085", "disclos": "0.0028", "rebound": "0.0085", "stop": "0.0085", "break": "0.0028", "worst": "0.0085", "know": "0.0056", "press": "0.0028", "loss": "0.0056", "bar": "0.0028", "success": "0.0056", "lost": "0.0198", "outperform": "0.0056", "drop": "0.0876", "negat": "0.0056", "resolv": "0.0028", "defens": "0.0028", "benefit": "0.0056", "integr": "0.0169", "lose": "0.0226", "popular": "0.0113", "collaps": "0.0056", "crisi": "0.0028", "prevent": "0.0085", "confid": "0.0056", "slower": "0.0028", "shut": "0.0028", "slowdown": "0.0028", "strongest": "0.0028", "cost": "0.0085", "opportun": "0.0028", "fail": "0.0169", "close": "0.0113", "precipit": "0.0028", "concern": "0.0169", "lead": "0.0339", "profit": "0.0028", "defend": "0.0028", "abl": "0.0028", "bad": "0.0028", "favor": "0.0113", "restructur": "0.0028", "outstand": "0.0056", "deficit": "0.0028", "progress": "0.0028", "boost": "0.0056", "correct": "0.0028", "encourag": "0.0028", "investig": "0.0028", "advanc": "0.0113", "weak": "0.0028", "ban": "0.0085", "slow": "0.0056", "excess": "0.0028", "disput": "0.0028", "strong": "0.0113", "great": "0.0028", "deterior": "0.0028", "unemploy": "0.0028", "contract": "0.0226", "threat": "0.0056", "improv": "0.0028", "allianc": "0.0113", "suspend": "0.0028", "effici": "0.0028", "declin": "0.0508", "win": "0.0198", "bankruptci": "0.0028", "shortag": "0.0028", "cancel": "0.0028", "stabl": "0.0028", "miss": "0.0028", "drought": "0.0028", "damag": "0.0028", "bolster": "0.0028", "better": "0.0028", "question": "0.0028", "construct": "0.0056", "doubt": "0.0028", "downgrad": "0.0028", "threaten": "0.0028", "unexpect": "0.0028", "forc": "0.0113", "hurt": "0.0028", "warn": "0.0056", "gain": "0.0339", "termin": "0.0028", "eas": "0.0028", "highest": "0.0085", "fraud": "0.0028", "default": "0.0085", "seiz": "0.0169", "will": "0.0028", "limit": "0.0028", "posit": "0.0028", "problem": "0.0113", "claim": "0.0028", "weaker": "0.0028", "advantag": "0.0056", "strengthen": "0.0028", "challeng": "0.0028", "premier": "0.0028", "worri": "0.0028", "alleg": "0.0028", "critic": "0.0028", "attract": "0.0085", "sever": "0.0028", "halt": "0.0028", "strength": "0.0028", "delay": "0.0056", "fire": "0.0028", "boom": "0.0113", "reject": "0.0085", "weaken": "0.0056", "difficult": "0.0056", "tighten": "0.0028", "effect": "0.0028", "resign": "0.0028", "alert": "0.0028", "quit": "0.0028", "refin": "0.0085", "postpon": "0.0028", "stabil": "0.0085", "stress": "0.0028", "liquid": "0.0056", "antitrust": "0.0028", "stronger": "0.0028", "su": "0.0028", "inform": "0.0056", "deni": "0.0028", "achiev": "0.0028"}, "5": {"recess": "0.0031", "opposit": "0.0031", "lack": "0.0031", "protest": "0.0063", "surpass": "0.0031", "fear": "0.0063", "suffer": "0.0031", "fine": "0.0031", "accus": "0.0031", "cut": "0.0063", "depend": "0.0031", "except": "0.0031", "late": "0.0063", "arrest": "0.0031", "bailout": "0.0031", "volatil": "0.0094", "disrupt": "0.0031", "complaint": "0.0031", "good": "0.0031", "greater": "0.0063", "disclos": "0.0031", "rebound": "0.0157", "stop": "0.0031", "break": "0.0031", "worst": "0.0063", "know": "0.0031", "press": "0.0031", "loss": "0.0063", "bar": "0.0063", "success": "0.0063", "lost": "0.0063", "outperform": "0.0031", "drop": "0.0723", "negat": "0.0094", "resolv": "0.0031", "defens": "0.0031", "benefit": "0.0031", "integr": "0.0189", "lose": "0.0126", "popular": "0.0031", "collaps": "0.0031", "crisi": "0.0031", "prevent": "0.0031", "confid": "0.0031", "slower": "0.0063", "shut": "0.0063", "slowdown": "0.0063", "strongest": "0.0031", "cost": "0.0189", "opportun": "0.0063", "fail": "0.0031", "close": "0.0189", "precipit": "0.0031", "concern": "0.0157", "lead": "0.0314", "profit": "0.0031", "defend": "0.0063", "abl": "0.0031", "bad": "0.0031", "favor": "0.0063", "restructur": "0.0031", "outstand": "0.0031", "deficit": "0.0031", "progress": "0.0031", "boost": "0.0063", "correct": "0.0031", "encourag": "0.0031", "investig": "0.0031", "advanc": "0.0283", "weak": "0.0031", "ban": "0.0063", "slow": "0.0220", "excess": "0.0031", "disput": "0.0063", "strong": "0.0126", "great": "0.0031", "deterior": "0.0031", "unemploy": "0.0031", "contract": "0.0094", "threat": "0.0031", "improv": "0.0031", "allianc": "0.0031", "suspend": "0.0031", "effici": "0.0031", "declin": "0.0440", "win": "0.0220", "bankruptci": "0.0063", "shortag": "0.0063", "cancel": "0.0063", "stabl": "0.0031", "miss": "0.0031", "drought": "0.0031", "damag": "0.0031", "bolster": "0.0063", "better": "0.0031", "question": "0.0031", "construct": "0.0031", "doubt": "0.0031", "downgrad": "0.0031", "threaten": "0.0031", "unexpect": "0.0063", "forc": "0.0063", "hurt": "0.0031", "warn": "0.0031", "gain": "0.0566", "termin": "0.0031", "eas": "0.0063", "highest": "0.0157", "fraud": "0.0031", "default": "0.0063", "seiz": "0.0063", "will": "0.0031", "limit": "0.0126", "posit": "0.0126", "problem": "0.0031", "claim": "0.0031", "weaker": "0.0031", "advantag": "0.0094", "strengthen": "0.0094", "challeng": "0.0063", "premier": "0.0031", "worri": "0.0031", "alleg": "0.0031", "critic": "0.0031", "attract": "0.0094", "sever": "0.0031", "halt": "0.0031", "strength": "0.0031", "delay": "0.0031", "fire": "0.0031", "boom": "0.0094", "reject": "0.0031", "weaken": "0.0126", "difficult": "0.0031", "tighten": "0.0031", "effect": "0.0031", "resign": "0.0031", "alert": "0.0031", "quit": "0.0031", "refin": "0.0063", "postpon": "0.0031", "stabil": "0.0031", "stress": "0.0031", "liquid": "0.0063", "antitrust": "0.0031", "stronger": "0.0031", "su": "0.0031", "inform": "0.0031", "deni": "0.0031", "achiev": "0.0031"}, "6": {"recess": "0.0019", "opposit": "0.0056", "lack": "0.0038", "protest": "0.0094", "surpass": "0.0019", "fear": "0.0038", "suffer": "0.0019", "fine": "0.0019", "accus": "0.0019", "cut": "0.0094", "depend": "0.0038", "except": "0.0019", "late": "0.0019", "arrest": "0.0038", "bailout": "0.0019", "volatil": "0.0019", "disrupt": "0.0019", "complaint": "0.0019", "good": "0.0075", "greater": "0.0094", "disclos": "0.0019", "rebound": "0.0207", "stop": "0.0019", "break": "0.0019", "worst": "0.0019", "know": "0.0019", "press": "0.0019", "loss": "0.0056", "bar": "0.0038", "success": "0.0056", "lost": "0.0075", "outperform": "0.0019", "drop": "0.0659", "negat": "0.0038", "resolv": "0.0019", "defens": "0.0019", "benefit": "0.0038", "integr": "0.0113", "lose": "0.0094", "popular": "0.0019", "collaps": "0.0056", "crisi": "0.0075", "prevent": "0.0151", "confid": "0.0019", "slower": "0.0132", "shut": "0.0056", "slowdown": "0.0019", "strongest": "0.0019", "cost": "0.0113", "opportun": "0.0038", "fail": "0.0056", "close": "0.0151", "precipit": "0.0019", "concern": "0.0264", "lead": "0.0188", "profit": "0.0038", "defend": "0.0038", "abl": "0.0038", "bad": "0.0019", "favor": "0.0038", "restructur": "0.0038", "outstand": "0.0038", "deficit": "0.0019", "progress": "0.0038", "boost": "0.0094", "correct": "0.0019", "encourag": "0.0019", "investig": "0.0019", "advanc": "0.0301", "weak": "0.0019", "ban": "0.0038", "slow": "0.0169", "excess": "0.0038", "disput": "0.0056", "strong": "0.0113", "great": "0.0019", "deterior": "0.0019", "unemploy": "0.0019", "contract": "0.0169", "threat": "0.0019", "improv": "0.0056", "allianc": "0.0019", "suspend": "0.0075", "effici": "0.0019", "declin": "0.0452", "win": "0.0019", "bankruptci": "0.0056", "shortag": "0.0038", "cancel": "0.0056", "stabl": "0.0038", "miss": "0.0038", "drought": "0.0019", "damag": "0.0056", "bolster": "0.0019", "better": "0.0094", "question": "0.0019", "construct": "0.0094", "doubt": "0.0038", "downgrad": "0.0019", "threaten": "0.0038", "unexpect": "0.0075", "forc": "0.0075", "hurt": "0.0056", "warn": "0.0019", "gain": "0.1205", "termin": "0.0019", "eas": "0.0113", "highest": "0.0075", "fraud": "0.0019", "default": "0.0056", "seiz": "0.0056", "will": "0.0019", "limit": "0.0075", "posit": "0.0038", "problem": "0.0019", "claim": "0.0038", "weaker": "0.0019", "advantag": "0.0056", "strengthen": "0.0056", "challeng": "0.0038", "premier": "0.0019", "worri": "0.0075", "alleg": "0.0038", "critic": "0.0019", "attract": "0.0075", "sever": "0.0056", "halt": "0.0038", "strength": "0.0094", "delay": "0.0094", "fire": "0.0038", "boom": "0.0056", "reject": "0.0019", "weaken": "0.0113", "difficult": "0.0019", "tighten": "0.0113", "effect": "0.0075", "resign": "0.0019", "alert": "0.0019", "quit": "0.0019", "refin": "0.0151", "postpon": "0.0019", "stabil": "0.0075", "stress": "0.0019", "liquid": "0.0056", "antitrust": "0.0038", "stronger": "0.0019", "su": "0.0019", "inform": "0.0056", "deni": "0.0019", "achiev": "0.0019"}, "7": {"recess": "0.0029", "opposit": "0.0087", "lack": "0.0029", "protest": "0.0174", "surpass": "0.0029", "fear": "0.0058", "suffer": "0.0058", "fine": "0.0029", "accus": "0.0029", "cut": "0.0029", "depend": "0.0029", "except": "0.0029", "late": "0.0029", "arrest": "0.0029", "bailout": "0.0058", "volatil": "0.0029", "disrupt": "0.0029", "complaint": "0.0029", "good": "0.0058", "greater": "0.0029", "disclos": "0.0029", "rebound": "0.0116", "stop": "0.0029", "break": "0.0029", "worst": "0.0058", "know": "0.0029", "press": "0.0029", "loss": "0.0029", "bar": "0.0058", "success": "0.0029", "lost": "0.0087", "outperform": "0.0029", "drop": "0.0610", "negat": "0.0058", "resolv": "0.0029", "defens": "0.0029", "benefit": "0.0029", "integr": "0.0029", "lose": "0.0058", "popular": "0.0029", "collaps": "0.0029", "crisi": "0.0087", "prevent": "0.0058", "confid": "0.0029", "slower": "0.0029", "shut": "0.0029", "slowdown": "0.0029", "strongest": "0.0116", "cost": "0.0058", "opportun": "0.0029", "fail": "0.0029", "close": "0.0116", "precipit": "0.0029", "concern": "0.0262", "lead": "0.0407", "profit": "0.0145", "defend": "0.0029", "abl": "0.0029", "bad": "0.0029", "favor": "0.0087", "restructur": "0.0058", "outstand": "0.0029", "deficit": "0.0029", "progress": "0.0029", "boost": "0.0145", "correct": "0.0029", "encourag": "0.0029", "investig": "0.0029", "advanc": "0.0203", "weak": "0.0029", "ban": "0.0029", "slow": "0.0145", "excess": "0.0029", "disput": "0.0029", "strong": "0.0087", "great": "0.0029", "deterior": "0.0029", "unemploy": "0.0029", "contract": "0.0116", "threat": "0.0029", "improv": "0.0058", "allianc": "0.0029", "suspend": "0.0116", "effici": "0.0029", "declin": "0.0436", "win": "0.0058", "bankruptci": "0.0029", "shortag": "0.0029", "cancel": "0.0029", "stabl": "0.0029", "miss": "0.0029", "drought": "0.0029", "damag": "0.0029", "bolster": "0.0058", "better": "0.0029", "question": "0.0029", "construct": "0.0116", "doubt": "0.0029", "downgrad": "0.0029", "threaten": "0.0029", "unexpect": "0.0029", "forc": "0.0029", "hurt": "0.0029", "warn": "0.0029", "gain": "0.1105", "termin": "0.0029", "eas": "0.0116", "highest": "0.0203", "fraud": "0.0029", "default": "0.0029", "seiz": "0.0058", "will": "0.0058", "limit": "0.0145", "posit": "0.0145", "problem": "0.0029", "claim": "0.0029", "weaker": "0.0029", "advantag": "0.0029", "strengthen": "0.0145", "challeng": "0.0029", "premier": "0.0029", "worri": "0.0029", "alleg": "0.0058", "critic": "0.0029", "attract": "0.0029", "sever": "0.0029", "halt": "0.0058", "strength": "0.0029", "delay": "0.0087", "fire": "0.0029", "boom": "0.0058", "reject": "0.0058", "weaken": "0.0029", "difficult": "0.0029", "tighten": "0.0087", "effect": "0.0058", "resign": "0.0029", "alert": "0.0058", "quit": "0.0087", "refin": "0.0058", "postpon": "0.0058", "stabil": "0.0029", "stress": "0.0029", "liquid": "0.0029", "antitrust": "0.0029", "stronger": "0.0029", "su": "0.0029", "inform": "0.0029", "deni": "0.0029", "achiev": "0.0029"}, "8": {"recess": "0.0026", "opposit": "0.0026", "lack": "0.0052", "protest": "0.0026", "surpass": "0.0077", "fear": "0.0026", "suffer": "0.0026", "fine": "0.0026", "accus": "0.0026", "cut": "0.0155", "depend": "0.0103", "except": "0.0052", "late": "0.0077", "arrest": "0.0026", "bailout": "0.0026", "volatil": "0.0052", "disrupt": "0.0026", "complaint": "0.0052", "good": "0.0206", "greater": "0.0206", "disclos": "0.0026", "rebound": "0.0052", "stop": "0.0026", "break": "0.0026", "worst": "0.0026", "know": "0.0026", "press": "0.0026", "loss": "0.0052", "bar": "0.0026", "success": "0.0026", "lost": "0.0052", "outperform": "0.0026", "drop": "0.0619", "negat": "0.0026", "resolv": "0.0026", "defens": "0.0026", "benefit": "0.0052", "integr": "0.0155", "lose": "0.0052", "popular": "0.0026", "collaps": "0.0026", "crisi": "0.0077", "prevent": "0.0026", "confid": "0.0026", "slower": "0.0052", "shut": "0.0026", "slowdown": "0.0103", "strongest": "0.0052", "cost": "0.0284", "opportun": "0.0052", "fail": "0.0026", "close": "0.0103", "precipit": "0.0026", "concern": "0.0232", "lead": "0.0206", "profit": "0.0052", "defend": "0.0026", "abl": "0.0026", "bad": "0.0026", "favor": "0.0052", "restructur": "0.0052", "outstand": "0.0026", "deficit": "0.0052", "progress": "0.0052", "boost": "0.0103", "correct": "0.0052", "encourag": "0.0026", "investig": "0.0026", "advanc": "0.0284", "weak": "0.0052", "ban": "0.0026", "slow": "0.0232", "excess": "0.0026", "disput": "0.0052", "strong": "0.0026", "great": "0.0026", "deterior": "0.0026", "unemploy": "0.0052", "contract": "0.0052", "threat": "0.0026", "improv": "0.0026", "allianc": "0.0026", "suspend": "0.0026", "effici": "0.0026", "declin": "0.0412", "win": "0.0026", "bankruptci": "0.0077", "shortag": "0.0026", "cancel": "0.0052", "stabl": "0.0077", "miss": "0.0052", "drought": "0.0026", "damag": "0.0026", "bolster": "0.0052", "better": "0.0077", "question": "0.0026", "construct": "0.0103", "doubt": "0.0026", "downgrad": "0.0026", "threaten": "0.0052", "unexpect": "0.0077", "forc": "0.0026", "hurt": "0.0052", "warn": "0.0026", "gain": "0.0799", "termin": "0.0026", "eas": "0.0103", "highest": "0.0077", "fraud": "0.0026", "default": "0.0026", "seiz": "0.0052", "will": "0.0026", "limit": "0.0026", "posit": "0.0361", "problem": "0.0052", "claim": "0.0077", "weaker": "0.0026", "advantag": "0.0026", "strengthen": "0.0103", "challeng": "0.0026", "premier": "0.0026", "worri": "0.0026", "alleg": "0.0026", "critic": "0.0026", "attract": "0.0026", "sever": "0.0026", "halt": "0.0052", "strength": "0.0052", "delay": "0.0052", "fire": "0.0052", "boom": "0.0026", "reject": "0.0026", "weaken": "0.0077", "difficult": "0.0026", "tighten": "0.0026", "effect": "0.0077", "resign": "0.0026", "alert": "0.0052", "quit": "0.0026", "refin": "0.0103", "postpon": "0.0026", "stabil": "0.0077", "stress": "0.0026", "liquid": "0.0052", "antitrust": "0.0077", "stronger": "0.0052", "su": "0.0103", "inform": "0.0052", "deni": "0.0026", "achiev": "0.0026"}, "9": {"recess": "0.0049", "opposit": "0.0024", "lack": "0.0024", "protest": "0.0024", "surpass": "0.0024", "fear": "0.0024", "suffer": "0.0024", "fine": "0.0024", "accus": "0.0024", "cut": "0.0098", "depend": "0.0024", "except": "0.0024", "late": "0.0024", "arrest": "0.0024", "bailout": "0.0049", "volatil": "0.0024", "disrupt": "0.0024", "complaint": "0.0024", "good": "0.0146", "greater": "0.0024", "disclos": "0.0024", "rebound": "0.0073", "stop": "0.0024", "break": "0.0024", "worst": "0.0024", "know": "0.0024", "press": "0.0024", "loss": "0.0122", "bar": "0.0024", "success": "0.0024", "lost": "0.0073", "outperform": "0.0024", "drop": "0.0463", "negat": "0.0049", "resolv": "0.0024", "defens": "0.0024", "benefit": "0.0073", "integr": "0.0146", "lose": "0.0098", "popular": "0.0024", "collaps": "0.0024", "crisi": "0.0098", "prevent": "0.0049", "confid": "0.0024", "slower": "0.0049", "shut": "0.0049", "slowdown": "0.0049", "strongest": "0.0073", "cost": "0.0098", "opportun": "0.0024", "fail": "0.0049", "close": "0.0220", "precipit": "0.0024", "concern": "0.0244", "lead": "0.0244", "profit": "0.0268", "defend": "0.0024", "abl": "0.0073", "bad": "0.0049", "favor": "0.0049", "restructur": "0.0049", "outstand": "0.0049", "deficit": "0.0049", "progress": "0.0024", "boost": "0.0146", "correct": "0.0024", "encourag": "0.0049", "investig": "0.0024", "advanc": "0.0488", "weak": "0.0024", "ban": "0.0098", "slow": "0.0171", "excess": "0.0024", "disput": "0.0024", "strong": "0.0049", "great": "0.0049", "deterior": "0.0024", "unemploy": "0.0024", "contract": "0.0195", "threat": "0.0024", "improv": "0.0049", "allianc": "0.0024", "suspend": "0.0024", "effici": "0.0024", "declin": "0.0317", "win": "0.0049", "bankruptci": "0.0073", "shortag": "0.0024", "cancel": "0.0024", "stabl": "0.0024", "miss": "0.0024", "drought": "0.0073", "damag": "0.0024", "bolster": "0.0024", "better": "0.0049", "question": "0.0024", "construct": "0.0244", "doubt": "0.0024", "downgrad": "0.0024", "threaten": "0.0024", "unexpect": "0.0024", "forc": "0.0024", "hurt": "0.0024", "warn": "0.0024", "gain": "0.1390", "termin": "0.0049", "eas": "0.0146", "highest": "0.0098", "fraud": "0.0024", "default": "0.0049", "seiz": "0.0024", "will": "0.0024", "limit": "0.0049", "posit": "0.0049", "problem": "0.0024", "claim": "0.0049", "weaker": "0.0024", "advantag": "0.0049", "strengthen": "0.0024", "challeng": "0.0024", "premier": "0.0024", "worri": "0.0024", "alleg": "0.0049", "critic": "0.0049", "attract": "0.0073", "sever": "0.0049", "halt": "0.0049", "strength": "0.0024", "delay": "0.0024", "fire": "0.0024", "boom": "0.0024", "reject": "0.0049", "weaken": "0.0024", "difficult": "0.0024", "tighten": "0.0049", "effect": "0.0098", "resign": "0.0024", "alert": "0.0024", "quit": "0.0024", "refin": "0.0073", "postpon": "0.0049", "stabil": "0.0049", "stress": "0.0024", "liquid": "0.0024", "antitrust": "0.0024", "stronger": "0.0049", "su": "0.0024", "inform": "0.0024", "deni": "0.0024", "achiev": "0.0024"}, "10": {"recess": "0.0026", "opposit": "0.0013", "lack": "0.0013", "protest": "0.0039", "surpass": "0.0026", "fear": "0.0026", "suffer": "0.0013", "fine": "0.0013", "accus": "0.0013", "cut": "0.0118", "depend": "0.0053", "except": "0.0013", "late": "0.0053", "arrest": "0.0013", "bailout": "0.0039", "volatil": "0.0026", "disrupt": "0.0026", "complaint": "0.0013", "good": "0.0132", "greater": "0.0013", "disclos": "0.0026", "rebound": "0.0145", "stop": "0.0053", "break": "0.0013", "worst": "0.0013", "know": "0.0013", "press": "0.0039", "loss": "0.0053", "bar": "0.0013", "success": "0.0013", "lost": "0.0026", "outperform": "0.0013", "drop": "0.0487", "negat": "0.0026", "resolv": "0.0026", "defens": "0.0013", "benefit": "0.0066", "integr": "0.0026", "lose": "0.0039", "popular": "0.0013", "collaps": "0.0013", "crisi": "0.0092", "prevent": "0.0118", "confid": "0.0039", "slower": "0.0039", "shut": "0.0026", "slowdown": "0.0026", "strongest": "0.0118", "cost": "0.0237", "opportun": "0.0013", "fail": "0.0039", "close": "0.0276", "precipit": "0.0013", "concern": "0.0276", "lead": "0.0355", "profit": "0.0105", "defend": "0.0026", "abl": "0.0053", "bad": "0.0053", "favor": "0.0053", "restructur": "0.0013", "outstand": "0.0013", "deficit": "0.0053", "progress": "0.0013", "boost": "0.0224", "correct": "0.0013", "encourag": "0.0053", "investig": "0.0013", "advanc": "0.0408", "weak": "0.0013", "ban": "0.0053", "slow": "0.0158", "excess": "0.0039", "disput": "0.0026", "strong": "0.0171", "great": "0.0013", "deterior": "0.0013", "unemploy": "0.0013", "contract": "0.0026", "threat": "0.0039", "improv": "0.0079", "allianc": "0.0013", "suspend": "0.0039", "effici": "0.0013", "declin": "0.0526", "win": "0.0066", "bankruptci": "0.0053", "shortag": "0.0026", "cancel": "0.0013", "stabl": "0.0053", "miss": "0.0026", "drought": "0.0013", "damag": "0.0013", "bolster": "0.0026", "better": "0.0039", "question": "0.0013", "construct": "0.0250", "doubt": "0.0013", "downgrad": "0.0013", "threaten": "0.0026", "unexpect": "0.0066", "forc": "0.0079", "hurt": "0.0013", "warn": "0.0013", "gain": "0.1434", "termin": "0.0026", "eas": "0.0145", "highest": "0.0171", "fraud": "0.0013", "default": "0.0013", "seiz": "0.0053", "will": "0.0013", "limit": "0.0132", "posit": "0.0053", "problem": "0.0053", "claim": "0.0026", "weaker": "0.0026", "advantag": "0.0105", "strengthen": "0.0066", "challeng": "0.0039", "premier": "0.0013", "worri": "0.0026", "alleg": "0.0013", "critic": "0.0013", "attract": "0.0026", "sever": "0.0013", "halt": "0.0026", "strength": "0.0013", "delay": "0.0039", "fire": "0.0026", "boom": "0.0039", "reject": "0.0013", "weaken": "0.0066", "difficult": "0.0026", "tighten": "0.0066", "effect": "0.0026", "resign": "0.0013", "alert": "0.0039", "quit": "0.0039", "refin": "0.0092", "postpon": "0.0026", "stabil": "0.0026", "stress": "0.0013", "liquid": "0.0079", "antitrust": "0.0026", "stronger": "0.0026", "su": "0.0013", "inform": "0.0092", "deni": "0.0039", "achiev": "0.0026"}, "11": {"recess": "0.0054", "opposit": "0.0027", "lack": "0.0014", "protest": "0.0176", "surpass": "0.0041", "fear": "0.0027", "suffer": "0.0014", "fine": "0.0014", "accus": "0.0014", "cut": "0.0203", "depend": "0.0041", "except": "0.0014", "late": "0.0054", "arrest": "0.0014", "bailout": "0.0041", "volatil": "0.0014", "disrupt": "0.0014", "complaint": "0.0014", "good": "0.0095", "greater": "0.0054", "disclos": "0.0054", "rebound": "0.0149", "stop": "0.0027", "break": "0.0014", "worst": "0.0027", "know": "0.0014", "press": "0.0095", "loss": "0.0014", "bar": "0.0014", "success": "0.0014", "lost": "0.0054", "outperform": "0.0027", "drop": "0.0582", "negat": "0.0027", "resolv": "0.0014", "defens": "0.0014", "benefit": "0.0027", "integr": "0.0095", "lose": "0.0027", "popular": "0.0014", "collaps": "0.0014", "crisi": "0.0149", "prevent": "0.0041", "confid": "0.0041", "slower": "0.0041", "shut": "0.0054", "slowdown": "0.0014", "strongest": "0.0027", "cost": "0.0284", "opportun": "0.0068", "fail": "0.0041", "close": "0.0054", "precipit": "0.0014", "concern": "0.0271", "lead": "0.0257", "profit": "0.0095", "defend": "0.0041", "abl": "0.0027", "bad": "0.0027", "favor": "0.0054", "restructur": "0.0014", "outstand": "0.0041", "deficit": "0.0108", "progress": "0.0014", "boost": "0.0176", "correct": "0.0041", "encourag": "0.0027", "investig": "0.0014", "advanc": "0.0271", "weak": "0.0014", "ban": "0.0014", "slow": "0.0217", "excess": "0.0014", "disput": "0.0041", "strong": "0.0095", "great": "0.0014", "deterior": "0.0014", "unemploy": "0.0027", "contract": "0.0108", "threat": "0.0014", "improv": "0.0054", "allianc": "0.0014", "suspend": "0.0054", "effici": "0.0027", "declin": "0.0609", "win": "0.0027", "bankruptci": "0.0041", "shortag": "0.0014", "cancel": "0.0027", "stabl": "0.0095", "miss": "0.0014", "drought": "0.0014", "damag": "0.0041", "bolster": "0.0041", "better": "0.0014", "question": "0.0041", "construct": "0.0203", "doubt": "0.0041", "downgrad": "0.0014", "threaten": "0.0054", "unexpect": "0.0081", "forc": "0.0041", "hurt": "0.0027", "warn": "0.0014", "gain": "0.1421", "termin": "0.0014", "eas": "0.0108", "highest": "0.0054", "fraud": "0.0014", "default": "0.0027", "seiz": "0.0054", "will": "0.0014", "limit": "0.0068", "posit": "0.0081", "problem": "0.0054", "claim": "0.0014", "weaker": "0.0014", "advantag": "0.0027", "strengthen": "0.0122", "challeng": "0.0041", "premier": "0.0014", "worri": "0.0041", "alleg": "0.0014", "critic": "0.0014", "attract": "0.0081", "sever": "0.0027", "halt": "0.0054", "strength": "0.0014", "delay": "0.0054", "fire": "0.0041", "boom": "0.0014", "reject": "0.0027", "weaken": "0.0068", "difficult": "0.0027", "tighten": "0.0068", "effect": "0.0068", "resign": "0.0014", "alert": "0.0041", "quit": "0.0041", "refin": "0.0122", "postpon": "0.0014", "stabil": "0.0014", "stress": "0.0014", "liquid": "0.0135", "antitrust": "0.0014", "stronger": "0.0014", "su": "0.0014", "inform": "0.0081", "deni": "0.0014", "achiev": "0.0014"}, "12": {"recess": "0.0018", "opposit": "0.0125", "lack": "0.0054", "protest": "0.0107", "surpass": "0.0036", "fear": "0.0072", "suffer": "0.0018", "fine": "0.0018", "accus": "0.0107", "cut": "0.0268", "depend": "0.0036", "except": "0.0018", "late": "0.0036", "arrest": "0.0018", "bailout": "0.0018", "volatil": "0.0036", "disrupt": "0.0018", "complaint": "0.0018", "good": "0.0036", "greater": "0.0072", "disclos": "0.0018", "rebound": "0.0143", "stop": "0.0018", "break": "0.0018", "worst": "0.0018", "know": "0.0054", "press": "0.0018", "loss": "0.0072", "bar": "0.0018", "success": "0.0036", "lost": "0.0233", "outperform": "0.0018", "drop": "0.0894", "negat": "0.0054", "resolv": "0.0036", "defens": "0.0018", "benefit": "0.0107", "integr": "0.0018", "lose": "0.0143", "popular": "0.0018", "collaps": "0.0107", "crisi": "0.0036", "prevent": "0.0072", "confid": "0.0018", "slower": "0.0036", "shut": "0.0018", "slowdown": "0.0018", "strongest": "0.0036", "cost": "0.0161", "opportun": "0.0018", "fail": "0.0072", "close": "0.0107", "precipit": "0.0018", "concern": "0.0358", "lead": "0.0340", "profit": "0.0036", "defend": "0.0072", "abl": "0.0018", "bad": "0.0018", "favor": "0.0054", "restructur": "0.0018", "outstand": "0.0018", "deficit": "0.0072", "progress": "0.0072", "boost": "0.0072", "correct": "0.0036", "encourag": "0.0036", "investig": "0.0018", "advanc": "0.0143", "weak": "0.0018", "ban": "0.0036", "slow": "0.0107", "excess": "0.0036", "disput": "0.0018", "strong": "0.0089", "great": "0.0054", "deterior": "0.0018", "unemploy": "0.0036", "contract": "0.0143", "threat": "0.0018", "improv": "0.0036", "allianc": "0.0036", "suspend": "0.0125", "effici": "0.0018", "declin": "0.0662", "win": "0.0161", "bankruptci": "0.0018", "shortag": "0.0036", "cancel": "0.0018", "stabl": "0.0018", "miss": "0.0018", "drought": "0.0018", "damag": "0.0036", "bolster": "0.0018", "better": "0.0036", "question": "0.0054", "construct": "0.0036", "doubt": "0.0072", "downgrad": "0.0018", "threaten": "0.0018", "unexpect": "0.0089", "forc": "0.0054", "hurt": "0.0018", "warn": "0.0054", "gain": "0.0501", "termin": "0.0018", "eas": "0.0018", "highest": "0.0107", "fraud": "0.0018", "default": "0.0072", "seiz": "0.0125", "will": "0.0018", "limit": "0.0072", "posit": "0.0072", "problem": "0.0054", "claim": "0.0250", "weaker": "0.0018", "advantag": "0.0036", "strengthen": "0.0089", "challeng": "0.0018", "premier": "0.0018", "worri": "0.0054", "alleg": "0.0018", "critic": "0.0018", "attract": "0.0036", "sever": "0.0036", "halt": "0.0036", "strength": "0.0054", "delay": "0.0072", "fire": "0.0018", "boom": "0.0197", "reject": "0.0054", "weaken": "0.0036", "difficult": "0.0054", "tighten": "0.0054", "effect": "0.0018", "resign": "0.0018", "alert": "0.0036", "quit": "0.0018", "refin": "0.0036", "postpon": "0.0018", "stabil": "0.0036", "stress": "0.0018", "liquid": "0.0018", "antitrust": "0.0018", "stronger": "0.0018", "su": "0.0036", "inform": "0.0036", "deni": "0.0018", "achiev": "0.0018"}, "13": {"recess": "0.0054", "opposit": "0.0054", "lack": "0.0054", "protest": "0.0054", "surpass": "0.0054", "fear": "0.0054", "suffer": "0.0054", "fine": "0.0054", "accus": "0.0054", "cut": "0.0054", "depend": "0.0054", "except": "0.0054", "late": "0.0054", "arrest": "0.0054", "bailout": "0.0054", "volatil": "0.0054", "disrupt": "0.0054", "complaint": "0.0054", "good": "0.0054", "greater": "0.0054", "disclos": "0.0054", "rebound": "0.0108", "stop": "0.0054", "break": "0.0054", "worst": "0.0054", "know": "0.0054", "press": "0.0054", "loss": "0.0054", "bar": "0.0054", "success": "0.0108", "lost": "0.0054", "outperform": "0.0054", "drop": "0.0324", "negat": "0.0054", "resolv": "0.0054", "defens": "0.0054", "benefit": "0.0054", "integr": "0.0324", "lose": "0.0054", "popular": "0.0054", "collaps": "0.0054", "crisi": "0.0054", "prevent": "0.0054", "confid": "0.0054", "slower": "0.0108", "shut": "0.0054", "slowdown": "0.0054", "strongest": "0.0054", "cost": "0.0054", "opportun": "0.0054", "fail": "0.0054", "close": "0.0108", "precipit": "0.0054", "concern": "0.0054", "lead": "0.0054", "profit": "0.0054", "defend": "0.0054", "abl": "0.0054", "bad": "0.0054", "favor": "0.0054", "restructur": "0.0054", "outstand": "0.0054", "deficit": "0.0054", "progress": "0.0054", "boost": "0.0054", "correct": "0.0054", "encourag": "0.0054", "investig": "0.0054", "advanc": "0.0216", "weak": "0.0054", "ban": "0.0054", "slow": "0.0108", "excess": "0.0054", "disput": "0.0054", "strong": "0.0108", "great": "0.0054", "deterior": "0.0054", "unemploy": "0.0054", "contract": "0.0054", "threat": "0.0054", "improv": "0.0054", "allianc": "0.0054", "suspend": "0.0054", "effici": "0.0054", "declin": "0.0216", "win": "0.0054", "bankruptci": "0.0054", "shortag": "0.0054", "cancel": "0.0054", "stabl": "0.0054", "miss": "0.0054", "drought": "0.0054", "damag": "0.0054", "bolster": "0.0054", "better": "0.0054", "question": "0.0054", "construct": "0.0108", "doubt": "0.0054", "downgrad": "0.0054", "threaten": "0.0054", "unexpect": "0.0054", "forc": "0.0054", "hurt": "0.0054", "warn": "0.0054", "gain": "0.0649", "termin": "0.0054", "eas": "0.0054", "highest": "0.0054", "fraud": "0.0054", "default": "0.0054", "seiz": "0.0054", "will": "0.0054", "limit": "0.0054", "posit": "0.0054", "problem": "0.0054", "claim": "0.0054", "weaker": "0.0054", "advantag": "0.0054", "strengthen": "0.0054", "challeng": "0.0054", "premier": "0.0054", "worri": "0.0054", "alleg": "0.0054", "critic": "0.0054", "attract": "0.0054", "sever": "0.0054", "halt": "0.0054", "strength": "0.0054", "delay": "0.0054", "fire": "0.0054", "boom": "0.0054", "reject": "0.0054", "weaken": "0.0054", "difficult": "0.0054", "tighten": "0.0054", "effect": "0.0054", "resign": "0.0054", "alert": "0.0054", "quit": "0.0054", "refin": "0.0108", "postpon": "0.0054", "stabil": "0.0054", "stress": "0.0054", "liquid": "0.0054", "antitrust": "0.0054", "stronger": "0.0054", "su": "0.0054", "inform": "0.0054", "deni": "0.0054", "achiev": "0.0054"}, "14": {"recess": "0.0029", "opposit": "0.0057", "lack": "0.0057", "protest": "0.0057", "surpass": "0.0029", "fear": "0.0029", "suffer": "0.0029", "fine": "0.0029", "accus": "0.0029", "cut": "0.0057", "depend": "0.0029", "except": "0.0029", "late": "0.0057", "arrest": "0.0029", "bailout": "0.0086", "volatil": "0.0115", "disrupt": "0.0057", "complaint": "0.0029", "good": "0.0086", "greater": "0.0029", "disclos": "0.0029", "rebound": "0.0115", "stop": "0.0057", "break": "0.0029", "worst": "0.0057", "know": "0.0029", "press": "0.0057", "loss": "0.0057", "bar": "0.0029", "success": "0.0029", "lost": "0.0057", "outperform": "0.0029", "drop": "0.0747", "negat": "0.0086", "resolv": "0.0029", "defens": "0.0029", "benefit": "0.0057", "integr": "0.0029", "lose": "0.0144", "popular": "0.0029", "collaps": "0.0029", "crisi": "0.0144", "prevent": "0.0057", "confid": "0.0029", "slower": "0.0057", "shut": "0.0029", "slowdown": "0.0057", "strongest": "0.0057", "cost": "0.0029", "opportun": "0.0029", "fail": "0.0029", "close": "0.0172", "precipit": "0.0029", "concern": "0.0172", "lead": "0.0144", "profit": "0.0115", "defend": "0.0029", "abl": "0.0029", "bad": "0.0029", "favor": "0.0029", "restructur": "0.0029", "outstand": "0.0057", "deficit": "0.0057", "progress": "0.0029", "boost": "0.0144", "correct": "0.0057", "encourag": "0.0029", "investig": "0.0029", "advanc": "0.0431", "weak": "0.0029", "ban": "0.0029", "slow": "0.0115", "excess": "0.0029", "disput": "0.0029", "strong": "0.0029", "great": "0.0029", "deterior": "0.0029", "unemploy": "0.0029", "contract": "0.0144", "threat": "0.0029", "improv": "0.0029", "allianc": "0.0029", "suspend": "0.0057", "effici": "0.0029", "declin": "0.0431", "win": "0.0029", "bankruptci": "0.0029", "shortag": "0.0172", "cancel": "0.0057", "stabl": "0.0057", "miss": "0.0057", "drought": "0.0029", "damag": "0.0029", "bolster": "0.0029", "better": "0.0029", "question": "0.0029", "construct": "0.0144", "doubt": "0.0029", "downgrad": "0.0029", "threaten": "0.0029", "unexpect": "0.0029", "forc": "0.0086", "hurt": "0.0029", "warn": "0.0029", "gain": "0.0833", "termin": "0.0029", "eas": "0.0086", "highest": "0.0144", "fraud": "0.0029", "default": "0.0029", "seiz": "0.0029", "will": "0.0057", "limit": "0.0144", "posit": "0.0086", "problem": "0.0029", "claim": "0.0029", "weaker": "0.0029", "advantag": "0.0057", "strengthen": "0.0057", "challeng": "0.0029", "premier": "0.0029", "worri": "0.0029", "alleg": "0.0029", "critic": "0.0029", "attract": "0.0029", "sever": "0.0029", "halt": "0.0057", "strength": "0.0029", "delay": "0.0029", "fire": "0.0029", "boom": "0.0057", "reject": "0.0115", "weaken": "0.0230", "difficult": "0.0029", "tighten": "0.0086", "effect": "0.0029", "resign": "0.0029", "alert": "0.0029", "quit": "0.0029", "refin": "0.0115", "postpon": "0.0029", "stabil": "0.0029", "stress": "0.0029", "liquid": "0.0086", "antitrust": "0.0029", "stronger": "0.0029", "su": "0.0029", "inform": "0.0057", "deni": "0.0029", "achiev": "0.0029"}, "15": {"recess": "0.0039", "opposit": "0.0059", "lack": "0.0039", "protest": "0.0020", "surpass": "0.0020", "fear": "0.0020", "suffer": "0.0020", "fine": "0.0020", "accus": "0.0020", "cut": "0.0118", "depend": "0.0020", "except": "0.0039", "late": "0.0079", "arrest": "0.0020", "bailout": "0.0039", "volatil": "0.0059", "disrupt": "0.0039", "complaint": "0.0039", "good": "0.0138", "greater": "0.0039", "disclos": "0.0020", "rebound": "0.0157", "stop": "0.0039", "break": "0.0059", "worst": "0.0039", "know": "0.0020", "press": "0.0020", "loss": "0.0079", "bar": "0.0059", "success": "0.0020", "lost": "0.0059", "outperform": "0.0020", "drop": "0.0688", "negat": "0.0039", "resolv": "0.0020", "defens": "0.0020", "benefit": "0.0039", "integr": "0.0039", "lose": "0.0059", "popular": "0.0020", "collaps": "0.0039", "crisi": "0.0098", "prevent": "0.0079", "confid": "0.0020", "slower": "0.0039", "shut": "0.0039", "slowdown": "0.0020", "strongest": "0.0098", "cost": "0.0275", "opportun": "0.0020", "fail": "0.0020", "close": "0.0118", "precipit": "0.0020", "concern": "0.0196", "lead": "0.0275", "profit": "0.0138", "defend": "0.0020", "abl": "0.0020", "bad": "0.0039", "favor": "0.0039", "restructur": "0.0020", "outstand": "0.0020", "deficit": "0.0059", "progress": "0.0020", "boost": "0.0177", "correct": "0.0020", "encourag": "0.0020", "investig": "0.0020", "advanc": "0.0432", "weak": "0.0020", "ban": "0.0020", "slow": "0.0157", "excess": "0.0020", "disput": "0.0039", "strong": "0.0059", "great": "0.0039", "deterior": "0.0020", "unemploy": "0.0059", "contract": "0.0138", "threat": "0.0020", "improv": "0.0039", "allianc": "0.0020", "suspend": "0.0079", "effici": "0.0020", "declin": "0.0413", "win": "0.0039", "bankruptci": "0.0039", "shortag": "0.0039", "cancel": "0.0020", "stabl": "0.0059", "miss": "0.0079", "drought": "0.0020", "damag": "0.0039", "bolster": "0.0059", "better": "0.0039", "question": "0.0020", "construct": "0.0196", "doubt": "0.0020", "downgrad": "0.0020", "threaten": "0.0020", "unexpect": "0.0039", "forc": "0.0059", "hurt": "0.0039", "warn": "0.0020", "gain": "0.1375", "termin": "0.0020", "eas": "0.0098", "highest": "0.0138", "fraud": "0.0020", "default": "0.0059", "seiz": "0.0020", "will": "0.0039", "limit": "0.0059", "posit": "0.0039", "problem": "0.0059", "claim": "0.0079", "weaker": "0.0020", "advantag": "0.0059", "strengthen": "0.0138", "challeng": "0.0020", "premier": "0.0020", "worri": "0.0020", "alleg": "0.0039", "critic": "0.0020", "attract": "0.0020", "sever": "0.0020", "halt": "0.0020", "strength": "0.0020", "delay": "0.0020", "fire": "0.0020", "boom": "0.0039", "reject": "0.0020", "weaken": "0.0079", "difficult": "0.0020", "tighten": "0.0039", "effect": "0.0039", "resign": "0.0020", "alert": "0.0020", "quit": "0.0059", "refin": "0.0098", "postpon": "0.0020", "stabil": "0.0039", "stress": "0.0020", "liquid": "0.0020", "antitrust": "0.0020", "stronger": "0.0020", "su": "0.0079", "inform": "0.0039", "deni": "0.0020", "achiev": "0.0020"}, "16": {"recess": "0.0058", "opposit": "0.0135", "lack": "0.0019", "protest": "0.0058", "surpass": "0.0039", "fear": "0.0039", "suffer": "0.0019", "fine": "0.0019", "accus": "0.0019", "cut": "0.0155", "depend": "0.0019", "except": "0.0039", "late": "0.0077", "arrest": "0.0019", "bailout": "0.0019", "volatil": "0.0039", "disrupt": "0.0039", "complaint": "0.0019", "good": "0.0116", "greater": "0.0116", "disclos": "0.0019", "rebound": "0.0135", "stop": "0.0058", "break": "0.0019", "worst": "0.0058", "know": "0.0019", "press": "0.0019", "loss": "0.0058", "bar": "0.0019", "success": "0.0019", "lost": "0.0097", "outperform": "0.0019", "drop": "0.0851", "negat": "0.0058", "resolv": "0.0019", "defens": "0.0019", "benefit": "0.0077", "integr": "0.0077", "lose": "0.0174", "popular": "0.0058", "collaps": "0.0019", "crisi": "0.0058", "prevent": "0.0116", "confid": "0.0039", "slower": "0.0019", "shut": "0.0019", "slowdown": "0.0019", "strongest": "0.0058", "cost": "0.0155", "opportun": "0.0019", "fail": "0.0077", "close": "0.0251", "precipit": "0.0019", "concern": "0.0213", "lead": "0.0271", "profit": "0.0077", "defend": "0.0019", "abl": "0.0019", "bad": "0.0039", "favor": "0.0058", "restructur": "0.0019", "outstand": "0.0039", "deficit": "0.0058", "progress": "0.0039", "boost": "0.0135", "correct": "0.0019", "encourag": "0.0019", "investig": "0.0019", "advanc": "0.0271", "weak": "0.0019", "ban": "0.0058", "slow": "0.0155", "excess": "0.0019", "disput": "0.0019", "strong": "0.0077", "great": "0.0039", "deterior": "0.0019", "unemploy": "0.0019", "contract": "0.0135", "threat": "0.0019", "improv": "0.0058", "allianc": "0.0019", "suspend": "0.0039", "effici": "0.0019", "declin": "0.0522", "win": "0.0097", "bankruptci": "0.0019", "shortag": "0.0058", "cancel": "0.0019", "stabl": "0.0019", "miss": "0.0019", "drought": "0.0019", "damag": "0.0019", "bolster": "0.0039", "better": "0.0019", "question": "0.0039", "construct": "0.0116", "doubt": "0.0039", "downgrad": "0.0019", "threaten": "0.0019", "unexpect": "0.0077", "forc": "0.0077", "hurt": "0.0019", "warn": "0.0019", "gain": "0.0967", "termin": "0.0019", "eas": "0.0077", "highest": "0.0193", "fraud": "0.0019", "default": "0.0058", "seiz": "0.0058", "will": "0.0019", "limit": "0.0058", "posit": "0.0116", "problem": "0.0097", "claim": "0.0019", "weaker": "0.0019", "advantag": "0.0039", "strengthen": "0.0058", "challeng": "0.0019", "premier": "0.0019", "worri": "0.0019", "alleg": "0.0019", "critic": "0.0039", "attract": "0.0019", "sever": "0.0019", "halt": "0.0019", "strength": "0.0019", "delay": "0.0019", "fire": "0.0019", "boom": "0.0077", "reject": "0.0058", "weaken": "0.0077", "difficult": "0.0039", "tighten": "0.0039", "effect": "0.0019", "resign": "0.0019", "alert": "0.0019", "quit": "0.0058", "refin": "0.0116", "postpon": "0.0019", "stabil": "0.0077", "stress": "0.0019", "liquid": "0.0039", "antitrust": "0.0019", "stronger": "0.0039", "su": "0.0019", "inform": "0.0039", "deni": "0.0019", "achiev": "0.0019"}, "17": {"recess": "0.0019", "opposit": "0.0074", "lack": "0.0074", "protest": "0.0037", "surpass": "0.0019", "fear": "0.0019", "suffer": "0.0019", "fine": "0.0019", "accus": "0.0019", "cut": "0.0074", "depend": "0.0019", "except": "0.0019", "late": "0.0074", "arrest": "0.0019", "bailout": "0.0093", "volatil": "0.0167", "disrupt": "0.0019", "complaint": "0.0019", "good": "0.0111", "greater": "0.0093", "disclos": "0.0056", "rebound": "0.0167", "stop": "0.0037", "break": "0.0019", "worst": "0.0019", "know": "0.0019", "press": "0.0056", "loss": "0.0037", "bar": "0.0037", "success": "0.0019", "lost": "0.0056", "outperform": "0.0019", "drop": "0.0537", "negat": "0.0037", "resolv": "0.0019", "defens": "0.0019", "benefit": "0.0037", "integr": "0.0019", "lose": "0.0056", "popular": "0.0019", "collaps": "0.0019", "crisi": "0.0148", "prevent": "0.0185", "confid": "0.0019", "slower": "0.0019", "shut": "0.0037", "slowdown": "0.0019", "strongest": "0.0093", "cost": "0.0222", "opportun": "0.0037", "fail": "0.0037", "close": "0.0130", "precipit": "0.0019", "concern": "0.0130", "lead": "0.0222", "profit": "0.0093", "defend": "0.0019", "abl": "0.0019", "bad": "0.0019", "favor": "0.0019", "restructur": "0.0019", "outstand": "0.0037", "deficit": "0.0074", "progress": "0.0019", "boost": "0.0241", "correct": "0.0019", "encourag": "0.0019", "investig": "0.0019", "advanc": "0.0407", "weak": "0.0019", "ban": "0.0019", "slow": "0.0111", "excess": "0.0019", "disput": "0.0037", "strong": "0.0093", "great": "0.0019", "deterior": "0.0019", "unemploy": "0.0019", "contract": "0.0130", "threat": "0.0056", "improv": "0.0019", "allianc": "0.0019", "suspend": "0.0019", "effici": "0.0019", "declin": "0.0796", "win": "0.0037", "bankruptci": "0.0019", "shortag": "0.0019", "cancel": "0.0037", "stabl": "0.0093", "miss": "0.0037", "drought": "0.0019", "damag": "0.0019", "bolster": "0.0019", "better": "0.0019", "question": "0.0019", "construct": "0.0241", "doubt": "0.0019", "downgrad": "0.0019", "threaten": "0.0019", "unexpect": "0.0037", "forc": "0.0056", "hurt": "0.0019", "warn": "0.0019", "gain": "0.1333", "termin": "0.0019", "eas": "0.0019", "highest": "0.0056", "fraud": "0.0019", "default": "0.0037", "seiz": "0.0019", "will": "0.0056", "limit": "0.0111", "posit": "0.0093", "problem": "0.0019", "claim": "0.0019", "weaker": "0.0056", "advantag": "0.0056", "strengthen": "0.0093", "challeng": "0.0019", "premier": "0.0019", "worri": "0.0019", "alleg": "0.0037", "critic": "0.0019", "attract": "0.0019", "sever": "0.0019", "halt": "0.0037", "strength": "0.0019", "delay": "0.0037", "fire": "0.0019", "boom": "0.0056", "reject": "0.0019", "weaken": "0.0074", "difficult": "0.0037", "tighten": "0.0037", "effect": "0.0056", "resign": "0.0019", "alert": "0.0056", "quit": "0.0037", "refin": "0.0222", "postpon": "0.0019", "stabil": "0.0037", "stress": "0.0019", "liquid": "0.0056", "antitrust": "0.0019", "stronger": "0.0019", "su": "0.0019", "inform": "0.0111", "deni": "0.0019", "achiev": "0.0019"}, "18": {"recess": "0.0018", "opposit": "0.0090", "lack": "0.0072", "protest": "0.0108", "surpass": "0.0054", "fear": "0.0072", "suffer": "0.0018", "fine": "0.0018", "accus": "0.0090", "cut": "0.0180", "depend": "0.0036", "except": "0.0018", "late": "0.0036", "arrest": "0.0018", "bailout": "0.0054", "volatil": "0.0108", "disrupt": "0.0018", "complaint": "0.0018", "good": "0.0054", "greater": "0.0144", "disclos": "0.0018", "rebound": "0.0144", "stop": "0.0036", "break": "0.0018", "worst": "0.0018", "know": "0.0054", "press": "0.0018", "loss": "0.0072", "bar": "0.0018", "success": "0.0036", "lost": "0.0233", "outperform": "0.0036", "drop": "0.0539", "negat": "0.0072", "resolv": "0.0036", "defens": "0.0018", "benefit": "0.0090", "integr": "0.0144", "lose": "0.0072", "popular": "0.0018", "collaps": "0.0090", "crisi": "0.0090", "prevent": "0.0072", "confid": "0.0018", "slower": "0.0036", "shut": "0.0036", "slowdown": "0.0018", "strongest": "0.0036", "cost": "0.0180", "opportun": "0.0018", "fail": "0.0054", "close": "0.0108", "precipit": "0.0018", "concern": "0.0233", "lead": "0.0305", "profit": "0.0036", "defend": "0.0072", "abl": "0.0036", "bad": "0.0018", "favor": "0.0036", "restructur": "0.0018", "outstand": "0.0018", "deficit": "0.0036", "progress": "0.0072", "boost": "0.0072", "correct": "0.0018", "encourag": "0.0036", "investig": "0.0018", "advanc": "0.0162", "weak": "0.0018", "ban": "0.0036", "slow": "0.0090", "excess": "0.0072", "disput": "0.0018", "strong": "0.0072", "great": "0.0054", "deterior": "0.0018", "unemploy": "0.0036", "contract": "0.0180", "threat": "0.0036", "improv": "0.0054", "allianc": "0.0072", "suspend": "0.0144", "effici": "0.0018", "declin": "0.0521", "win": "0.0108", "bankruptci": "0.0018", "shortag": "0.0036", "cancel": "0.0018", "stabl": "0.0018", "miss": "0.0018", "drought": "0.0018", "damag": "0.0036", "bolster": "0.0018", "better": "0.0036", "question": "0.0054", "construct": "0.0036", "doubt": "0.0054", "downgrad": "0.0018", "threaten": "0.0018", "unexpect": "0.0036", "forc": "0.0054", "hurt": "0.0018", "warn": "0.0036", "gain": "0.0592", "termin": "0.0018", "eas": "0.0018", "highest": "0.0108", "fraud": "0.0018", "default": "0.0072", "seiz": "0.0108", "will": "0.0036", "limit": "0.0126", "posit": "0.0036", "problem": "0.0072", "claim": "0.0251", "weaker": "0.0018", "advantag": "0.0054", "strengthen": "0.0072", "challeng": "0.0018", "premier": "0.0018", "worri": "0.0054", "alleg": "0.0018", "critic": "0.0018", "attract": "0.0126", "sever": "0.0072", "halt": "0.0036", "strength": "0.0036", "delay": "0.0090", "fire": "0.0018", "boom": "0.0180", "reject": "0.0036", "weaken": "0.0108", "difficult": "0.0054", "tighten": "0.0036", "effect": "0.0018", "resign": "0.0018", "alert": "0.0018", "quit": "0.0018", "refin": "0.0054", "postpon": "0.0018", "stabil": "0.0072", "stress": "0.0018", "liquid": "0.0144", "antitrust": "0.0018", "stronger": "0.0018", "su": "0.0036", "inform": "0.0054", "deni": "0.0018", "achiev": "0.0018"}, "19": {"recess": "0.0085", "opposit": "0.0042", "lack": "0.0021", "protest": "0.0064", "surpass": "0.0085", "fear": "0.0042", "suffer": "0.0021", "fine": "0.0021", "accus": "0.0021", "cut": "0.0191", "depend": "0.0042", "except": "0.0042", "late": "0.0064", "arrest": "0.0021", "bailout": "0.0085", "volatil": "0.0021", "disrupt": "0.0021", "complaint": "0.0021", "good": "0.0148", "greater": "0.0064", "disclos": "0.0064", "rebound": "0.0106", "stop": "0.0042", "break": "0.0021", "worst": "0.0021", "know": "0.0021", "press": "0.0169", "loss": "0.0064", "bar": "0.0021", "success": "0.0021", "lost": "0.0064", "outperform": "0.0042", "drop": "0.0339", "negat": "0.0021", "resolv": "0.0021", "defens": "0.0021", "benefit": "0.0021", "integr": "0.0148", "lose": "0.0021", "popular": "0.0021", "collaps": "0.0021", "crisi": "0.0233", "prevent": "0.0042", "confid": "0.0064", "slower": "0.0021", "shut": "0.0064", "slowdown": "0.0021", "strongest": "0.0021", "cost": "0.0381", "opportun": "0.0106", "fail": "0.0042", "close": "0.0021", "precipit": "0.0021", "concern": "0.0275", "lead": "0.0191", "profit": "0.0042", "defend": "0.0042", "abl": "0.0042", "bad": "0.0021", "favor": "0.0064", "restructur": "0.0021", "outstand": "0.0064", "deficit": "0.0106", "progress": "0.0021", "boost": "0.0360", "correct": "0.0042", "encourag": "0.0064", "investig": "0.0021", "advanc": "0.0085", "weak": "0.0021", "ban": "0.0021", "slow": "0.0148", "excess": "0.0021", "disput": "0.0042", "strong": "0.0106", "great": "0.0021", "deterior": "0.0021", "unemploy": "0.0042", "contract": "0.0106", "threat": "0.0021", "improv": "0.0106", "allianc": "0.0021", "suspend": "0.0021", "effici": "0.0042", "declin": "0.0593", "win": "0.0042", "bankruptci": "0.0021", "shortag": "0.0021", "cancel": "0.0021", "stabl": "0.0106", "miss": "0.0021", "drought": "0.0021", "damag": "0.0042", "bolster": "0.0021", "better": "0.0042", "question": "0.0042", "construct": "0.0191", "doubt": "0.0064", "downgrad": "0.0021", "threaten": "0.0148", "unexpect": "0.0064", "forc": "0.0042", "hurt": "0.0021", "warn": "0.0021", "gain": "0.0508", "termin": "0.0021", "eas": "0.0085", "highest": "0.0085", "fraud": "0.0021", "default": "0.0021", "seiz": "0.0064", "will": "0.0021", "limit": "0.0021", "posit": "0.0085", "problem": "0.0021", "claim": "0.0021", "weaker": "0.0021", "advantag": "0.0085", "strengthen": "0.0127", "challeng": "0.0042", "premier": "0.0021", "worri": "0.0042", "alleg": "0.0021", "critic": "0.0021", "attract": "0.0085", "sever": "0.0042", "halt": "0.0021", "strength": "0.0021", "delay": "0.0021", "fire": "0.0042", "boom": "0.0021", "reject": "0.0021", "weaken": "0.0042", "difficult": "0.0042", "tighten": "0.0085", "effect": "0.0085", "resign": "0.0021", "alert": "0.0085", "quit": "0.0064", "refin": "0.0127", "postpon": "0.0021", "stabil": "0.0021", "stress": "0.0021", "liquid": "0.0191", "antitrust": "0.0021", "stronger": "0.0042", "su": "0.0021", "inform": "0.0169", "deni": "0.0021", "achiev": "0.0042"}, "20": {"recess": "0.0021", "opposit": "0.0042", "lack": "0.0021", "protest": "0.0062", "surpass": "0.0021", "fear": "0.0062", "suffer": "0.0042", "fine": "0.0021", "accus": "0.0021", "cut": "0.0042", "depend": "0.0042", "except": "0.0042", "late": "0.0042", "arrest": "0.0021", "bailout": "0.0021", "volatil": "0.0083", "disrupt": "0.0021", "complaint": "0.0021", "good": "0.0125", "greater": "0.0062", "disclos": "0.0021", "rebound": "0.0062", "stop": "0.0021", "break": "0.0021", "worst": "0.0042", "know": "0.0042", "press": "0.0021", "loss": "0.0062", "bar": "0.0042", "success": "0.0021", "lost": "0.0062", "outperform": "0.0021", "drop": "0.0832", "negat": "0.0042", "resolv": "0.0021", "defens": "0.0021", "benefit": "0.0021", "integr": "0.0021", "lose": "0.0125", "popular": "0.0021", "collaps": "0.0021", "crisi": "0.0125", "prevent": "0.0104", "confid": "0.0042", "slower": "0.0042", "shut": "0.0062", "slowdown": "0.0021", "strongest": "0.0125", "cost": "0.0125", "opportun": "0.0021", "fail": "0.0062", "close": "0.0187", "precipit": "0.0021", "concern": "0.0312", "lead": "0.0416", "profit": "0.0125", "defend": "0.0021", "abl": "0.0062", "bad": "0.0021", "favor": "0.0062", "restructur": "0.0021", "outstand": "0.0042", "deficit": "0.0021", "progress": "0.0021", "boost": "0.0104", "correct": "0.0062", "encourag": "0.0042", "investig": "0.0021", "advanc": "0.0457", "weak": "0.0021", "ban": "0.0042", "slow": "0.0166", "excess": "0.0021", "disput": "0.0021", "strong": "0.0042", "great": "0.0042", "deterior": "0.0021", "unemploy": "0.0021", "contract": "0.0062", "threat": "0.0042", "improv": "0.0021", "allianc": "0.0021", "suspend": "0.0021", "effici": "0.0021", "declin": "0.0686", "win": "0.0042", "bankruptci": "0.0021", "shortag": "0.0042", "cancel": "0.0021", "stabl": "0.0062", "miss": "0.0042", "drought": "0.0021", "damag": "0.0021", "bolster": "0.0042", "better": "0.0042", "question": "0.0021", "construct": "0.0125", "doubt": "0.0021", "downgrad": "0.0021", "threaten": "0.0042", "unexpect": "0.0042", "forc": "0.0021", "hurt": "0.0021", "warn": "0.0042", "gain": "0.0936", "termin": "0.0021", "eas": "0.0062", "highest": "0.0104", "fraud": "0.0021", "default": "0.0042", "seiz": "0.0042", "will": "0.0021", "limit": "0.0125", "posit": "0.0083", "problem": "0.0042", "claim": "0.0104", "weaker": "0.0042", "advantag": "0.0042", "strengthen": "0.0104", "challeng": "0.0062", "premier": "0.0021", "worri": "0.0062", "alleg": "0.0021", "critic": "0.0021", "attract": "0.0062", "sever": "0.0042", "halt": "0.0042", "strength": "0.0021", "delay": "0.0021", "fire": "0.0021", "boom": "0.0021", "reject": "0.0021", "weaken": "0.0042", "difficult": "0.0042", "tighten": "0.0083", "effect": "0.0042", "resign": "0.0021", "alert": "0.0042", "quit": "0.0042", "refin": "0.0083", "postpon": "0.0042", "stabil": "0.0042", "stress": "0.0021", "liquid": "0.0021", "antitrust": "0.0021", "stronger": "0.0042", "su": "0.0021", "inform": "0.0021", "deni": "0.0021", "achiev": "0.0021"}}, "MERVAL": {"1": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "2": {"recess": "0.0013", "opposit": "0.0057", "lack": "0.0025", "protest": "0.0088", "surpass": "0.0038", "fear": "0.0006", "suffer": "0.0063", "fine": "0.0044", "accus": "0.0019", "cut": "0.0239", "depend": "0.0025", "except": "0.0019", "late": "0.0057", "arrest": "0.0006", "bailout": "0.0013", "volatil": "0.0019", "disrupt": "0.0013", "complaint": "0.0019", "good": "0.0075", "greater": "0.0057", "disclos": "0.0013", "rebound": "0.0057", "stop": "0.0088", "break": "0.0013", "worst": "0.0038", "know": "0.0013", "press": "0.0044", "loss": "0.0126", "bar": "0.0013", "success": "0.0019", "lost": "0.0082", "outperform": "0.0006", "drop": "0.0383", "negat": "0.0031", "resolv": "0.0038", "defens": "0.0025", "benefit": "0.0075", "integr": "0.0006", "lose": "0.0057", "popular": "0.0031", "collaps": "0.0031", "crisi": "0.0094", "prevent": "0.0031", "confid": "0.0031", "slower": "0.0044", "shut": "0.0075", "slowdown": "0.0006", "strongest": "0.0013", "cost": "0.0232", "opportun": "0.0050", "fail": "0.0101", "close": "0.0258", "precipit": "0.0006", "concern": "0.0144", "lead": "0.0107", "profit": "0.0446", "defend": "0.0013", "abl": "0.0044", "bad": "0.0019", "favor": "0.0019", "restructur": "0.0075", "outstand": "0.0025", "deficit": "0.0063", "progress": "0.0025", "boost": "0.0289", "correct": "0.0025", "encourag": "0.0006", "investig": "0.0069", "advanc": "0.0503", "weak": "0.0006", "ban": "0.0031", "slow": "0.0082", "excess": "0.0013", "disput": "0.0050", "strong": "0.0038", "great": "0.0038", "deterior": "0.0006", "unemploy": "0.0019", "contract": "0.0371", "threat": "0.0013", "improv": "0.0151", "allianc": "0.0063", "suspend": "0.0075", "effici": "0.0013", "declin": "0.0465", "win": "0.0057", "bankruptci": "0.0006", "shortag": "0.0138", "cancel": "0.0038", "stabl": "0.0006", "miss": "0.0025", "drought": "0.0006", "damag": "0.0038", "bolster": "0.0050", "better": "0.0057", "question": "0.0050", "construct": "0.0101", "doubt": "0.0019", "downgrad": "0.0013", "threaten": "0.0057", "unexpect": "0.0013", "forc": "0.0094", "hurt": "0.0013", "warn": "0.0006", "gain": "0.0817", "termin": "0.0088", "eas": "0.0025", "highest": "0.0119", "fraud": "0.0013", "default": "0.0063", "seiz": "0.0088", "will": "0.0013", "limit": "0.0050", "posit": "0.0170", "problem": "0.0031", "claim": "0.0019", "weaker": "0.0031", "advantag": "0.0025", "strengthen": "0.0044", "challeng": "0.0038", "premier": "0.0025", "worri": "0.0013", "alleg": "0.0031", "critic": "0.0013", "attract": "0.0063", "sever": "0.0063", "halt": "0.0132", "strength": "0.0031", "delay": "0.0094", "fire": "0.0019", "boom": "0.0025", "reject": "0.0050", "weaken": "0.0050", "difficult": "0.0044", "tighten": "0.0013", "effect": "0.0063", "resign": "0.0006", "alert": "0.0013", "quit": "0.0006", "refin": "0.0226", "postpon": "0.0038", "stabil": "0.0025", "stress": "0.0025", "liquid": "0.0031", "antitrust": "0.0031", "stronger": "0.0019", "su": "0.0025", "inform": "0.0044", "deni": "0.0013", "achiev": "0.0025"}, "3": {"recess": "0.0038", "opposit": "0.0113", "lack": "0.0045", "protest": "0.0091", "surpass": "0.0023", "fear": "0.0023", "suffer": "0.0015", "fine": "0.0015", "accus": "0.0023", "cut": "0.0219", "depend": "0.0045", "except": "0.0061", "late": "0.0053", "arrest": "0.0023", "bailout": "0.0023", "volatil": "0.0023", "disrupt": "0.0061", "complaint": "0.0015", "good": "0.0091", "greater": "0.0045", "disclos": "0.0023", "rebound": "0.0045", "stop": "0.0038", "break": "0.0008", "worst": "0.0038", "know": "0.0038", "press": "0.0061", "loss": "0.0136", "bar": "0.0015", "success": "0.0045", "lost": "0.0113", "outperform": "0.0008", "drop": "0.0552", "negat": "0.0045", "resolv": "0.0015", "defens": "0.0030", "benefit": "0.0045", "integr": "0.0015", "lose": "0.0045", "popular": "0.0015", "collaps": "0.0023", "crisi": "0.0083", "prevent": "0.0030", "confid": "0.0045", "slower": "0.0015", "shut": "0.0030", "slowdown": "0.0008", "strongest": "0.0008", "cost": "0.0272", "opportun": "0.0023", "fail": "0.0083", "close": "0.0234", "precipit": "0.0008", "concern": "0.0144", "lead": "0.0166", "profit": "0.0378", "defend": "0.0030", "abl": "0.0038", "bad": "0.0023", "favor": "0.0023", "restructur": "0.0083", "outstand": "0.0015", "deficit": "0.0053", "progress": "0.0008", "boost": "0.0378", "correct": "0.0008", "encourag": "0.0008", "investig": "0.0030", "advanc": "0.0378", "weak": "0.0023", "ban": "0.0008", "slow": "0.0045", "excess": "0.0008", "disput": "0.0023", "strong": "0.0091", "great": "0.0030", "deterior": "0.0015", "unemploy": "0.0038", "contract": "0.0325", "threat": "0.0038", "improv": "0.0083", "allianc": "0.0030", "suspend": "0.0061", "effici": "0.0015", "declin": "0.0590", "win": "0.0068", "bankruptci": "0.0008", "shortag": "0.0053", "cancel": "0.0076", "stabl": "0.0015", "miss": "0.0053", "drought": "0.0015", "damag": "0.0038", "bolster": "0.0015", "better": "0.0061", "question": "0.0030", "construct": "0.0113", "doubt": "0.0023", "downgrad": "0.0030", "threaten": "0.0083", "unexpect": "0.0015", "forc": "0.0106", "hurt": "0.0038", "warn": "0.0008", "gain": "0.0794", "termin": "0.0045", "eas": "0.0038", "highest": "0.0182", "fraud": "0.0023", "default": "0.0091", "seiz": "0.0053", "will": "0.0023", "limit": "0.0083", "posit": "0.0076", "problem": "0.0038", "claim": "0.0015", "weaker": "0.0015", "advantag": "0.0030", "strengthen": "0.0038", "challeng": "0.0038", "premier": "0.0023", "worri": "0.0008", "alleg": "0.0015", "critic": "0.0008", "attract": "0.0083", "sever": "0.0045", "halt": "0.0113", "strength": "0.0008", "delay": "0.0053", "fire": "0.0023", "boom": "0.0023", "reject": "0.0023", "weaken": "0.0045", "difficult": "0.0061", "tighten": "0.0023", "effect": "0.0061", "resign": "0.0015", "alert": "0.0008", "quit": "0.0008", "refin": "0.0250", "postpon": "0.0015", "stabil": "0.0023", "stress": "0.0030", "liquid": "0.0030", "antitrust": "0.0038", "stronger": "0.0015", "su": "0.0030", "inform": "0.0045", "deni": "0.0015", "achiev": "0.0015"}, "4": {"recess": "0.0023", "opposit": "0.0085", "lack": "0.0039", "protest": "0.0062", "surpass": "0.0023", "fear": "0.0023", "suffer": "0.0031", "fine": "0.0015", "accus": "0.0008", "cut": "0.0217", "depend": "0.0023", "except": "0.0031", "late": "0.0031", "arrest": "0.0015", "bailout": "0.0046", "volatil": "0.0015", "disrupt": "0.0023", "complaint": "0.0008", "good": "0.0101", "greater": "0.0046", "disclos": "0.0023", "rebound": "0.0031", "stop": "0.0031", "break": "0.0015", "worst": "0.0039", "know": "0.0023", "press": "0.0085", "loss": "0.0131", "bar": "0.0008", "success": "0.0015", "lost": "0.0139", "outperform": "0.0039", "drop": "0.0596", "negat": "0.0039", "resolv": "0.0015", "defens": "0.0023", "benefit": "0.0077", "integr": "0.0008", "lose": "0.0093", "popular": "0.0008", "collaps": "0.0023", "crisi": "0.0155", "prevent": "0.0054", "confid": "0.0062", "slower": "0.0015", "shut": "0.0054", "slowdown": "0.0008", "strongest": "0.0023", "cost": "0.0224", "opportun": "0.0054", "fail": "0.0101", "close": "0.0240", "precipit": "0.0008", "concern": "0.0309", "lead": "0.0147", "profit": "0.0340", "defend": "0.0008", "abl": "0.0054", "bad": "0.0031", "favor": "0.0015", "restructur": "0.0077", "outstand": "0.0015", "deficit": "0.0015", "progress": "0.0023", "boost": "0.0271", "correct": "0.0023", "encourag": "0.0023", "investig": "0.0046", "advanc": "0.0518", "weak": "0.0023", "ban": "0.0023", "slow": "0.0085", "excess": "0.0015", "disput": "0.0023", "strong": "0.0054", "great": "0.0015", "deterior": "0.0023", "unemploy": "0.0023", "contract": "0.0294", "threat": "0.0023", "improv": "0.0062", "allianc": "0.0031", "suspend": "0.0046", "effici": "0.0015", "declin": "0.0557", "win": "0.0062", "bankruptci": "0.0008", "shortag": "0.0062", "cancel": "0.0070", "stabl": "0.0008", "miss": "0.0093", "drought": "0.0023", "damag": "0.0008", "bolster": "0.0039", "better": "0.0070", "question": "0.0039", "construct": "0.0062", "doubt": "0.0008", "downgrad": "0.0023", "threaten": "0.0031", "unexpect": "0.0015", "forc": "0.0077", "hurt": "0.0031", "warn": "0.0015", "gain": "0.0804", "termin": "0.0015", "eas": "0.0147", "highest": "0.0116", "fraud": "0.0023", "default": "0.0070", "seiz": "0.0046", "will": "0.0023", "limit": "0.0070", "posit": "0.0054", "problem": "0.0031", "claim": "0.0015", "weaker": "0.0023", "advantag": "0.0023", "strengthen": "0.0054", "challeng": "0.0023", "premier": "0.0023", "worri": "0.0015", "alleg": "0.0031", "critic": "0.0023", "attract": "0.0046", "sever": "0.0046", "halt": "0.0070", "strength": "0.0031", "delay": "0.0101", "fire": "0.0023", "boom": "0.0008", "reject": "0.0015", "weaken": "0.0085", "difficult": "0.0054", "tighten": "0.0023", "effect": "0.0046", "resign": "0.0015", "alert": "0.0008", "quit": "0.0015", "refin": "0.0186", "postpon": "0.0054", "stabil": "0.0054", "stress": "0.0023", "liquid": "0.0046", "antitrust": "0.0008", "stronger": "0.0015", "su": "0.0023", "inform": "0.0039", "deni": "0.0008", "achiev": "0.0023"}, "5": {"recess": "0.0100", "opposit": "0.0033", "lack": "0.0134", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0033", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0033", "fine": "0.0033", "accus": "0.0033", "cut": "0.0100", "depend": "0.0033", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0033", "arrest": "0.0033", "bailout": "0.0033", "volatil": "0.0033", "disrupt": "0.0033", "complaint": "0.0033", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0033", "disclos": "0.0033", "rebound": "0.0167", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0134", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0033", "loss": "0.0301", "bar": "0.0033", "success": "0.0033", "lost": "0.0100", "outperform": "0.0033", "drop": "0.0201", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0033", "defens": "0.0033", "benefit": "0.0033", "integr": "0.0033", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0033", "confid": "0.0201", "slower": "0.0033", "shut": "0.0033", "slowdown": "0.0033", "strongest": "0.0033", "cost": "0.0301", "opportun": "0.0100", "fail": "0.0100", "close": "0.0134", "precipit": "0.0033", "concern": "0.0100", "lead": "0.0134", "profit": "0.0100", "defend": "0.0033", "abl": "0.0033", "bad": "0.0033", "favor": "0.0033", "restructur": "0.0167", "outstand": "0.0100", "deficit": "0.0134", "progress": "0.0033", "boost": "0.0234", "correct": "0.0033", "encourag": "0.0033", "investig": "0.0033", "advanc": "0.0134", "weak": "0.0033", "ban": "0.0033", "slow": "0.0033", "excess": "0.0033", "disput": "0.0033", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0033", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0033", "contract": "0.0134", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0100", "allianc": "0.0033", "suspend": "0.0033", "effici": "0.0033", "declin": "0.0334", "win": "0.0033", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0033", "cancel": "0.0033", "stabl": "0.0033", "miss": "0.0033", "drought": "0.0033", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0033", "better": "0.0134", "question": "0.0033", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0033", "downgrad": "0.0033", "threaten": "0.0100", "unexpect": "0.0033", "forc": "0.0033", "hurt": "0.0033", "warn": "0.0033", "gain": "0.0502", "termin": "0.0033", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0100", "fraud": "0.0033", "default": "0.0167", "seiz": "0.0033", "will": "0.0033", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0167", "problem": "0.0033", "claim": "0.0033", "weaker": "0.0033", "advantag": "0.0100", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0033", "premier": "0.0033", "worri": "0.0033", "alleg": "0.0033", "critic": "0.0033", "attract": "0.0100", "sever": "0.0033", "halt": "0.0033", "strength": "0.0033", "delay": "0.0033", "fire": "0.0033", "boom": "0.0033", "reject": "0.0033", "weaken": "0.0033", "difficult": "0.0100", "tighten": "0.0033", "effect": "0.0033", "resign": "0.0033", "alert": "0.0033", "quit": "0.0033", "refin": "0.0100", "postpon": "0.0033", "stabil": "0.0033", "stress": "0.0033", "liquid": "0.0100", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0033", "su": "0.0033", "inform": "0.0033", "deni": "0.0033", "achiev": "0.0033"}, "6": {"recess": "0.0019", "opposit": "0.0057", "lack": "0.0028", "protest": "0.0047", "surpass": "0.0028", "fear": "0.0009", "suffer": "0.0009", "fine": "0.0019", "accus": "0.0009", "cut": "0.0142", "depend": "0.0038", "except": "0.0038", "late": "0.0047", "arrest": "0.0028", "bailout": "0.0009", "volatil": "0.0038", "disrupt": "0.0009", "complaint": "0.0019", "good": "0.0104", "greater": "0.0038", "disclos": "0.0038", "rebound": "0.0047", "stop": "0.0076", "break": "0.0047", "worst": "0.0057", "know": "0.0009", "press": "0.0028", "loss": "0.0076", "bar": "0.0019", "success": "0.0019", "lost": "0.0114", "outperform": "0.0019", "drop": "0.0369", "negat": "0.0038", "resolv": "0.0019", "defens": "0.0038", "benefit": "0.0104", "integr": "0.0009", "lose": "0.0104", "popular": "0.0057", "collaps": "0.0019", "crisi": "0.0066", "prevent": "0.0038", "confid": "0.0066", "slower": "0.0019", "shut": "0.0057", "slowdown": "0.0019", "strongest": "0.0019", "cost": "0.0170", "opportun": "0.0028", "fail": "0.0151", "close": "0.0199", "precipit": "0.0009", "concern": "0.0180", "lead": "0.0132", "profit": "0.0218", "defend": "0.0019", "abl": "0.0057", "bad": "0.0009", "favor": "0.0019", "restructur": "0.0076", "outstand": "0.0028", "deficit": "0.0132", "progress": "0.0047", "boost": "0.0180", "correct": "0.0019", "encourag": "0.0009", "investig": "0.0009", "advanc": "0.0464", "weak": "0.0076", "ban": "0.0019", "slow": "0.0085", "excess": "0.0028", "disput": "0.0066", "strong": "0.0066", "great": "0.0009", "deterior": "0.0009", "unemploy": "0.0038", "contract": "0.0341", "threat": "0.0009", "improv": "0.0104", "allianc": "0.0047", "suspend": "0.0038", "effici": "0.0019", "declin": "0.0539", "win": "0.0057", "bankruptci": "0.0009", "shortag": "0.0085", "cancel": "0.0076", "stabl": "0.0028", "miss": "0.0009", "drought": "0.0047", "damag": "0.0038", "bolster": "0.0038", "better": "0.0009", "question": "0.0047", "construct": "0.0076", "doubt": "0.0009", "downgrad": "0.0028", "threaten": "0.0038", "unexpect": "0.0057", "forc": "0.0161", "hurt": "0.0047", "warn": "0.0019", "gain": "0.0993", "termin": "0.0009", "eas": "0.0038", "highest": "0.0199", "fraud": "0.0009", "default": "0.0142", "seiz": "0.0066", "will": "0.0047", "limit": "0.0132", "posit": "0.0114", "problem": "0.0038", "claim": "0.0019", "weaker": "0.0047", "advantag": "0.0028", "strengthen": "0.0009", "challeng": "0.0038", "premier": "0.0019", "worri": "0.0038", "alleg": "0.0009", "critic": "0.0009", "attract": "0.0095", "sever": "0.0057", "halt": "0.0123", "strength": "0.0009", "delay": "0.0038", "fire": "0.0028", "boom": "0.0038", "reject": "0.0009", "weaken": "0.0066", "difficult": "0.0019", "tighten": "0.0028", "effect": "0.0047", "resign": "0.0009", "alert": "0.0019", "quit": "0.0028", "refin": "0.0246", "postpon": "0.0028", "stabil": "0.0009", "stress": "0.0009", "liquid": "0.0047", "antitrust": "0.0019", "stronger": "0.0019", "su": "0.0076", "inform": "0.0019", "deni": "0.0028", "achiev": "0.0019"}, "7": {"recess": "0.0065", "opposit": "0.0065", "lack": "0.0065", "protest": "0.0065", "surpass": "0.0065", "fear": "0.0065", "suffer": "0.0065", "fine": "0.0065", "accus": "0.0065", "cut": "0.0065", "depend": "0.0065", "except": "0.0065", "late": "0.0065", "arrest": "0.0065", "bailout": "0.0065", "volatil": "0.0065", "disrupt": "0.0065", "complaint": "0.0065", "good": "0.0065", "greater": "0.0065", "disclos": "0.0065", "rebound": "0.0065", "stop": "0.0065", "break": "0.0065", "worst": "0.0065", "know": "0.0065", "press": "0.0065", "loss": "0.0065", "bar": "0.0065", "success": "0.0065", "lost": "0.0065", "outperform": "0.0065", "drop": "0.0065", "negat": "0.0065", "resolv": "0.0065", "defens": "0.0065", "benefit": "0.0065", "integr": "0.0065", "lose": "0.0065", "popular": "0.0065", "collaps": "0.0065", "crisi": "0.0065", "prevent": "0.0065", "confid": "0.0065", "slower": "0.0065", "shut": "0.0065", "slowdown": "0.0065", "strongest": "0.0065", "cost": "0.0065", "opportun": "0.0131", "fail": "0.0065", "close": "0.0065", "precipit": "0.0065", "concern": "0.0065", "lead": "0.0065", "profit": "0.0065", "defend": "0.0065", "abl": "0.0065", "bad": "0.0065", "favor": "0.0065", "restructur": "0.0065", "outstand": "0.0065", "deficit": "0.0065", "progress": "0.0065", "boost": "0.0131", "correct": "0.0065", "encourag": "0.0065", "investig": "0.0065", "advanc": "0.0065", "weak": "0.0065", "ban": "0.0065", "slow": "0.0065", "excess": "0.0065", "disput": "0.0065", "strong": "0.0065", "great": "0.0065", "deterior": "0.0065", "unemploy": "0.0065", "contract": "0.0131", "threat": "0.0065", "improv": "0.0065", "allianc": "0.0065", "suspend": "0.0065", "effici": "0.0065", "declin": "0.0065", "win": "0.0065", "bankruptci": "0.0065", "shortag": "0.0065", "cancel": "0.0065", "stabl": "0.0065", "miss": "0.0065", "drought": "0.0065", "damag": "0.0065", "bolster": "0.0065", "better": "0.0065", "question": "0.0065", "construct": "0.0065", "doubt": "0.0065", "downgrad": "0.0065", "threaten": "0.0065", "unexpect": "0.0065", "forc": "0.0065", "hurt": "0.0065", "warn": "0.0065", "gain": "0.0065", "termin": "0.0065", "eas": "0.0065", "highest": "0.0065", "fraud": "0.0065", "default": "0.0065", "seiz": "0.0065", "will": "0.0065", "limit": "0.0065", "posit": "0.0065", "problem": "0.0065", "claim": "0.0065", "weaker": "0.0065", "advantag": "0.0065", "strengthen": "0.0065", "challeng": "0.0065", "premier": "0.0065", "worri": "0.0065", "alleg": "0.0065", "critic": "0.0065", "attract": "0.0065", "sever": "0.0065", "halt": "0.0065", "strength": "0.0065", "delay": "0.0065", "fire": "0.0065", "boom": "0.0065", "reject": "0.0065", "weaken": "0.0065", "difficult": "0.0065", "tighten": "0.0065", "effect": "0.0065", "resign": "0.0065", "alert": "0.0065", "quit": "0.0065", "refin": "0.0065", "postpon": "0.0065", "stabil": "0.0065", "stress": "0.0065", "liquid": "0.0065", "antitrust": "0.0065", "stronger": "0.0065", "su": "0.0065", "inform": "0.0065", "deni": "0.0065", "achiev": "0.0065"}, "8": {"recess": "0.0023", "opposit": "0.0017", "lack": "0.0045", "protest": "0.0062", "surpass": "0.0045", "fear": "0.0023", "suffer": "0.0017", "fine": "0.0011", "accus": "0.0017", "cut": "0.0215", "depend": "0.0040", "except": "0.0028", "late": "0.0023", "arrest": "0.0023", "bailout": "0.0011", "volatil": "0.0011", "disrupt": "0.0057", "complaint": "0.0011", "good": "0.0085", "greater": "0.0051", "disclos": "0.0023", "rebound": "0.0045", "stop": "0.0023", "break": "0.0023", "worst": "0.0068", "know": "0.0023", "press": "0.0023", "loss": "0.0147", "bar": "0.0011", "success": "0.0034", "lost": "0.0130", "outperform": "0.0023", "drop": "0.0640", "negat": "0.0011", "resolv": "0.0028", "defens": "0.0017", "benefit": "0.0085", "integr": "0.0006", "lose": "0.0096", "popular": "0.0028", "collaps": "0.0006", "crisi": "0.0062", "prevent": "0.0051", "confid": "0.0051", "slower": "0.0006", "shut": "0.0051", "slowdown": "0.0023", "strongest": "0.0011", "cost": "0.0170", "opportun": "0.0040", "fail": "0.0096", "close": "0.0249", "precipit": "0.0006", "concern": "0.0221", "lead": "0.0108", "profit": "0.0317", "defend": "0.0017", "abl": "0.0023", "bad": "0.0028", "favor": "0.0017", "restructur": "0.0045", "outstand": "0.0023", "deficit": "0.0102", "progress": "0.0023", "boost": "0.0328", "correct": "0.0017", "encourag": "0.0006", "investig": "0.0040", "advanc": "0.0334", "weak": "0.0023", "ban": "0.0017", "slow": "0.0051", "excess": "0.0011", "disput": "0.0040", "strong": "0.0045", "great": "0.0028", "deterior": "0.0006", "unemploy": "0.0017", "contract": "0.0266", "threat": "0.0011", "improv": "0.0068", "allianc": "0.0045", "suspend": "0.0034", "effici": "0.0011", "declin": "0.0634", "win": "0.0057", "bankruptci": "0.0011", "shortag": "0.0051", "cancel": "0.0040", "stabl": "0.0040", "miss": "0.0028", "drought": "0.0006", "damag": "0.0023", "bolster": "0.0023", "better": "0.0057", "question": "0.0028", "construct": "0.0130", "doubt": "0.0011", "downgrad": "0.0034", "threaten": "0.0028", "unexpect": "0.0017", "forc": "0.0079", "hurt": "0.0057", "warn": "0.0023", "gain": "0.0997", "termin": "0.0096", "eas": "0.0040", "highest": "0.0193", "fraud": "0.0023", "default": "0.0176", "seiz": "0.0040", "will": "0.0011", "limit": "0.0074", "posit": "0.0243", "problem": "0.0034", "claim": "0.0011", "weaker": "0.0034", "advantag": "0.0051", "strengthen": "0.0017", "challeng": "0.0034", "premier": "0.0017", "worri": "0.0006", "alleg": "0.0034", "critic": "0.0011", "attract": "0.0074", "sever": "0.0040", "halt": "0.0096", "strength": "0.0011", "delay": "0.0040", "fire": "0.0011", "boom": "0.0011", "reject": "0.0011", "weaken": "0.0074", "difficult": "0.0028", "tighten": "0.0011", "effect": "0.0040", "resign": "0.0017", "alert": "0.0017", "quit": "0.0017", "refin": "0.0300", "postpon": "0.0023", "stabil": "0.0034", "stress": "0.0017", "liquid": "0.0040", "antitrust": "0.0023", "stronger": "0.0028", "su": "0.0051", "inform": "0.0011", "deni": "0.0006", "achiev": "0.0011"}, "9": {"recess": "0.0057", "opposit": "0.0086", "lack": "0.0014", "protest": "0.0086", "surpass": "0.0043", "fear": "0.0014", "suffer": "0.0072", "fine": "0.0029", "accus": "0.0029", "cut": "0.0172", "depend": "0.0072", "except": "0.0043", "late": "0.0043", "arrest": "0.0014", "bailout": "0.0029", "volatil": "0.0029", "disrupt": "0.0029", "complaint": "0.0043", "good": "0.0100", "greater": "0.0029", "disclos": "0.0029", "rebound": "0.0043", "stop": "0.0086", "break": "0.0014", "worst": "0.0086", "know": "0.0014", "press": "0.0072", "loss": "0.0129", "bar": "0.0029", "success": "0.0014", "lost": "0.0100", "outperform": "0.0014", "drop": "0.0415", "negat": "0.0029", "resolv": "0.0043", "defens": "0.0014", "benefit": "0.0086", "integr": "0.0043", "lose": "0.0057", "popular": "0.0029", "collaps": "0.0014", "crisi": "0.0086", "prevent": "0.0014", "confid": "0.0072", "slower": "0.0014", "shut": "0.0014", "slowdown": "0.0014", "strongest": "0.0014", "cost": "0.0129", "opportun": "0.0029", "fail": "0.0057", "close": "0.0244", "precipit": "0.0014", "concern": "0.0172", "lead": "0.0100", "profit": "0.0372", "defend": "0.0014", "abl": "0.0057", "bad": "0.0029", "favor": "0.0014", "restructur": "0.0115", "outstand": "0.0057", "deficit": "0.0029", "progress": "0.0014", "boost": "0.0229", "correct": "0.0029", "encourag": "0.0014", "investig": "0.0043", "advanc": "0.0344", "weak": "0.0014", "ban": "0.0057", "slow": "0.0043", "excess": "0.0014", "disput": "0.0072", "strong": "0.0043", "great": "0.0057", "deterior": "0.0014", "unemploy": "0.0014", "contract": "0.0215", "threat": "0.0029", "improv": "0.0129", "allianc": "0.0043", "suspend": "0.0072", "effici": "0.0043", "declin": "0.0645", "win": "0.0086", "bankruptci": "0.0014", "shortag": "0.0129", "cancel": "0.0029", "stabl": "0.0057", "miss": "0.0057", "drought": "0.0014", "damag": "0.0043", "bolster": "0.0043", "better": "0.0072", "question": "0.0043", "construct": "0.0100", "doubt": "0.0014", "downgrad": "0.0043", "threaten": "0.0086", "unexpect": "0.0043", "forc": "0.0100", "hurt": "0.0043", "warn": "0.0014", "gain": "0.0688", "termin": "0.0043", "eas": "0.0057", "highest": "0.0100", "fraud": "0.0014", "default": "0.0129", "seiz": "0.0043", "will": "0.0029", "limit": "0.0072", "posit": "0.0158", "problem": "0.0057", "claim": "0.0029", "weaker": "0.0029", "advantag": "0.0043", "strengthen": "0.0057", "challeng": "0.0029", "premier": "0.0014", "worri": "0.0014", "alleg": "0.0043", "critic": "0.0043", "attract": "0.0100", "sever": "0.0029", "halt": "0.0086", "strength": "0.0014", "delay": "0.0057", "fire": "0.0029", "boom": "0.0043", "reject": "0.0029", "weaken": "0.0029", "difficult": "0.0014", "tighten": "0.0043", "effect": "0.0014", "resign": "0.0029", "alert": "0.0014", "quit": "0.0014", "refin": "0.0143", "postpon": "0.0029", "stabil": "0.0072", "stress": "0.0014", "liquid": "0.0043", "antitrust": "0.0043", "stronger": "0.0014", "su": "0.0043", "inform": "0.0057", "deni": "0.0029", "achiev": "0.0014"}, "10": {"recess": "0.0076", "opposit": "0.0038", "lack": "0.0038", "protest": "0.0038", "surpass": "0.0114", "fear": "0.0038", "suffer": "0.0038", "fine": "0.0038", "accus": "0.0038", "cut": "0.0152", "depend": "0.0114", "except": "0.0076", "late": "0.0076", "arrest": "0.0038", "bailout": "0.0038", "volatil": "0.0038", "disrupt": "0.0038", "complaint": "0.0038", "good": "0.0038", "greater": "0.0038", "disclos": "0.0038", "rebound": "0.0038", "stop": "0.0038", "break": "0.0038", "worst": "0.0114", "know": "0.0038", "press": "0.0076", "loss": "0.0038", "bar": "0.0038", "success": "0.0038", "lost": "0.0114", "outperform": "0.0038", "drop": "0.0304", "negat": "0.0038", "resolv": "0.0038", "defens": "0.0038", "benefit": "0.0076", "integr": "0.0038", "lose": "0.0038", "popular": "0.0038", "collaps": "0.0038", "crisi": "0.0152", "prevent": "0.0038", "confid": "0.0076", "slower": "0.0038", "shut": "0.0076", "slowdown": "0.0038", "strongest": "0.0038", "cost": "0.0190", "opportun": "0.0076", "fail": "0.0114", "close": "0.0190", "precipit": "0.0038", "concern": "0.0228", "lead": "0.0038", "profit": "0.0076", "defend": "0.0038", "abl": "0.0038", "bad": "0.0038", "favor": "0.0038", "restructur": "0.0152", "outstand": "0.0076", "deficit": "0.0038", "progress": "0.0038", "boost": "0.0190", "correct": "0.0038", "encourag": "0.0038", "investig": "0.0076", "advanc": "0.0190", "weak": "0.0038", "ban": "0.0038", "slow": "0.0076", "excess": "0.0038", "disput": "0.0038", "strong": "0.0076", "great": "0.0038", "deterior": "0.0038", "unemploy": "0.0038", "contract": "0.0076", "threat": "0.0038", "improv": "0.0076", "allianc": "0.0038", "suspend": "0.0076", "effici": "0.0076", "declin": "0.0532", "win": "0.0114", "bankruptci": "0.0038", "shortag": "0.0038", "cancel": "0.0076", "stabl": "0.0038", "miss": "0.0038", "drought": "0.0038", "damag": "0.0038", "bolster": "0.0038", "better": "0.0038", "question": "0.0076", "construct": "0.0038", "doubt": "0.0038", "downgrad": "0.0038", "threaten": "0.0038", "unexpect": "0.0038", "forc": "0.0152", "hurt": "0.0038", "warn": "0.0038", "gain": "0.0266", "termin": "0.0038", "eas": "0.0076", "highest": "0.0076", "fraud": "0.0038", "default": "0.0304", "seiz": "0.0038", "will": "0.0038", "limit": "0.0152", "posit": "0.0076", "problem": "0.0038", "claim": "0.0038", "weaker": "0.0076", "advantag": "0.0076", "strengthen": "0.0038", "challeng": "0.0076", "premier": "0.0038", "worri": "0.0038", "alleg": "0.0038", "critic": "0.0038", "attract": "0.0076", "sever": "0.0038", "halt": "0.0038", "strength": "0.0038", "delay": "0.0038", "fire": "0.0038", "boom": "0.0076", "reject": "0.0038", "weaken": "0.0038", "difficult": "0.0038", "tighten": "0.0038", "effect": "0.0038", "resign": "0.0114", "alert": "0.0038", "quit": "0.0038", "refin": "0.0076", "postpon": "0.0038", "stabil": "0.0038", "stress": "0.0038", "liquid": "0.0076", "antitrust": "0.0038", "stronger": "0.0038", "su": "0.0038", "inform": "0.0038", "deni": "0.0038", "achiev": "0.0076"}, "11": {"recess": "0.0033", "opposit": "0.0065", "lack": "0.0033", "protest": "0.0033", "surpass": "0.0033", "fear": "0.0033", "suffer": "0.0033", "fine": "0.0033", "accus": "0.0033", "cut": "0.0130", "depend": "0.0033", "except": "0.0033", "late": "0.0033", "arrest": "0.0033", "bailout": "0.0033", "volatil": "0.0065", "disrupt": "0.0033", "complaint": "0.0065", "good": "0.0033", "greater": "0.0098", "disclos": "0.0065", "rebound": "0.0098", "stop": "0.0033", "break": "0.0033", "worst": "0.0065", "know": "0.0033", "press": "0.0033", "loss": "0.0065", "bar": "0.0033", "success": "0.0033", "lost": "0.0163", "outperform": "0.0033", "drop": "0.0195", "negat": "0.0033", "resolv": "0.0033", "defens": "0.0033", "benefit": "0.0033", "integr": "0.0033", "lose": "0.0163", "popular": "0.0130", "collaps": "0.0033", "crisi": "0.0130", "prevent": "0.0033", "confid": "0.0033", "slower": "0.0033", "shut": "0.0033", "slowdown": "0.0033", "strongest": "0.0033", "cost": "0.0163", "opportun": "0.0098", "fail": "0.0098", "close": "0.0098", "precipit": "0.0033", "concern": "0.0065", "lead": "0.0065", "profit": "0.0358", "defend": "0.0033", "abl": "0.0033", "bad": "0.0033", "favor": "0.0033", "restructur": "0.0130", "outstand": "0.0033", "deficit": "0.0065", "progress": "0.0065", "boost": "0.0293", "correct": "0.0033", "encourag": "0.0033", "investig": "0.0033", "advanc": "0.0195", "weak": "0.0033", "ban": "0.0098", "slow": "0.0033", "excess": "0.0033", "disput": "0.0033", "strong": "0.0098", "great": "0.0065", "deterior": "0.0033", "unemploy": "0.0033", "contract": "0.0195", "threat": "0.0033", "improv": "0.0326", "allianc": "0.0033", "suspend": "0.0033", "effici": "0.0033", "declin": "0.0293", "win": "0.0065", "bankruptci": "0.0033", "shortag": "0.0033", "cancel": "0.0033", "stabl": "0.0033", "miss": "0.0033", "drought": "0.0033", "damag": "0.0033", "bolster": "0.0033", "better": "0.0065", "question": "0.0033", "construct": "0.0163", "doubt": "0.0033", "downgrad": "0.0065", "threaten": "0.0033", "unexpect": "0.0033", "forc": "0.0065", "hurt": "0.0033", "warn": "0.0033", "gain": "0.0293", "termin": "0.0130", "eas": "0.0065", "highest": "0.0033", "fraud": "0.0033", "default": "0.0065", "seiz": "0.0098", "will": "0.0033", "limit": "0.0033", "posit": "0.0130", "problem": "0.0033", "claim": "0.0033", "weaker": "0.0033", "advantag": "0.0065", "strengthen": "0.0033", "challeng": "0.0098", "premier": "0.0033", "worri": "0.0033", "alleg": "0.0033", "critic": "0.0033", "attract": "0.0098", "sever": "0.0033", "halt": "0.0033", "strength": "0.0033", "delay": "0.0130", "fire": "0.0033", "boom": "0.0033", "reject": "0.0033", "weaken": "0.0033", "difficult": "0.0065", "tighten": "0.0065", "effect": "0.0065", "resign": "0.0033", "alert": "0.0033", "quit": "0.0033", "refin": "0.0521", "postpon": "0.0065", "stabil": "0.0033", "stress": "0.0033", "liquid": "0.0098", "antitrust": "0.0065", "stronger": "0.0033", "su": "0.0033", "inform": "0.0065", "deni": "0.0033", "achiev": "0.0065"}, "12": {"recess": "0.0049", "opposit": "0.0061", "lack": "0.0049", "protest": "0.0097", "surpass": "0.0012", "fear": "0.0049", "suffer": "0.0012", "fine": "0.0012", "accus": "0.0024", "cut": "0.0255", "depend": "0.0036", "except": "0.0073", "late": "0.0061", "arrest": "0.0012", "bailout": "0.0024", "volatil": "0.0012", "disrupt": "0.0024", "complaint": "0.0024", "good": "0.0049", "greater": "0.0024", "disclos": "0.0036", "rebound": "0.0085", "stop": "0.0073", "break": "0.0049", "worst": "0.0073", "know": "0.0012", "press": "0.0061", "loss": "0.0207", "bar": "0.0024", "success": "0.0012", "lost": "0.0182", "outperform": "0.0012", "drop": "0.0645", "negat": "0.0036", "resolv": "0.0036", "defens": "0.0024", "benefit": "0.0085", "integr": "0.0024", "lose": "0.0134", "popular": "0.0061", "collaps": "0.0049", "crisi": "0.0134", "prevent": "0.0049", "confid": "0.0134", "slower": "0.0036", "shut": "0.0061", "slowdown": "0.0012", "strongest": "0.0012", "cost": "0.0182", "opportun": "0.0036", "fail": "0.0073", "close": "0.0243", "precipit": "0.0012", "concern": "0.0170", "lead": "0.0182", "profit": "0.0158", "defend": "0.0024", "abl": "0.0061", "bad": "0.0024", "favor": "0.0024", "restructur": "0.0024", "outstand": "0.0036", "deficit": "0.0036", "progress": "0.0012", "boost": "0.0365", "correct": "0.0012", "encourag": "0.0012", "investig": "0.0109", "advanc": "0.0146", "weak": "0.0012", "ban": "0.0012", "slow": "0.0073", "excess": "0.0012", "disput": "0.0085", "strong": "0.0012", "great": "0.0024", "deterior": "0.0049", "unemploy": "0.0024", "contract": "0.0377", "threat": "0.0036", "improv": "0.0085", "allianc": "0.0012", "suspend": "0.0170", "effici": "0.0012", "declin": "0.0754", "win": "0.0097", "bankruptci": "0.0036", "shortag": "0.0024", "cancel": "0.0085", "stabl": "0.0012", "miss": "0.0061", "drought": "0.0012", "damag": "0.0061", "bolster": "0.0012", "better": "0.0012", "question": "0.0036", "construct": "0.0085", "doubt": "0.0012", "downgrad": "0.0012", "threaten": "0.0073", "unexpect": "0.0024", "forc": "0.0085", "hurt": "0.0061", "warn": "0.0024", "gain": "0.0389", "termin": "0.0036", "eas": "0.0036", "highest": "0.0109", "fraud": "0.0024", "default": "0.0036", "seiz": "0.0085", "will": "0.0036", "limit": "0.0049", "posit": "0.0073", "problem": "0.0049", "claim": "0.0012", "weaker": "0.0036", "advantag": "0.0036", "strengthen": "0.0036", "challeng": "0.0049", "premier": "0.0012", "worri": "0.0012", "alleg": "0.0049", "critic": "0.0012", "attract": "0.0073", "sever": "0.0061", "halt": "0.0122", "strength": "0.0012", "delay": "0.0049", "fire": "0.0024", "boom": "0.0012", "reject": "0.0012", "weaken": "0.0012", "difficult": "0.0049", "tighten": "0.0012", "effect": "0.0049", "resign": "0.0036", "alert": "0.0012", "quit": "0.0024", "refin": "0.0073", "postpon": "0.0012", "stabil": "0.0049", "stress": "0.0012", "liquid": "0.0024", "antitrust": "0.0049", "stronger": "0.0024", "su": "0.0012", "inform": "0.0085", "deni": "0.0049", "achiev": "0.0024"}, "13": {"recess": "0.0034", "opposit": "0.0026", "lack": "0.0060", "protest": "0.0077", "surpass": "0.0034", "fear": "0.0043", "suffer": "0.0043", "fine": "0.0017", "accus": "0.0009", "cut": "0.0340", "depend": "0.0068", "except": "0.0026", "late": "0.0077", "arrest": "0.0009", "bailout": "0.0009", "volatil": "0.0017", "disrupt": "0.0068", "complaint": "0.0009", "good": "0.0102", "greater": "0.0026", "disclos": "0.0026", "rebound": "0.0077", "stop": "0.0043", "break": "0.0034", "worst": "0.0068", "know": "0.0068", "press": "0.0026", "loss": "0.0238", "bar": "0.0009", "success": "0.0043", "lost": "0.0094", "outperform": "0.0017", "drop": "0.0527", "negat": "0.0051", "resolv": "0.0034", "defens": "0.0026", "benefit": "0.0077", "integr": "0.0017", "lose": "0.0068", "popular": "0.0034", "collaps": "0.0017", "crisi": "0.0051", "prevent": "0.0017", "confid": "0.0094", "slower": "0.0034", "shut": "0.0060", "slowdown": "0.0026", "strongest": "0.0009", "cost": "0.0289", "opportun": "0.0051", "fail": "0.0060", "close": "0.0247", "precipit": "0.0009", "concern": "0.0162", "lead": "0.0145", "profit": "0.0374", "defend": "0.0017", "abl": "0.0077", "bad": "0.0009", "favor": "0.0009", "restructur": "0.0026", "outstand": "0.0034", "deficit": "0.0068", "progress": "0.0017", "boost": "0.0298", "correct": "0.0009", "encourag": "0.0017", "investig": "0.0026", "advanc": "0.0272", "weak": "0.0034", "ban": "0.0026", "slow": "0.0026", "excess": "0.0017", "disput": "0.0051", "strong": "0.0051", "great": "0.0034", "deterior": "0.0026", "unemploy": "0.0034", "contract": "0.0196", "threat": "0.0034", "improv": "0.0094", "allianc": "0.0009", "suspend": "0.0085", "effici": "0.0034", "declin": "0.0536", "win": "0.0060", "bankruptci": "0.0017", "shortag": "0.0077", "cancel": "0.0026", "stabl": "0.0034", "miss": "0.0085", "drought": "0.0009", "damag": "0.0034", "bolster": "0.0034", "better": "0.0051", "question": "0.0009", "construct": "0.0153", "doubt": "0.0017", "downgrad": "0.0034", "threaten": "0.0068", "unexpect": "0.0026", "forc": "0.0034", "hurt": "0.0068", "warn": "0.0017", "gain": "0.0689", "termin": "0.0094", "eas": "0.0043", "highest": "0.0145", "fraud": "0.0009", "default": "0.0119", "seiz": "0.0034", "will": "0.0009", "limit": "0.0060", "posit": "0.0085", "problem": "0.0043", "claim": "0.0017", "weaker": "0.0017", "advantag": "0.0017", "strengthen": "0.0051", "challeng": "0.0017", "premier": "0.0017", "worri": "0.0009", "alleg": "0.0026", "critic": "0.0017", "attract": "0.0085", "sever": "0.0043", "halt": "0.0162", "strength": "0.0017", "delay": "0.0034", "fire": "0.0009", "boom": "0.0017", "reject": "0.0009", "weaken": "0.0009", "difficult": "0.0034", "tighten": "0.0034", "effect": "0.0051", "resign": "0.0017", "alert": "0.0009", "quit": "0.0026", "refin": "0.0298", "postpon": "0.0034", "stabil": "0.0068", "stress": "0.0009", "liquid": "0.0034", "antitrust": "0.0009", "stronger": "0.0017", "su": "0.0060", "inform": "0.0060", "deni": "0.0026", "achiev": "0.0009"}, "14": {"recess": "0.0009", "opposit": "0.0046", "lack": "0.0055", "protest": "0.0111", "surpass": "0.0037", "fear": "0.0028", "suffer": "0.0037", "fine": "0.0009", "accus": "0.0018", "cut": "0.0313", "depend": "0.0018", "except": "0.0028", "late": "0.0074", "arrest": "0.0009", "bailout": "0.0018", "volatil": "0.0009", "disrupt": "0.0028", "complaint": "0.0018", "good": "0.0028", "greater": "0.0028", "disclos": "0.0037", "rebound": "0.0028", "stop": "0.0046", "break": "0.0018", "worst": "0.0028", "know": "0.0018", "press": "0.0074", "loss": "0.0175", "bar": "0.0018", "success": "0.0028", "lost": "0.0166", "outperform": "0.0018", "drop": "0.0645", "negat": "0.0037", "resolv": "0.0018", "defens": "0.0046", "benefit": "0.0055", "integr": "0.0009", "lose": "0.0101", "popular": "0.0037", "collaps": "0.0037", "crisi": "0.0101", "prevent": "0.0028", "confid": "0.0046", "slower": "0.0018", "shut": "0.0028", "slowdown": "0.0009", "strongest": "0.0018", "cost": "0.0138", "opportun": "0.0028", "fail": "0.0055", "close": "0.0286", "precipit": "0.0009", "concern": "0.0147", "lead": "0.0074", "profit": "0.0175", "defend": "0.0018", "abl": "0.0018", "bad": "0.0018", "favor": "0.0028", "restructur": "0.0074", "outstand": "0.0028", "deficit": "0.0028", "progress": "0.0009", "boost": "0.0267", "correct": "0.0018", "encourag": "0.0009", "investig": "0.0018", "advanc": "0.0461", "weak": "0.0018", "ban": "0.0028", "slow": "0.0055", "excess": "0.0009", "disput": "0.0065", "strong": "0.0018", "great": "0.0018", "deterior": "0.0018", "unemploy": "0.0009", "contract": "0.0249", "threat": "0.0018", "improv": "0.0083", "allianc": "0.0055", "suspend": "0.0046", "effici": "0.0009", "declin": "0.0811", "win": "0.0055", "bankruptci": "0.0037", "shortag": "0.0147", "cancel": "0.0055", "stabl": "0.0009", "miss": "0.0037", "drought": "0.0009", "damag": "0.0028", "bolster": "0.0037", "better": "0.0046", "question": "0.0037", "construct": "0.0147", "doubt": "0.0009", "downgrad": "0.0101", "threaten": "0.0046", "unexpect": "0.0018", "forc": "0.0065", "hurt": "0.0055", "warn": "0.0009", "gain": "0.0700", "termin": "0.0055", "eas": "0.0065", "highest": "0.0147", "fraud": "0.0028", "default": "0.0046", "seiz": "0.0065", "will": "0.0018", "limit": "0.0018", "posit": "0.0194", "problem": "0.0055", "claim": "0.0083", "weaker": "0.0009", "advantag": "0.0028", "strengthen": "0.0046", "challeng": "0.0037", "premier": "0.0009", "worri": "0.0028", "alleg": "0.0046", "critic": "0.0018", "attract": "0.0065", "sever": "0.0074", "halt": "0.0129", "strength": "0.0028", "delay": "0.0074", "fire": "0.0009", "boom": "0.0018", "reject": "0.0018", "weaken": "0.0046", "difficult": "0.0065", "tighten": "0.0018", "effect": "0.0046", "resign": "0.0009", "alert": "0.0018", "quit": "0.0009", "refin": "0.0175", "postpon": "0.0065", "stabil": "0.0009", "stress": "0.0083", "liquid": "0.0037", "antitrust": "0.0018", "stronger": "0.0018", "su": "0.0037", "inform": "0.0037", "deni": "0.0009", "achiev": "0.0009"}, "15": {"recess": "0.0051", "opposit": "0.0051", "lack": "0.0051", "protest": "0.0025", "surpass": "0.0025", "fear": "0.0051", "suffer": "0.0025", "fine": "0.0051", "accus": "0.0025", "cut": "0.0076", "depend": "0.0025", "except": "0.0025", "late": "0.0101", "arrest": "0.0025", "bailout": "0.0025", "volatil": "0.0025", "disrupt": "0.0025", "complaint": "0.0025", "good": "0.0152", "greater": "0.0051", "disclos": "0.0025", "rebound": "0.0101", "stop": "0.0025", "break": "0.0076", "worst": "0.0051", "know": "0.0152", "press": "0.0051", "loss": "0.0101", "bar": "0.0025", "success": "0.0127", "lost": "0.0101", "outperform": "0.0025", "drop": "0.0076", "negat": "0.0051", "resolv": "0.0051", "defens": "0.0076", "benefit": "0.0025", "integr": "0.0051", "lose": "0.0076", "popular": "0.0025", "collaps": "0.0025", "crisi": "0.0051", "prevent": "0.0051", "confid": "0.0051", "slower": "0.0025", "shut": "0.0051", "slowdown": "0.0025", "strongest": "0.0025", "cost": "0.0380", "opportun": "0.0025", "fail": "0.0101", "close": "0.0177", "precipit": "0.0025", "concern": "0.0076", "lead": "0.0127", "profit": "0.0152", "defend": "0.0051", "abl": "0.0101", "bad": "0.0025", "favor": "0.0025", "restructur": "0.0076", "outstand": "0.0025", "deficit": "0.0025", "progress": "0.0025", "boost": "0.0405", "correct": "0.0025", "encourag": "0.0025", "investig": "0.0025", "advanc": "0.0304", "weak": "0.0076", "ban": "0.0051", "slow": "0.0101", "excess": "0.0051", "disput": "0.0051", "strong": "0.0076", "great": "0.0025", "deterior": "0.0025", "unemploy": "0.0051", "contract": "0.0278", "threat": "0.0051", "improv": "0.0051", "allianc": "0.0025", "suspend": "0.0051", "effici": "0.0051", "declin": "0.0253", "win": "0.0051", "bankruptci": "0.0025", "shortag": "0.0025", "cancel": "0.0076", "stabl": "0.0076", "miss": "0.0025", "drought": "0.0025", "damag": "0.0025", "bolster": "0.0025", "better": "0.0025", "question": "0.0051", "construct": "0.0152", "doubt": "0.0025", "downgrad": "0.0051", "threaten": "0.0101", "unexpect": "0.0025", "forc": "0.0025", "hurt": "0.0025", "warn": "0.0025", "gain": "0.0785", "termin": "0.0101", "eas": "0.0025", "highest": "0.0051", "fraud": "0.0025", "default": "0.0051", "seiz": "0.0051", "will": "0.0025", "limit": "0.0025", "posit": "0.0253", "problem": "0.0076", "claim": "0.0025", "weaker": "0.0051", "advantag": "0.0051", "strengthen": "0.0051", "challeng": "0.0025", "premier": "0.0025", "worri": "0.0051", "alleg": "0.0025", "critic": "0.0025", "attract": "0.0127", "sever": "0.0025", "halt": "0.0076", "strength": "0.0025", "delay": "0.0076", "fire": "0.0025", "boom": "0.0051", "reject": "0.0025", "weaken": "0.0025", "difficult": "0.0051", "tighten": "0.0076", "effect": "0.0051", "resign": "0.0025", "alert": "0.0025", "quit": "0.0025", "refin": "0.0177", "postpon": "0.0025", "stabil": "0.0076", "stress": "0.0025", "liquid": "0.0051", "antitrust": "0.0025", "stronger": "0.0025", "su": "0.0127", "inform": "0.0025", "deni": "0.0051", "achiev": "0.0051"}, "16": {"recess": "0.0084", "opposit": "0.0042", "lack": "0.0042", "protest": "0.0042", "surpass": "0.0042", "fear": "0.0042", "suffer": "0.0042", "fine": "0.0042", "accus": "0.0042", "cut": "0.0042", "depend": "0.0042", "except": "0.0084", "late": "0.0042", "arrest": "0.0042", "bailout": "0.0042", "volatil": "0.0042", "disrupt": "0.0042", "complaint": "0.0042", "good": "0.0084", "greater": "0.0042", "disclos": "0.0042", "rebound": "0.0084", "stop": "0.0126", "break": "0.0042", "worst": "0.0210", "know": "0.0042", "press": "0.0042", "loss": "0.0168", "bar": "0.0042", "success": "0.0042", "lost": "0.0126", "outperform": "0.0042", "drop": "0.0294", "negat": "0.0042", "resolv": "0.0042", "defens": "0.0042", "benefit": "0.0042", "integr": "0.0042", "lose": "0.0084", "popular": "0.0042", "collaps": "0.0084", "crisi": "0.0126", "prevent": "0.0042", "confid": "0.0042", "slower": "0.0042", "shut": "0.0042", "slowdown": "0.0042", "strongest": "0.0042", "cost": "0.0084", "opportun": "0.0042", "fail": "0.0084", "close": "0.0126", "precipit": "0.0042", "concern": "0.0252", "lead": "0.0084", "profit": "0.0252", "defend": "0.0042", "abl": "0.0042", "bad": "0.0042", "favor": "0.0042", "restructur": "0.0084", "outstand": "0.0042", "deficit": "0.0084", "progress": "0.0042", "boost": "0.0042", "correct": "0.0084", "encourag": "0.0042", "investig": "0.0042", "advanc": "0.0126", "weak": "0.0042", "ban": "0.0042", "slow": "0.0042", "excess": "0.0042", "disput": "0.0042", "strong": "0.0042", "great": "0.0042", "deterior": "0.0042", "unemploy": "0.0042", "contract": "0.0168", "threat": "0.0042", "improv": "0.0084", "allianc": "0.0042", "suspend": "0.0042", "effici": "0.0042", "declin": "0.0462", "win": "0.0042", "bankruptci": "0.0042", "shortag": "0.0042", "cancel": "0.0042", "stabl": "0.0042", "miss": "0.0042", "drought": "0.0042", "damag": "0.0042", "bolster": "0.0042", "better": "0.0042", "question": "0.0042", "construct": "0.0042", "doubt": "0.0042", "downgrad": "0.0042", "threaten": "0.0042", "unexpect": "0.0042", "forc": "0.0042", "hurt": "0.0042", "warn": "0.0042", "gain": "0.0546", "termin": "0.0042", "eas": "0.0084", "highest": "0.0168", "fraud": "0.0042", "default": "0.0126", "seiz": "0.0168", "will": "0.0042", "limit": "0.0042", "posit": "0.0084", "problem": "0.0042", "claim": "0.0042", "weaker": "0.0042", "advantag": "0.0084", "strengthen": "0.0042", "challeng": "0.0042", "premier": "0.0042", "worri": "0.0042", "alleg": "0.0042", "critic": "0.0042", "attract": "0.0042", "sever": "0.0042", "halt": "0.0042", "strength": "0.0042", "delay": "0.0042", "fire": "0.0042", "boom": "0.0042", "reject": "0.0042", "weaken": "0.0126", "difficult": "0.0042", "tighten": "0.0084", "effect": "0.0042", "resign": "0.0042", "alert": "0.0042", "quit": "0.0042", "refin": "0.0084", "postpon": "0.0042", "stabil": "0.0042", "stress": "0.0042", "liquid": "0.0042", "antitrust": "0.0042", "stronger": "0.0042", "su": "0.0042", "inform": "0.0084", "deni": "0.0084", "achiev": "0.0042"}, "17": {"recess": "0.0059", "opposit": "0.0059", "lack": "0.0059", "protest": "0.0059", "surpass": "0.0059", "fear": "0.0059", "suffer": "0.0059", "fine": "0.0059", "accus": "0.0059", "cut": "0.0059", "depend": "0.0059", "except": "0.0059", "late": "0.0059", "arrest": "0.0118", "bailout": "0.0059", "volatil": "0.0059", "disrupt": "0.0059", "complaint": "0.0059", "good": "0.0059", "greater": "0.0118", "disclos": "0.0059", "rebound": "0.0059", "stop": "0.0059", "break": "0.0059", "worst": "0.0059", "know": "0.0118", "press": "0.0059", "loss": "0.0118", "bar": "0.0059", "success": "0.0059", "lost": "0.0059", "outperform": "0.0059", "drop": "0.0178", "negat": "0.0059", "resolv": "0.0059", "defens": "0.0059", "benefit": "0.0059", "integr": "0.0059", "lose": "0.0059", "popular": "0.0059", "collaps": "0.0059", "crisi": "0.0059", "prevent": "0.0118", "confid": "0.0059", "slower": "0.0059", "shut": "0.0059", "slowdown": "0.0059", "strongest": "0.0059", "cost": "0.0059", "opportun": "0.0059", "fail": "0.0059", "close": "0.0059", "precipit": "0.0059", "concern": "0.0118", "lead": "0.0059", "profit": "0.0059", "defend": "0.0059", "abl": "0.0059", "bad": "0.0059", "favor": "0.0059", "restructur": "0.0059", "outstand": "0.0059", "deficit": "0.0059", "progress": "0.0059", "boost": "0.0059", "correct": "0.0059", "encourag": "0.0059", "investig": "0.0178", "advanc": "0.0118", "weak": "0.0059", "ban": "0.0059", "slow": "0.0059", "excess": "0.0059", "disput": "0.0059", "strong": "0.0059", "great": "0.0059", "deterior": "0.0059", "unemploy": "0.0059", "contract": "0.0118", "threat": "0.0059", "improv": "0.0059", "allianc": "0.0059", "suspend": "0.0059", "effici": "0.0059", "declin": "0.0059", "win": "0.0059", "bankruptci": "0.0059", "shortag": "0.0059", "cancel": "0.0059", "stabl": "0.0059", "miss": "0.0118", "drought": "0.0059", "damag": "0.0118", "bolster": "0.0059", "better": "0.0059", "question": "0.0118", "construct": "0.0059", "doubt": "0.0059", "downgrad": "0.0059", "threaten": "0.0059", "unexpect": "0.0059", "forc": "0.0059", "hurt": "0.0059", "warn": "0.0059", "gain": "0.0059", "termin": "0.0059", "eas": "0.0059", "highest": "0.0059", "fraud": "0.0118", "default": "0.0059", "seiz": "0.0059", "will": "0.0059", "limit": "0.0059", "posit": "0.0118", "problem": "0.0059", "claim": "0.0059", "weaker": "0.0059", "advantag": "0.0059", "strengthen": "0.0059", "challeng": "0.0118", "premier": "0.0059", "worri": "0.0059", "alleg": "0.0118", "critic": "0.0059", "attract": "0.0059", "sever": "0.0059", "halt": "0.0059", "strength": "0.0059", "delay": "0.0059", "fire": "0.0059", "boom": "0.0059", "reject": "0.0059", "weaken": "0.0059", "difficult": "0.0059", "tighten": "0.0059", "effect": "0.0059", "resign": "0.0059", "alert": "0.0059", "quit": "0.0059", "refin": "0.0059", "postpon": "0.0059", "stabil": "0.0059", "stress": "0.0059", "liquid": "0.0059", "antitrust": "0.0059", "stronger": "0.0059", "su": "0.0059", "inform": "0.0059", "deni": "0.0059", "achiev": "0.0059"}, "18": {"recess": "0.0022", "opposit": "0.0022", "lack": "0.0022", "protest": "0.0022", "surpass": "0.0022", "fear": "0.0022", "suffer": "0.0022", "fine": "0.0043", "accus": "0.0022", "cut": "0.0410", "depend": "0.0022", "except": "0.0022", "late": "0.0022", "arrest": "0.0022", "bailout": "0.0022", "volatil": "0.0022", "disrupt": "0.0043", "complaint": "0.0022", "good": "0.0108", "greater": "0.0065", "disclos": "0.0022", "rebound": "0.0065", "stop": "0.0065", "break": "0.0065", "worst": "0.0043", "know": "0.0022", "press": "0.0043", "loss": "0.0173", "bar": "0.0022", "success": "0.0022", "lost": "0.0130", "outperform": "0.0043", "drop": "0.0648", "negat": "0.0022", "resolv": "0.0065", "defens": "0.0022", "benefit": "0.0043", "integr": "0.0022", "lose": "0.0086", "popular": "0.0043", "collaps": "0.0022", "crisi": "0.0151", "prevent": "0.0043", "confid": "0.0022", "slower": "0.0022", "shut": "0.0043", "slowdown": "0.0022", "strongest": "0.0022", "cost": "0.0065", "opportun": "0.0065", "fail": "0.0065", "close": "0.0130", "precipit": "0.0022", "concern": "0.0173", "lead": "0.0022", "profit": "0.0130", "defend": "0.0022", "abl": "0.0022", "bad": "0.0086", "favor": "0.0022", "restructur": "0.0043", "outstand": "0.0043", "deficit": "0.0022", "progress": "0.0022", "boost": "0.0302", "correct": "0.0022", "encourag": "0.0022", "investig": "0.0065", "advanc": "0.0346", "weak": "0.0022", "ban": "0.0043", "slow": "0.0022", "excess": "0.0022", "disput": "0.0086", "strong": "0.0022", "great": "0.0022", "deterior": "0.0022", "unemploy": "0.0022", "contract": "0.0410", "threat": "0.0022", "improv": "0.0022", "allianc": "0.0043", "suspend": "0.0108", "effici": "0.0043", "declin": "0.0583", "win": "0.0043", "bankruptci": "0.0022", "shortag": "0.0086", "cancel": "0.0065", "stabl": "0.0022", "miss": "0.0043", "drought": "0.0022", "damag": "0.0043", "bolster": "0.0043", "better": "0.0022", "question": "0.0043", "construct": "0.0086", "doubt": "0.0022", "downgrad": "0.0043", "threaten": "0.0022", "unexpect": "0.0022", "forc": "0.0065", "hurt": "0.0022", "warn": "0.0043", "gain": "0.0691", "termin": "0.0108", "eas": "0.0043", "highest": "0.0151", "fraud": "0.0043", "default": "0.0043", "seiz": "0.0065", "will": "0.0022", "limit": "0.0022", "posit": "0.0043", "problem": "0.0086", "claim": "0.0043", "weaker": "0.0022", "advantag": "0.0065", "strengthen": "0.0043", "challeng": "0.0022", "premier": "0.0043", "worri": "0.0022", "alleg": "0.0065", "critic": "0.0022", "attract": "0.0022", "sever": "0.0043", "halt": "0.0194", "strength": "0.0022", "delay": "0.0043", "fire": "0.0022", "boom": "0.0022", "reject": "0.0022", "weaken": "0.0065", "difficult": "0.0065", "tighten": "0.0043", "effect": "0.0022", "resign": "0.0022", "alert": "0.0022", "quit": "0.0022", "refin": "0.0259", "postpon": "0.0022", "stabil": "0.0065", "stress": "0.0043", "liquid": "0.0065", "antitrust": "0.0022", "stronger": "0.0043", "su": "0.0065", "inform": "0.0065", "deni": "0.0022", "achiev": "0.0022"}, "19": {"recess": "0.0037", "opposit": "0.0019", "lack": "0.0019", "protest": "0.0112", "surpass": "0.0019", "fear": "0.0019", "suffer": "0.0019", "fine": "0.0019", "accus": "0.0019", "cut": "0.0131", "depend": "0.0037", "except": "0.0037", "late": "0.0037", "arrest": "0.0037", "bailout": "0.0019", "volatil": "0.0056", "disrupt": "0.0037", "complaint": "0.0056", "good": "0.0056", "greater": "0.0037", "disclos": "0.0019", "rebound": "0.0037", "stop": "0.0093", "break": "0.0019", "worst": "0.0131", "know": "0.0037", "press": "0.0056", "loss": "0.0131", "bar": "0.0019", "success": "0.0037", "lost": "0.0056", "outperform": "0.0019", "drop": "0.0466", "negat": "0.0037", "resolv": "0.0075", "defens": "0.0037", "benefit": "0.0037", "integr": "0.0037", "lose": "0.0075", "popular": "0.0019", "collaps": "0.0037", "crisi": "0.0075", "prevent": "0.0037", "confid": "0.0019", "slower": "0.0019", "shut": "0.0037", "slowdown": "0.0037", "strongest": "0.0019", "cost": "0.0112", "opportun": "0.0075", "fail": "0.0131", "close": "0.0168", "precipit": "0.0019", "concern": "0.0149", "lead": "0.0075", "profit": "0.0112", "defend": "0.0019", "abl": "0.0037", "bad": "0.0019", "favor": "0.0019", "restructur": "0.0056", "outstand": "0.0019", "deficit": "0.0075", "progress": "0.0019", "boost": "0.0243", "correct": "0.0037", "encourag": "0.0019", "investig": "0.0093", "advanc": "0.0224", "weak": "0.0037", "ban": "0.0075", "slow": "0.0056", "excess": "0.0037", "disput": "0.0112", "strong": "0.0056", "great": "0.0019", "deterior": "0.0019", "unemploy": "0.0019", "contract": "0.0504", "threat": "0.0056", "improv": "0.0131", "allianc": "0.0019", "suspend": "0.0019", "effici": "0.0056", "declin": "0.0485", "win": "0.0019", "bankruptci": "0.0019", "shortag": "0.0037", "cancel": "0.0131", "stabl": "0.0037", "miss": "0.0019", "drought": "0.0019", "damag": "0.0056", "bolster": "0.0037", "better": "0.0075", "question": "0.0056", "construct": "0.0093", "doubt": "0.0019", "downgrad": "0.0037", "threaten": "0.0037", "unexpect": "0.0019", "forc": "0.0056", "hurt": "0.0037", "warn": "0.0019", "gain": "0.0653", "termin": "0.0056", "eas": "0.0056", "highest": "0.0168", "fraud": "0.0037", "default": "0.0149", "seiz": "0.0112", "will": "0.0037", "limit": "0.0056", "posit": "0.0056", "problem": "0.0056", "claim": "0.0056", "weaker": "0.0019", "advantag": "0.0056", "strengthen": "0.0037", "challeng": "0.0019", "premier": "0.0019", "worri": "0.0019", "alleg": "0.0037", "critic": "0.0019", "attract": "0.0149", "sever": "0.0019", "halt": "0.0224", "strength": "0.0019", "delay": "0.0075", "fire": "0.0019", "boom": "0.0019", "reject": "0.0037", "weaken": "0.0112", "difficult": "0.0019", "tighten": "0.0056", "effect": "0.0056", "resign": "0.0019", "alert": "0.0019", "quit": "0.0019", "refin": "0.0243", "postpon": "0.0019", "stabil": "0.0019", "stress": "0.0019", "liquid": "0.0056", "antitrust": "0.0019", "stronger": "0.0037", "su": "0.0056", "inform": "0.0131", "deni": "0.0037", "achiev": "0.0019"}, "20": {"recess": "0.0039", "opposit": "0.0118", "lack": "0.0039", "protest": "0.0078", "surpass": "0.0039", "fear": "0.0039", "suffer": "0.0039", "fine": "0.0039", "accus": "0.0078", "cut": "0.0078", "depend": "0.0039", "except": "0.0039", "late": "0.0196", "arrest": "0.0039", "bailout": "0.0039", "volatil": "0.0039", "disrupt": "0.0039", "complaint": "0.0039", "good": "0.0039", "greater": "0.0039", "disclos": "0.0118", "rebound": "0.0039", "stop": "0.0039", "break": "0.0039", "worst": "0.0039", "know": "0.0039", "press": "0.0039", "loss": "0.0118", "bar": "0.0039", "success": "0.0118", "lost": "0.0157", "outperform": "0.0039", "drop": "0.0196", "negat": "0.0078", "resolv": "0.0039", "defens": "0.0039", "benefit": "0.0039", "integr": "0.0039", "lose": "0.0039", "popular": "0.0039", "collaps": "0.0039", "crisi": "0.0039", "prevent": "0.0039", "confid": "0.0078", "slower": "0.0039", "shut": "0.0039", "slowdown": "0.0039", "strongest": "0.0039", "cost": "0.0039", "opportun": "0.0078", "fail": "0.0039", "close": "0.0235", "precipit": "0.0039", "concern": "0.0078", "lead": "0.0353", "profit": "0.0039", "defend": "0.0078", "abl": "0.0039", "bad": "0.0078", "favor": "0.0078", "restructur": "0.0078", "outstand": "0.0039", "deficit": "0.0039", "progress": "0.0039", "boost": "0.0078", "correct": "0.0039", "encourag": "0.0039", "investig": "0.0039", "advanc": "0.0431", "weak": "0.0039", "ban": "0.0039", "slow": "0.0078", "excess": "0.0039", "disput": "0.0118", "strong": "0.0039", "great": "0.0039", "deterior": "0.0118", "unemploy": "0.0039", "contract": "0.0078", "threat": "0.0078", "improv": "0.0118", "allianc": "0.0039", "suspend": "0.0039", "effici": "0.0039", "declin": "0.0157", "win": "0.0157", "bankruptci": "0.0039", "shortag": "0.0078", "cancel": "0.0039", "stabl": "0.0039", "miss": "0.0039", "drought": "0.0039", "damag": "0.0039", "bolster": "0.0039", "better": "0.0039", "question": "0.0078", "construct": "0.0078", "doubt": "0.0039", "downgrad": "0.0039", "threaten": "0.0118", "unexpect": "0.0039", "forc": "0.0157", "hurt": "0.0078", "warn": "0.0039", "gain": "0.0471", "termin": "0.0039", "eas": "0.0118", "highest": "0.0039", "fraud": "0.0078", "default": "0.0039", "seiz": "0.0039", "will": "0.0039", "limit": "0.0078", "posit": "0.0118", "problem": "0.0078", "claim": "0.0078", "weaker": "0.0039", "advantag": "0.0039", "strengthen": "0.0039", "challeng": "0.0039", "premier": "0.0039", "worri": "0.0039", "alleg": "0.0078", "critic": "0.0039", "attract": "0.0039", "sever": "0.0039", "halt": "0.0039", "strength": "0.0039", "delay": "0.0039", "fire": "0.0078", "boom": "0.0039", "reject": "0.0039", "weaken": "0.0039", "difficult": "0.0039", "tighten": "0.0039", "effect": "0.0039", "resign": "0.0078", "alert": "0.0039", "quit": "0.0039", "refin": "0.0078", "postpon": "0.0118", "stabil": "0.0039", "stress": "0.0039", "liquid": "0.0039", "antitrust": "0.0039", "stronger": "0.0039", "su": "0.0039", "inform": "0.0078", "deni": "0.0078", "achiev": "0.0039"}}, "MEXBOL": {"1": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "2": {"recess": "0.0201", "opposit": "0.0050", "lack": "0.0050", "protest": "0.0050", "surpass": "0.0050", "fear": "0.0050", "suffer": "0.0050", "fine": "0.0050", "accus": "0.0050", "cut": "0.0151", "depend": "0.0050", "except": "0.0050", "late": "0.0050", "arrest": "0.0050", "bailout": "0.0050", "volatil": "0.0050", "disrupt": "0.0050", "complaint": "0.0050", "good": "0.0050", "greater": "0.0050", "disclos": "0.0101", "rebound": "0.0050", "stop": "0.0050", "break": "0.0050", "worst": "0.0050", "know": "0.0050", "press": "0.0101", "loss": "0.0050", "bar": "0.0050", "success": "0.0050", "lost": "0.0050", "outperform": "0.0050", "drop": "0.0101", "negat": "0.0050", "resolv": "0.0050", "defens": "0.0050", "benefit": "0.0050", "integr": "0.0101", "lose": "0.0050", "popular": "0.0050", "collaps": "0.0050", "crisi": "0.0101", "prevent": "0.0101", "confid": "0.0050", "slower": "0.0050", "shut": "0.0050", "slowdown": "0.0050", "strongest": "0.0050", "cost": "0.0050", "opportun": "0.0251", "fail": "0.0050", "close": "0.0101", "precipit": "0.0050", "concern": "0.0050", "lead": "0.0050", "profit": "0.0050", "defend": "0.0050", "abl": "0.0050", "bad": "0.0050", "favor": "0.0101", "restructur": "0.0050", "outstand": "0.0101", "deficit": "0.0050", "progress": "0.0050", "boost": "0.0101", "correct": "0.0101", "encourag": "0.0050", "investig": "0.0050", "advanc": "0.0101", "weak": "0.0050", "ban": "0.0050", "slow": "0.0050", "excess": "0.0050", "disput": "0.0050", "strong": "0.0101", "great": "0.0050", "deterior": "0.0050", "unemploy": "0.0101", "contract": "0.0050", "threat": "0.0050", "improv": "0.0050", "allianc": "0.0050", "suspend": "0.0101", "effici": "0.0101", "declin": "0.0101", "win": "0.0050", "bankruptci": "0.0050", "shortag": "0.0050", "cancel": "0.0050", "stabl": "0.0050", "miss": "0.0050", "drought": "0.0050", "damag": "0.0050", "bolster": "0.0050", "better": "0.0050", "question": "0.0101", "construct": "0.0050", "doubt": "0.0151", "downgrad": "0.0050", "threaten": "0.0050", "unexpect": "0.0050", "forc": "0.0151", "hurt": "0.0151", "warn": "0.0050", "gain": "0.0101", "termin": "0.0050", "eas": "0.0101", "highest": "0.0050", "fraud": "0.0050", "default": "0.0050", "seiz": "0.0050", "will": "0.0050", "limit": "0.0050", "posit": "0.0050", "problem": "0.0050", "claim": "0.0050", "weaker": "0.0050", "advantag": "0.0050", "strengthen": "0.0101", "challeng": "0.0101", "premier": "0.0050", "worri": "0.0050", "alleg": "0.0151", "critic": "0.0050", "attract": "0.0050", "sever": "0.0101", "halt": "0.0101", "strength": "0.0050", "delay": "0.0050", "fire": "0.0050", "boom": "0.0050", "reject": "0.0050", "weaken": "0.0101", "difficult": "0.0050", "tighten": "0.0050", "effect": "0.0201", "resign": "0.0050", "alert": "0.0050", "quit": "0.0050", "refin": "0.0050", "postpon": "0.0050", "stabil": "0.0050", "stress": "0.0050", "liquid": "0.0151", "antitrust": "0.0050", "stronger": "0.0050", "su": "0.0050", "inform": "0.0151", "deni": "0.0050", "achiev": "0.0050"}, "3": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "4": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "5": {"recess": "0.0051", "opposit": "0.0051", "lack": "0.0051", "protest": "0.0051", "surpass": "0.0051", "fear": "0.0051", "suffer": "0.0051", "fine": "0.0051", "accus": "0.0051", "cut": "0.0203", "depend": "0.0051", "except": "0.0051", "late": "0.0051", "arrest": "0.0051", "bailout": "0.0051", "volatil": "0.0102", "disrupt": "0.0051", "complaint": "0.0051", "good": "0.0051", "greater": "0.0051", "disclos": "0.0051", "rebound": "0.0051", "stop": "0.0051", "break": "0.0051", "worst": "0.0051", "know": "0.0051", "press": "0.0152", "loss": "0.0051", "bar": "0.0051", "success": "0.0051", "lost": "0.0051", "outperform": "0.0051", "drop": "0.0102", "negat": "0.0051", "resolv": "0.0051", "defens": "0.0051", "benefit": "0.0051", "integr": "0.0051", "lose": "0.0051", "popular": "0.0051", "collaps": "0.0051", "crisi": "0.0051", "prevent": "0.0051", "confid": "0.0051", "slower": "0.0051", "shut": "0.0102", "slowdown": "0.0051", "strongest": "0.0051", "cost": "0.0102", "opportun": "0.0051", "fail": "0.0051", "close": "0.0203", "precipit": "0.0051", "concern": "0.0051", "lead": "0.0102", "profit": "0.0102", "defend": "0.0051", "abl": "0.0102", "bad": "0.0051", "favor": "0.0051", "restructur": "0.0051", "outstand": "0.0051", "deficit": "0.0051", "progress": "0.0051", "boost": "0.0102", "correct": "0.0051", "encourag": "0.0051", "investig": "0.0051", "advanc": "0.0254", "weak": "0.0102", "ban": "0.0051", "slow": "0.0051", "excess": "0.0051", "disput": "0.0051", "strong": "0.0051", "great": "0.0051", "deterior": "0.0051", "unemploy": "0.0051", "contract": "0.0051", "threat": "0.0102", "improv": "0.0102", "allianc": "0.0051", "suspend": "0.0051", "effici": "0.0051", "declin": "0.0203", "win": "0.0102", "bankruptci": "0.0102", "shortag": "0.0051", "cancel": "0.0051", "stabl": "0.0102", "miss": "0.0102", "drought": "0.0051", "damag": "0.0051", "bolster": "0.0051", "better": "0.0102", "question": "0.0051", "construct": "0.0102", "doubt": "0.0051", "downgrad": "0.0051", "threaten": "0.0051", "unexpect": "0.0051", "forc": "0.0051", "hurt": "0.0051", "warn": "0.0051", "gain": "0.0508", "termin": "0.0051", "eas": "0.0051", "highest": "0.0102", "fraud": "0.0051", "default": "0.0152", "seiz": "0.0051", "will": "0.0051", "limit": "0.0051", "posit": "0.0051", "problem": "0.0051", "claim": "0.0051", "weaker": "0.0051", "advantag": "0.0102", "strengthen": "0.0051", "challeng": "0.0051", "premier": "0.0051", "worri": "0.0051", "alleg": "0.0051", "critic": "0.0051", "attract": "0.0051", "sever": "0.0051", "halt": "0.0051", "strength": "0.0051", "delay": "0.0051", "fire": "0.0051", "boom": "0.0051", "reject": "0.0051", "weaken": "0.0051", "difficult": "0.0051", "tighten": "0.0051", "effect": "0.0051", "resign": "0.0051", "alert": "0.0051", "quit": "0.0051", "refin": "0.0051", "postpon": "0.0051", "stabil": "0.0102", "stress": "0.0051", "liquid": "0.0051", "antitrust": "0.0051", "stronger": "0.0051", "su": "0.0051", "inform": "0.0102", "deni": "0.0051", "achiev": "0.0051"}, "6": {"recess": "0.0034", "opposit": "0.0034", "lack": "0.0068", "protest": "0.0034", "surpass": "0.0034", "fear": "0.0034", "suffer": "0.0034", "fine": "0.0068", "accus": "0.0034", "cut": "0.0238", "depend": "0.0034", "except": "0.0034", "late": "0.0068", "arrest": "0.0034", "bailout": "0.0102", "volatil": "0.0034", "disrupt": "0.0034", "complaint": "0.0034", "good": "0.0034", "greater": "0.0034", "disclos": "0.0034", "rebound": "0.0034", "stop": "0.0034", "break": "0.0034", "worst": "0.0034", "know": "0.0034", "press": "0.0068", "loss": "0.0170", "bar": "0.0034", "success": "0.0034", "lost": "0.0068", "outperform": "0.0034", "drop": "0.0374", "negat": "0.0034", "resolv": "0.0034", "defens": "0.0034", "benefit": "0.0068", "integr": "0.0034", "lose": "0.0102", "popular": "0.0034", "collaps": "0.0068", "crisi": "0.0102", "prevent": "0.0034", "confid": "0.0034", "slower": "0.0034", "shut": "0.0034", "slowdown": "0.0068", "strongest": "0.0034", "cost": "0.0306", "opportun": "0.0068", "fail": "0.0034", "close": "0.0170", "precipit": "0.0034", "concern": "0.0238", "lead": "0.0102", "profit": "0.0170", "defend": "0.0034", "abl": "0.0102", "bad": "0.0034", "favor": "0.0068", "restructur": "0.0034", "outstand": "0.0034", "deficit": "0.0068", "progress": "0.0034", "boost": "0.0102", "correct": "0.0034", "encourag": "0.0034", "investig": "0.0034", "advanc": "0.0170", "weak": "0.0034", "ban": "0.0034", "slow": "0.0068", "excess": "0.0034", "disput": "0.0034", "strong": "0.0068", "great": "0.0068", "deterior": "0.0034", "unemploy": "0.0068", "contract": "0.0068", "threat": "0.0034", "improv": "0.0068", "allianc": "0.0034", "suspend": "0.0034", "effici": "0.0034", "declin": "0.0612", "win": "0.0102", "bankruptci": "0.0068", "shortag": "0.0034", "cancel": "0.0034", "stabl": "0.0034", "miss": "0.0034", "drought": "0.0034", "damag": "0.0034", "bolster": "0.0034", "better": "0.0034", "question": "0.0034", "construct": "0.0068", "doubt": "0.0034", "downgrad": "0.0034", "threaten": "0.0034", "unexpect": "0.0034", "forc": "0.0136", "hurt": "0.0068", "warn": "0.0034", "gain": "0.0408", "termin": "0.0034", "eas": "0.0136", "highest": "0.0068", "fraud": "0.0034", "default": "0.0068", "seiz": "0.0034", "will": "0.0034", "limit": "0.0068", "posit": "0.0034", "problem": "0.0034", "claim": "0.0034", "weaker": "0.0034", "advantag": "0.0102", "strengthen": "0.0068", "challeng": "0.0170", "premier": "0.0034", "worri": "0.0136", "alleg": "0.0034", "critic": "0.0068", "attract": "0.0068", "sever": "0.0068", "halt": "0.0034", "strength": "0.0034", "delay": "0.0068", "fire": "0.0034", "boom": "0.0034", "reject": "0.0068", "weaken": "0.0068", "difficult": "0.0034", "tighten": "0.0034", "effect": "0.0068", "resign": "0.0034", "alert": "0.0034", "quit": "0.0068", "refin": "0.0034", "postpon": "0.0034", "stabil": "0.0034", "stress": "0.0034", "liquid": "0.0034", "antitrust": "0.0170", "stronger": "0.0068", "su": "0.0068", "inform": "0.0102", "deni": "0.0068", "achiev": "0.0034"}, "7": {"recess": "0.0049", "opposit": "0.0049", "lack": "0.0049", "protest": "0.0049", "surpass": "0.0049", "fear": "0.0049", "suffer": "0.0099", "fine": "0.0049", "accus": "0.0148", "cut": "0.0148", "depend": "0.0049", "except": "0.0049", "late": "0.0049", "arrest": "0.0049", "bailout": "0.0049", "volatil": "0.0049", "disrupt": "0.0049", "complaint": "0.0099", "good": "0.0099", "greater": "0.0049", "disclos": "0.0049", "rebound": "0.0049", "stop": "0.0099", "break": "0.0049", "worst": "0.0049", "know": "0.0049", "press": "0.0049", "loss": "0.0099", "bar": "0.0099", "success": "0.0049", "lost": "0.0099", "outperform": "0.0049", "drop": "0.0296", "negat": "0.0049", "resolv": "0.0049", "defens": "0.0049", "benefit": "0.0049", "integr": "0.0049", "lose": "0.0049", "popular": "0.0049", "collaps": "0.0049", "crisi": "0.0049", "prevent": "0.0049", "confid": "0.0049", "slower": "0.0049", "shut": "0.0049", "slowdown": "0.0049", "strongest": "0.0049", "cost": "0.0049", "opportun": "0.0049", "fail": "0.0049", "close": "0.0148", "precipit": "0.0049", "concern": "0.0049", "lead": "0.0049", "profit": "0.0197", "defend": "0.0049", "abl": "0.0049", "bad": "0.0148", "favor": "0.0049", "restructur": "0.0099", "outstand": "0.0049", "deficit": "0.0049", "progress": "0.0049", "boost": "0.0049", "correct": "0.0049", "encourag": "0.0049", "investig": "0.0049", "advanc": "0.0049", "weak": "0.0049", "ban": "0.0049", "slow": "0.0099", "excess": "0.0049", "disput": "0.0197", "strong": "0.0049", "great": "0.0049", "deterior": "0.0049", "unemploy": "0.0049", "contract": "0.0099", "threat": "0.0148", "improv": "0.0049", "allianc": "0.0049", "suspend": "0.0049", "effici": "0.0049", "declin": "0.0197", "win": "0.0099", "bankruptci": "0.0246", "shortag": "0.0049", "cancel": "0.0099", "stabl": "0.0099", "miss": "0.0049", "drought": "0.0049", "damag": "0.0049", "bolster": "0.0049", "better": "0.0049", "question": "0.0049", "construct": "0.0049", "doubt": "0.0049", "downgrad": "0.0049", "threaten": "0.0049", "unexpect": "0.0049", "forc": "0.0049", "hurt": "0.0099", "warn": "0.0049", "gain": "0.0099", "termin": "0.0049", "eas": "0.0049", "highest": "0.0099", "fraud": "0.0049", "default": "0.0049", "seiz": "0.0099", "will": "0.0049", "limit": "0.0099", "posit": "0.0049", "problem": "0.0049", "claim": "0.0049", "weaker": "0.0049", "advantag": "0.0049", "strengthen": "0.0099", "challeng": "0.0148", "premier": "0.0049", "worri": "0.0049", "alleg": "0.0049", "critic": "0.0049", "attract": "0.0049", "sever": "0.0099", "halt": "0.0148", "strength": "0.0049", "delay": "0.0049", "fire": "0.0049", "boom": "0.0049", "reject": "0.0049", "weaken": "0.0049", "difficult": "0.0049", "tighten": "0.0049", "effect": "0.0049", "resign": "0.0049", "alert": "0.0049", "quit": "0.0049", "refin": "0.0049", "postpon": "0.0049", "stabil": "0.0049", "stress": "0.0049", "liquid": "0.0049", "antitrust": "0.0099", "stronger": "0.0049", "su": "0.0049", "inform": "0.0049", "deni": "0.0049", "achiev": "0.0049"}, "8": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "9": {"recess": "0.0016", "opposit": "0.0016", "lack": "0.0079", "protest": "0.0016", "surpass": "0.0016", "fear": "0.0016", "suffer": "0.0016", "fine": "0.0159", "accus": "0.0079", "cut": "0.0349", "depend": "0.0016", "except": "0.0016", "late": "0.0063", "arrest": "0.0063", "bailout": "0.0016", "volatil": "0.0016", "disrupt": "0.0016", "complaint": "0.0079", "good": "0.0079", "greater": "0.0048", "disclos": "0.0095", "rebound": "0.0032", "stop": "0.0095", "break": "0.0016", "worst": "0.0063", "know": "0.0016", "press": "0.0095", "loss": "0.0111", "bar": "0.0127", "success": "0.0063", "lost": "0.0111", "outperform": "0.0016", "drop": "0.0397", "negat": "0.0048", "resolv": "0.0095", "defens": "0.0063", "benefit": "0.0032", "integr": "0.0016", "lose": "0.0016", "popular": "0.0016", "collaps": "0.0016", "crisi": "0.0032", "prevent": "0.0063", "confid": "0.0032", "slower": "0.0016", "shut": "0.0048", "slowdown": "0.0016", "strongest": "0.0016", "cost": "0.0175", "opportun": "0.0063", "fail": "0.0063", "close": "0.0159", "precipit": "0.0016", "concern": "0.0063", "lead": "0.0063", "profit": "0.0302", "defend": "0.0048", "abl": "0.0111", "bad": "0.0032", "favor": "0.0127", "restructur": "0.0016", "outstand": "0.0016", "deficit": "0.0016", "progress": "0.0016", "boost": "0.0111", "correct": "0.0016", "encourag": "0.0032", "investig": "0.0016", "advanc": "0.0095", "weak": "0.0048", "ban": "0.0095", "slow": "0.0016", "excess": "0.0016", "disput": "0.0254", "strong": "0.0048", "great": "0.0063", "deterior": "0.0032", "unemploy": "0.0016", "contract": "0.0079", "threat": "0.0032", "improv": "0.0079", "allianc": "0.0016", "suspend": "0.0016", "effici": "0.0032", "declin": "0.0635", "win": "0.0159", "bankruptci": "0.0063", "shortag": "0.0016", "cancel": "0.0048", "stabl": "0.0016", "miss": "0.0016", "drought": "0.0016", "damag": "0.0063", "bolster": "0.0032", "better": "0.0095", "question": "0.0016", "construct": "0.0016", "doubt": "0.0032", "downgrad": "0.0032", "threaten": "0.0032", "unexpect": "0.0032", "forc": "0.0111", "hurt": "0.0048", "warn": "0.0016", "gain": "0.0492", "termin": "0.0048", "eas": "0.0032", "highest": "0.0095", "fraud": "0.0111", "default": "0.0048", "seiz": "0.0016", "will": "0.0048", "limit": "0.0175", "posit": "0.0111", "problem": "0.0016", "claim": "0.0127", "weaker": "0.0016", "advantag": "0.0016", "strengthen": "0.0048", "challeng": "0.0175", "premier": "0.0016", "worri": "0.0063", "alleg": "0.0079", "critic": "0.0063", "attract": "0.0079", "sever": "0.0032", "halt": "0.0063", "strength": "0.0016", "delay": "0.0032", "fire": "0.0016", "boom": "0.0016", "reject": "0.0079", "weaken": "0.0032", "difficult": "0.0032", "tighten": "0.0016", "effect": "0.0048", "resign": "0.0032", "alert": "0.0016", "quit": "0.0016", "refin": "0.0016", "postpon": "0.0016", "stabil": "0.0016", "stress": "0.0016", "liquid": "0.0095", "antitrust": "0.0302", "stronger": "0.0032", "su": "0.0127", "inform": "0.0175", "deni": "0.0032", "achiev": "0.0032"}, "10": {"recess": "0.0034", "opposit": "0.0068", "lack": "0.0034", "protest": "0.0034", "surpass": "0.0034", "fear": "0.0034", "suffer": "0.0034", "fine": "0.0034", "accus": "0.0034", "cut": "0.0137", "depend": "0.0068", "except": "0.0068", "late": "0.0034", "arrest": "0.0034", "bailout": "0.0034", "volatil": "0.0034", "disrupt": "0.0034", "complaint": "0.0068", "good": "0.0205", "greater": "0.0034", "disclos": "0.0137", "rebound": "0.0068", "stop": "0.0068", "break": "0.0034", "worst": "0.0068", "know": "0.0068", "press": "0.0034", "loss": "0.0240", "bar": "0.0034", "success": "0.0034", "lost": "0.0068", "outperform": "0.0034", "drop": "0.0205", "negat": "0.0034", "resolv": "0.0034", "defens": "0.0034", "benefit": "0.0171", "integr": "0.0034", "lose": "0.0068", "popular": "0.0034", "collaps": "0.0034", "crisi": "0.0034", "prevent": "0.0034", "confid": "0.0034", "slower": "0.0034", "shut": "0.0034", "slowdown": "0.0068", "strongest": "0.0068", "cost": "0.0137", "opportun": "0.0171", "fail": "0.0034", "close": "0.0171", "precipit": "0.0034", "concern": "0.0068", "lead": "0.0034", "profit": "0.0582", "defend": "0.0034", "abl": "0.0068", "bad": "0.0034", "favor": "0.0068", "restructur": "0.0103", "outstand": "0.0034", "deficit": "0.0034", "progress": "0.0034", "boost": "0.0068", "correct": "0.0034", "encourag": "0.0034", "investig": "0.0034", "advanc": "0.0205", "weak": "0.0068", "ban": "0.0034", "slow": "0.0068", "excess": "0.0034", "disput": "0.0034", "strong": "0.0034", "great": "0.0034", "deterior": "0.0068", "unemploy": "0.0034", "contract": "0.0137", "threat": "0.0034", "improv": "0.0103", "allianc": "0.0034", "suspend": "0.0068", "effici": "0.0034", "declin": "0.0377", "win": "0.0068", "bankruptci": "0.0034", "shortag": "0.0068", "cancel": "0.0034", "stabl": "0.0034", "miss": "0.0068", "drought": "0.0034", "damag": "0.0034", "bolster": "0.0034", "better": "0.0103", "question": "0.0034", "construct": "0.0205", "doubt": "0.0034", "downgrad": "0.0034", "threaten": "0.0034", "unexpect": "0.0034", "forc": "0.0034", "hurt": "0.0137", "warn": "0.0034", "gain": "0.0445", "termin": "0.0034", "eas": "0.0034", "highest": "0.0103", "fraud": "0.0034", "default": "0.0068", "seiz": "0.0034", "will": "0.0034", "limit": "0.0034", "posit": "0.0068", "problem": "0.0034", "claim": "0.0137", "weaker": "0.0034", "advantag": "0.0103", "strengthen": "0.0034", "challeng": "0.0034", "premier": "0.0034", "worri": "0.0034", "alleg": "0.0034", "critic": "0.0034", "attract": "0.0103", "sever": "0.0068", "halt": "0.0103", "strength": "0.0034", "delay": "0.0034", "fire": "0.0034", "boom": "0.0034", "reject": "0.0034", "weaken": "0.0034", "difficult": "0.0103", "tighten": "0.0034", "effect": "0.0034", "resign": "0.0034", "alert": "0.0034", "quit": "0.0034", "refin": "0.0034", "postpon": "0.0034", "stabil": "0.0034", "stress": "0.0034", "liquid": "0.0068", "antitrust": "0.0103", "stronger": "0.0034", "su": "0.0034", "inform": "0.0137", "deni": "0.0034", "achiev": "0.0034"}, "11": {"recess": "0.0064", "opposit": "0.0021", "lack": "0.0107", "protest": "0.0021", "surpass": "0.0043", "fear": "0.0021", "suffer": "0.0021", "fine": "0.0215", "accus": "0.0043", "cut": "0.0236", "depend": "0.0064", "except": "0.0021", "late": "0.0021", "arrest": "0.0021", "bailout": "0.0021", "volatil": "0.0021", "disrupt": "0.0021", "complaint": "0.0129", "good": "0.0172", "greater": "0.0086", "disclos": "0.0150", "rebound": "0.0043", "stop": "0.0021", "break": "0.0043", "worst": "0.0086", "know": "0.0021", "press": "0.0021", "loss": "0.0107", "bar": "0.0107", "success": "0.0064", "lost": "0.0129", "outperform": "0.0021", "drop": "0.0322", "negat": "0.0043", "resolv": "0.0021", "defens": "0.0021", "benefit": "0.0064", "integr": "0.0043", "lose": "0.0021", "popular": "0.0021", "collaps": "0.0064", "crisi": "0.0064", "prevent": "0.0107", "confid": "0.0064", "slower": "0.0021", "shut": "0.0021", "slowdown": "0.0021", "strongest": "0.0043", "cost": "0.0107", "opportun": "0.0172", "fail": "0.0215", "close": "0.0107", "precipit": "0.0021", "concern": "0.0064", "lead": "0.0107", "profit": "0.0150", "defend": "0.0043", "abl": "0.0107", "bad": "0.0043", "favor": "0.0064", "restructur": "0.0021", "outstand": "0.0021", "deficit": "0.0021", "progress": "0.0021", "boost": "0.0107", "correct": "0.0021", "encourag": "0.0043", "investig": "0.0172", "advanc": "0.0150", "weak": "0.0021", "ban": "0.0107", "slow": "0.0043", "excess": "0.0043", "disput": "0.0021", "strong": "0.0086", "great": "0.0043", "deterior": "0.0064", "unemploy": "0.0021", "contract": "0.0107", "threat": "0.0021", "improv": "0.0129", "allianc": "0.0021", "suspend": "0.0043", "effici": "0.0021", "declin": "0.0279", "win": "0.0086", "bankruptci": "0.0043", "shortag": "0.0021", "cancel": "0.0021", "stabl": "0.0021", "miss": "0.0064", "drought": "0.0021", "damag": "0.0021", "bolster": "0.0021", "better": "0.0107", "question": "0.0021", "construct": "0.0021", "doubt": "0.0021", "downgrad": "0.0021", "threaten": "0.0043", "unexpect": "0.0021", "forc": "0.0043", "hurt": "0.0107", "warn": "0.0021", "gain": "0.0665", "termin": "0.0086", "eas": "0.0021", "highest": "0.0086", "fraud": "0.0021", "default": "0.0043", "seiz": "0.0021", "will": "0.0021", "limit": "0.0086", "posit": "0.0129", "problem": "0.0064", "claim": "0.0086", "weaker": "0.0021", "advantag": "0.0043", "strengthen": "0.0043", "challeng": "0.0064", "premier": "0.0043", "worri": "0.0043", "alleg": "0.0021", "critic": "0.0043", "attract": "0.0064", "sever": "0.0064", "halt": "0.0043", "strength": "0.0021", "delay": "0.0086", "fire": "0.0021", "boom": "0.0021", "reject": "0.0129", "weaken": "0.0021", "difficult": "0.0021", "tighten": "0.0021", "effect": "0.0086", "resign": "0.0043", "alert": "0.0043", "quit": "0.0021", "refin": "0.0021", "postpon": "0.0021", "stabil": "0.0086", "stress": "0.0043", "liquid": "0.0021", "antitrust": "0.0343", "stronger": "0.0064", "su": "0.0021", "inform": "0.0129", "deni": "0.0086", "achiev": "0.0043"}, "12": {"recess": "0.0013", "opposit": "0.0013", "lack": "0.0053", "protest": "0.0013", "surpass": "0.0027", "fear": "0.0027", "suffer": "0.0027", "fine": "0.0160", "accus": "0.0080", "cut": "0.0093", "depend": "0.0027", "except": "0.0013", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0080", "bailout": "0.0013", "volatil": "0.0013", "disrupt": "0.0013", "complaint": "0.0173", "good": "0.0027", "greater": "0.0027", "disclos": "0.0093", "rebound": "0.0040", "stop": "0.0053", "break": "0.0013", "worst": "0.0027", "know": "0.0040", "press": "0.0053", "loss": "0.0080", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0027", "lost": "0.0147", "outperform": "0.0013", "drop": "0.0293", "negat": "0.0013", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0040", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0013", "lose": "0.0027", "popular": "0.0013", "collaps": "0.0027", "crisi": "0.0027", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0013", "slower": "0.0013", "shut": "0.0027", "slowdown": "0.0013", "strongest": "0.0027", "cost": "0.0107", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0080", "close": "0.0160", "precipit": "0.0013", "concern": "0.0093", "lead": "0.0053", "profit": "0.0293", "defend": "0.0053", "abl": "0.0013", "bad": "0.0027", "favor": "0.0040", "restructur": "0.0040", "outstand": "0.0040", "deficit": "0.0040", "progress": "0.0013", "boost": "0.0080", "correct": "0.0013", "encourag": "0.0027", "investig": "0.0133", "advanc": "0.0187", "weak": "0.0027", "ban": "0.0120", "slow": "0.0027", "excess": "0.0013", "disput": "0.0133", "strong": "0.0053", "great": "0.0040", "deterior": "0.0040", "unemploy": "0.0027", "contract": "0.0093", "threat": "0.0013", "improv": "0.0053", "allianc": "0.0013", "suspend": "0.0040", "effici": "0.0027", "declin": "0.0760", "win": "0.0080", "bankruptci": "0.0120", "shortag": "0.0013", "cancel": "0.0040", "stabl": "0.0013", "miss": "0.0053", "drought": "0.0013", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0013", "better": "0.0053", "question": "0.0027", "construct": "0.0040", "doubt": "0.0013", "downgrad": "0.0013", "threaten": "0.0053", "unexpect": "0.0027", "forc": "0.0080", "hurt": "0.0107", "warn": "0.0013", "gain": "0.0560", "termin": "0.0080", "eas": "0.0027", "highest": "0.0147", "fraud": "0.0120", "default": "0.0080", "seiz": "0.0013", "will": "0.0027", "limit": "0.0120", "posit": "0.0107", "problem": "0.0093", "claim": "0.0400", "weaker": "0.0013", "advantag": "0.0013", "strengthen": "0.0053", "challeng": "0.0040", "premier": "0.0027", "worri": "0.0027", "alleg": "0.0173", "critic": "0.0027", "attract": "0.0027", "sever": "0.0053", "halt": "0.0093", "strength": "0.0040", "delay": "0.0040", "fire": "0.0013", "boom": "0.0013", "reject": "0.0240", "weaken": "0.0013", "difficult": "0.0053", "tighten": "0.0013", "effect": "0.0107", "resign": "0.0027", "alert": "0.0013", "quit": "0.0013", "refin": "0.0027", "postpon": "0.0013", "stabil": "0.0013", "stress": "0.0013", "liquid": "0.0053", "antitrust": "0.0293", "stronger": "0.0013", "su": "0.0120", "inform": "0.0227", "deni": "0.0053", "achiev": "0.0013"}, "13": {"recess": "0.0056", "opposit": "0.0056", "lack": "0.0111", "protest": "0.0056", "surpass": "0.0056", "fear": "0.0056", "suffer": "0.0056", "fine": "0.0056", "accus": "0.0056", "cut": "0.0111", "depend": "0.0056", "except": "0.0056", "late": "0.0056", "arrest": "0.0056", "bailout": "0.0056", "volatil": "0.0056", "disrupt": "0.0056", "complaint": "0.0056", "good": "0.0056", "greater": "0.0056", "disclos": "0.0056", "rebound": "0.0056", "stop": "0.0056", "break": "0.0056", "worst": "0.0056", "know": "0.0056", "press": "0.0111", "loss": "0.0056", "bar": "0.0056", "success": "0.0056", "lost": "0.0111", "outperform": "0.0056", "drop": "0.0111", "negat": "0.0056", "resolv": "0.0056", "defens": "0.0056", "benefit": "0.0056", "integr": "0.0056", "lose": "0.0056", "popular": "0.0056", "collaps": "0.0056", "crisi": "0.0056", "prevent": "0.0056", "confid": "0.0056", "slower": "0.0056", "shut": "0.0056", "slowdown": "0.0056", "strongest": "0.0056", "cost": "0.0278", "opportun": "0.0111", "fail": "0.0056", "close": "0.0056", "precipit": "0.0056", "concern": "0.0222", "lead": "0.0056", "profit": "0.0222", "defend": "0.0056", "abl": "0.0111", "bad": "0.0056", "favor": "0.0056", "restructur": "0.0056", "outstand": "0.0056", "deficit": "0.0056", "progress": "0.0056", "boost": "0.0111", "correct": "0.0056", "encourag": "0.0056", "investig": "0.0056", "advanc": "0.0056", "weak": "0.0056", "ban": "0.0056", "slow": "0.0056", "excess": "0.0056", "disput": "0.0056", "strong": "0.0056", "great": "0.0056", "deterior": "0.0056", "unemploy": "0.0056", "contract": "0.0111", "threat": "0.0056", "improv": "0.0056", "allianc": "0.0056", "suspend": "0.0056", "effici": "0.0056", "declin": "0.0167", "win": "0.0111", "bankruptci": "0.0056", "shortag": "0.0056", "cancel": "0.0056", "stabl": "0.0056", "miss": "0.0056", "drought": "0.0056", "damag": "0.0056", "bolster": "0.0056", "better": "0.0056", "question": "0.0056", "construct": "0.0056", "doubt": "0.0056", "downgrad": "0.0056", "threaten": "0.0056", "unexpect": "0.0056", "forc": "0.0111", "hurt": "0.0056", "warn": "0.0056", "gain": "0.0056", "termin": "0.0056", "eas": "0.0056", "highest": "0.0056", "fraud": "0.0056", "default": "0.0056", "seiz": "0.0056", "will": "0.0056", "limit": "0.0056", "posit": "0.0056", "problem": "0.0056", "claim": "0.0056", "weaker": "0.0056", "advantag": "0.0056", "strengthen": "0.0056", "challeng": "0.0056", "premier": "0.0056", "worri": "0.0167", "alleg": "0.0056", "critic": "0.0056", "attract": "0.0111", "sever": "0.0056", "halt": "0.0056", "strength": "0.0056", "delay": "0.0056", "fire": "0.0056", "boom": "0.0056", "reject": "0.0056", "weaken": "0.0056", "difficult": "0.0056", "tighten": "0.0056", "effect": "0.0111", "resign": "0.0056", "alert": "0.0056", "quit": "0.0056", "refin": "0.0056", "postpon": "0.0056", "stabil": "0.0056", "stress": "0.0056", "liquid": "0.0056", "antitrust": "0.0111", "stronger": "0.0111", "su": "0.0111", "inform": "0.0056", "deni": "0.0056", "achiev": "0.0056"}, "14": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "15": {"recess": "0.0012", "opposit": "0.0012", "lack": "0.0012", "protest": "0.0012", "surpass": "0.0035", "fear": "0.0012", "suffer": "0.0012", "fine": "0.0094", "accus": "0.0035", "cut": "0.0316", "depend": "0.0023", "except": "0.0012", "late": "0.0047", "arrest": "0.0012", "bailout": "0.0012", "volatil": "0.0035", "disrupt": "0.0012", "complaint": "0.0082", "good": "0.0070", "greater": "0.0035", "disclos": "0.0047", "rebound": "0.0059", "stop": "0.0082", "break": "0.0035", "worst": "0.0023", "know": "0.0035", "press": "0.0082", "loss": "0.0234", "bar": "0.0082", "success": "0.0023", "lost": "0.0234", "outperform": "0.0012", "drop": "0.0480", "negat": "0.0047", "resolv": "0.0059", "defens": "0.0023", "benefit": "0.0035", "integr": "0.0012", "lose": "0.0047", "popular": "0.0023", "collaps": "0.0023", "crisi": "0.0047", "prevent": "0.0023", "confid": "0.0059", "slower": "0.0012", "shut": "0.0035", "slowdown": "0.0023", "strongest": "0.0012", "cost": "0.0176", "opportun": "0.0035", "fail": "0.0082", "close": "0.0246", "precipit": "0.0012", "concern": "0.0117", "lead": "0.0082", "profit": "0.0386", "defend": "0.0047", "abl": "0.0070", "bad": "0.0012", "favor": "0.0059", "restructur": "0.0012", "outstand": "0.0047", "deficit": "0.0059", "progress": "0.0012", "boost": "0.0094", "correct": "0.0012", "encourag": "0.0035", "investig": "0.0141", "advanc": "0.0176", "weak": "0.0047", "ban": "0.0047", "slow": "0.0035", "excess": "0.0012", "disput": "0.0129", "strong": "0.0023", "great": "0.0012", "deterior": "0.0023", "unemploy": "0.0023", "contract": "0.0117", "threat": "0.0047", "improv": "0.0141", "allianc": "0.0012", "suspend": "0.0012", "effici": "0.0012", "declin": "0.0691", "win": "0.0082", "bankruptci": "0.0082", "shortag": "0.0012", "cancel": "0.0059", "stabl": "0.0035", "miss": "0.0047", "drought": "0.0012", "damag": "0.0023", "bolster": "0.0023", "better": "0.0105", "question": "0.0023", "construct": "0.0059", "doubt": "0.0012", "downgrad": "0.0023", "threaten": "0.0023", "unexpect": "0.0035", "forc": "0.0059", "hurt": "0.0082", "warn": "0.0012", "gain": "0.0644", "termin": "0.0012", "eas": "0.0035", "highest": "0.0141", "fraud": "0.0035", "default": "0.0094", "seiz": "0.0012", "will": "0.0012", "limit": "0.0129", "posit": "0.0269", "problem": "0.0059", "claim": "0.0258", "weaker": "0.0012", "advantag": "0.0035", "strengthen": "0.0023", "challeng": "0.0070", "premier": "0.0012", "worri": "0.0023", "alleg": "0.0059", "critic": "0.0023", "attract": "0.0047", "sever": "0.0035", "halt": "0.0012", "strength": "0.0012", "delay": "0.0012", "fire": "0.0023", "boom": "0.0035", "reject": "0.0152", "weaken": "0.0035", "difficult": "0.0059", "tighten": "0.0012", "effect": "0.0070", "resign": "0.0023", "alert": "0.0023", "quit": "0.0012", "refin": "0.0023", "postpon": "0.0012", "stabil": "0.0023", "stress": "0.0012", "liquid": "0.0035", "antitrust": "0.0246", "stronger": "0.0023", "su": "0.0059", "inform": "0.0070", "deni": "0.0070", "achiev": "0.0012"}, "16": {"recess": "0.0039", "opposit": "0.0039", "lack": "0.0039", "protest": "0.0039", "surpass": "0.0039", "fear": "0.0079", "suffer": "0.0039", "fine": "0.0039", "accus": "0.0039", "cut": "0.0276", "depend": "0.0039", "except": "0.0039", "late": "0.0079", "arrest": "0.0039", "bailout": "0.0039", "volatil": "0.0039", "disrupt": "0.0039", "complaint": "0.0157", "good": "0.0039", "greater": "0.0039", "disclos": "0.0079", "rebound": "0.0039", "stop": "0.0079", "break": "0.0039", "worst": "0.0039", "know": "0.0039", "press": "0.0079", "loss": "0.0079", "bar": "0.0079", "success": "0.0039", "lost": "0.0079", "outperform": "0.0039", "drop": "0.0315", "negat": "0.0039", "resolv": "0.0118", "defens": "0.0039", "benefit": "0.0039", "integr": "0.0039", "lose": "0.0039", "popular": "0.0039", "collaps": "0.0039", "crisi": "0.0039", "prevent": "0.0039", "confid": "0.0039", "slower": "0.0039", "shut": "0.0079", "slowdown": "0.0039", "strongest": "0.0079", "cost": "0.0157", "opportun": "0.0039", "fail": "0.0079", "close": "0.0236", "precipit": "0.0039", "concern": "0.0039", "lead": "0.0039", "profit": "0.0433", "defend": "0.0039", "abl": "0.0118", "bad": "0.0039", "favor": "0.0118", "restructur": "0.0039", "outstand": "0.0039", "deficit": "0.0039", "progress": "0.0039", "boost": "0.0039", "correct": "0.0039", "encourag": "0.0079", "investig": "0.0039", "advanc": "0.0157", "weak": "0.0039", "ban": "0.0039", "slow": "0.0039", "excess": "0.0039", "disput": "0.0157", "strong": "0.0039", "great": "0.0039", "deterior": "0.0039", "unemploy": "0.0039", "contract": "0.0039", "threat": "0.0039", "improv": "0.0079", "allianc": "0.0039", "suspend": "0.0118", "effici": "0.0079", "declin": "0.0157", "win": "0.0039", "bankruptci": "0.0157", "shortag": "0.0039", "cancel": "0.0039", "stabl": "0.0039", "miss": "0.0039", "drought": "0.0039", "damag": "0.0079", "bolster": "0.0039", "better": "0.0039", "question": "0.0039", "construct": "0.0079", "doubt": "0.0039", "downgrad": "0.0039", "threaten": "0.0039", "unexpect": "0.0039", "forc": "0.0079", "hurt": "0.0079", "warn": "0.0039", "gain": "0.0630", "termin": "0.0039", "eas": "0.0039", "highest": "0.0157", "fraud": "0.0039", "default": "0.0039", "seiz": "0.0039", "will": "0.0039", "limit": "0.0039", "posit": "0.0039", "problem": "0.0079", "claim": "0.0039", "weaker": "0.0039", "advantag": "0.0039", "strengthen": "0.0039", "challeng": "0.0157", "premier": "0.0039", "worri": "0.0039", "alleg": "0.0079", "critic": "0.0039", "attract": "0.0039", "sever": "0.0039", "halt": "0.0079", "strength": "0.0079", "delay": "0.0079", "fire": "0.0039", "boom": "0.0039", "reject": "0.0157", "weaken": "0.0039", "difficult": "0.0039", "tighten": "0.0039", "effect": "0.0039", "resign": "0.0039", "alert": "0.0039", "quit": "0.0039", "refin": "0.0039", "postpon": "0.0039", "stabil": "0.0039", "stress": "0.0039", "liquid": "0.0039", "antitrust": "0.0157", "stronger": "0.0039", "su": "0.0039", "inform": "0.0039", "deni": "0.0039", "achiev": "0.0039"}, "17": {"recess": "0.0014", "opposit": "0.0028", "lack": "0.0042", "protest": "0.0014", "surpass": "0.0055", "fear": "0.0042", "suffer": "0.0042", "fine": "0.0319", "accus": "0.0028", "cut": "0.0152", "depend": "0.0028", "except": "0.0028", "late": "0.0042", "arrest": "0.0042", "bailout": "0.0014", "volatil": "0.0014", "disrupt": "0.0014", "complaint": "0.0111", "good": "0.0125", "greater": "0.0042", "disclos": "0.0125", "rebound": "0.0028", "stop": "0.0111", "break": "0.0042", "worst": "0.0028", "know": "0.0042", "press": "0.0042", "loss": "0.0208", "bar": "0.0055", "success": "0.0014", "lost": "0.0152", "outperform": "0.0014", "drop": "0.0637", "negat": "0.0028", "resolv": "0.0028", "defens": "0.0028", "benefit": "0.0097", "integr": "0.0014", "lose": "0.0069", "popular": "0.0028", "collaps": "0.0014", "crisi": "0.0042", "prevent": "0.0028", "confid": "0.0069", "slower": "0.0014", "shut": "0.0014", "slowdown": "0.0028", "strongest": "0.0014", "cost": "0.0222", "opportun": "0.0125", "fail": "0.0125", "close": "0.0249", "precipit": "0.0014", "concern": "0.0069", "lead": "0.0069", "profit": "0.0443", "defend": "0.0042", "abl": "0.0083", "bad": "0.0042", "favor": "0.0028", "restructur": "0.0028", "outstand": "0.0028", "deficit": "0.0028", "progress": "0.0014", "boost": "0.0111", "correct": "0.0042", "encourag": "0.0028", "investig": "0.0055", "advanc": "0.0180", "weak": "0.0028", "ban": "0.0028", "slow": "0.0069", "excess": "0.0014", "disput": "0.0111", "strong": "0.0028", "great": "0.0014", "deterior": "0.0014", "unemploy": "0.0042", "contract": "0.0152", "threat": "0.0111", "improv": "0.0042", "allianc": "0.0028", "suspend": "0.0028", "effici": "0.0014", "declin": "0.0526", "win": "0.0083", "bankruptci": "0.0125", "shortag": "0.0014", "cancel": "0.0042", "stabl": "0.0028", "miss": "0.0028", "drought": "0.0014", "damag": "0.0014", "bolster": "0.0014", "better": "0.0208", "question": "0.0028", "construct": "0.0097", "doubt": "0.0042", "downgrad": "0.0014", "threaten": "0.0014", "unexpect": "0.0014", "forc": "0.0042", "hurt": "0.0069", "warn": "0.0014", "gain": "0.0568", "termin": "0.0028", "eas": "0.0014", "highest": "0.0111", "fraud": "0.0014", "default": "0.0042", "seiz": "0.0028", "will": "0.0014", "limit": "0.0055", "posit": "0.0097", "problem": "0.0055", "claim": "0.0028", "weaker": "0.0014", "advantag": "0.0028", "strengthen": "0.0055", "challeng": "0.0152", "premier": "0.0014", "worri": "0.0028", "alleg": "0.0028", "critic": "0.0014", "attract": "0.0042", "sever": "0.0042", "halt": "0.0055", "strength": "0.0028", "delay": "0.0014", "fire": "0.0014", "boom": "0.0042", "reject": "0.0042", "weaken": "0.0014", "difficult": "0.0042", "tighten": "0.0014", "effect": "0.0111", "resign": "0.0028", "alert": "0.0014", "quit": "0.0014", "refin": "0.0042", "postpon": "0.0014", "stabil": "0.0014", "stress": "0.0014", "liquid": "0.0028", "antitrust": "0.0429", "stronger": "0.0028", "su": "0.0028", "inform": "0.0042", "deni": "0.0055", "achiev": "0.0042"}, "18": {"recess": "0.0033", "opposit": "0.0033", "lack": "0.0017", "protest": "0.0033", "surpass": "0.0050", "fear": "0.0017", "suffer": "0.0017", "fine": "0.0017", "accus": "0.0017", "cut": "0.0167", "depend": "0.0033", "except": "0.0050", "late": "0.0033", "arrest": "0.0017", "bailout": "0.0017", "volatil": "0.0050", "disrupt": "0.0017", "complaint": "0.0033", "good": "0.0050", "greater": "0.0084", "disclos": "0.0084", "rebound": "0.0050", "stop": "0.0050", "break": "0.0033", "worst": "0.0033", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0234", "bar": "0.0050", "success": "0.0017", "lost": "0.0117", "outperform": "0.0017", "drop": "0.0435", "negat": "0.0050", "resolv": "0.0033", "defens": "0.0033", "benefit": "0.0117", "integr": "0.0017", "lose": "0.0050", "popular": "0.0033", "collaps": "0.0033", "crisi": "0.0151", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0017", "shut": "0.0033", "slowdown": "0.0033", "strongest": "0.0033", "cost": "0.0251", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0100", "close": "0.0117", "precipit": "0.0017", "concern": "0.0084", "lead": "0.0100", "profit": "0.0535", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0117", "bad": "0.0033", "favor": "0.0033", "restructur": "0.0033", "outstand": "0.0050", "deficit": "0.0033", "progress": "0.0017", "boost": "0.0201", "correct": "0.0033", "encourag": "0.0017", "investig": "0.0033", "advanc": "0.0117", "weak": "0.0017", "ban": "0.0084", "slow": "0.0033", "excess": "0.0017", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0033", "great": "0.0017", "deterior": "0.0017", "unemploy": "0.0033", "contract": "0.0201", "threat": "0.0050", "improv": "0.0151", "allianc": "0.0017", "suspend": "0.0050", "effici": "0.0050", "declin": "0.0518", "win": "0.0167", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0017", "cancel": "0.0033", "stabl": "0.0050", "miss": "0.0050", "drought": "0.0017", "damag": "0.0033", "bolster": "0.0017", "better": "0.0050", "question": "0.0033", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0033", "downgrad": "0.0050", "threaten": "0.0017", "unexpect": "0.0050", "forc": "0.0050", "hurt": "0.0050", "warn": "0.0017", "gain": "0.0803", "termin": "0.0017", "eas": "0.0033", "highest": "0.0167", "fraud": "0.0017", "default": "0.0234", "seiz": "0.0017", "will": "0.0017", "limit": "0.0017", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0017", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0017", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0033", "challeng": "0.0100", "premier": "0.0017", "worri": "0.0017", "alleg": "0.0033", "critic": "0.0017", "attract": "0.0050", "sever": "0.0017", "halt": "0.0033", "strength": "0.0033", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0017", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0184", "weaken": "0.0017", "difficult": "0.0050", "tighten": "0.0017", "effect": "0.0050", "resign": "0.0033", "alert": "0.0017", "quit": "0.0017", "refin": "0.0084", "postpon": "0.0017", "stabil": "0.0033", "stress": "0.0017", "liquid": "0.0117", "antitrust": "0.0050", "stronger": "0.0050", "su": "0.0017", "inform": "0.0033", "deni": "0.0033", "achiev": "0.0017"}, "19": {"recess": "0.0030", "opposit": "0.0030", "lack": "0.0060", "protest": "0.0030", "surpass": "0.0091", "fear": "0.0030", "suffer": "0.0030", "fine": "0.0393", "accus": "0.0030", "cut": "0.0181", "depend": "0.0060", "except": "0.0030", "late": "0.0091", "arrest": "0.0030", "bailout": "0.0030", "volatil": "0.0030", "disrupt": "0.0030", "complaint": "0.0060", "good": "0.0030", "greater": "0.0030", "disclos": "0.0151", "rebound": "0.0060", "stop": "0.0151", "break": "0.0030", "worst": "0.0030", "know": "0.0030", "press": "0.0060", "loss": "0.0060", "bar": "0.0030", "success": "0.0030", "lost": "0.0060", "outperform": "0.0030", "drop": "0.0544", "negat": "0.0091", "resolv": "0.0030", "defens": "0.0060", "benefit": "0.0121", "integr": "0.0030", "lose": "0.0091", "popular": "0.0030", "collaps": "0.0030", "crisi": "0.0030", "prevent": "0.0030", "confid": "0.0030", "slower": "0.0030", "shut": "0.0030", "slowdown": "0.0030", "strongest": "0.0030", "cost": "0.0302", "opportun": "0.0091", "fail": "0.0091", "close": "0.0242", "precipit": "0.0030", "concern": "0.0030", "lead": "0.0091", "profit": "0.0363", "defend": "0.0060", "abl": "0.0091", "bad": "0.0030", "favor": "0.0030", "restructur": "0.0030", "outstand": "0.0060", "deficit": "0.0030", "progress": "0.0030", "boost": "0.0091", "correct": "0.0030", "encourag": "0.0060", "investig": "0.0030", "advanc": "0.0242", "weak": "0.0030", "ban": "0.0030", "slow": "0.0121", "excess": "0.0030", "disput": "0.0121", "strong": "0.0091", "great": "0.0030", "deterior": "0.0030", "unemploy": "0.0060", "contract": "0.0060", "threat": "0.0091", "improv": "0.0060", "allianc": "0.0030", "suspend": "0.0030", "effici": "0.0030", "declin": "0.0332", "win": "0.0060", "bankruptci": "0.0030", "shortag": "0.0030", "cancel": "0.0030", "stabl": "0.0030", "miss": "0.0060", "drought": "0.0030", "damag": "0.0030", "bolster": "0.0030", "better": "0.0030", "question": "0.0030", "construct": "0.0060", "doubt": "0.0030", "downgrad": "0.0060", "threaten": "0.0060", "unexpect": "0.0030", "forc": "0.0030", "hurt": "0.0060", "warn": "0.0030", "gain": "0.0514", "termin": "0.0121", "eas": "0.0030", "highest": "0.0151", "fraud": "0.0030", "default": "0.0030", "seiz": "0.0030", "will": "0.0030", "limit": "0.0060", "posit": "0.0091", "problem": "0.0030", "claim": "0.0030", "weaker": "0.0030", "advantag": "0.0030", "strengthen": "0.0030", "challeng": "0.0091", "premier": "0.0060", "worri": "0.0030", "alleg": "0.0030", "critic": "0.0030", "attract": "0.0030", "sever": "0.0030", "halt": "0.0030", "strength": "0.0030", "delay": "0.0030", "fire": "0.0030", "boom": "0.0030", "reject": "0.0091", "weaken": "0.0030", "difficult": "0.0060", "tighten": "0.0091", "effect": "0.0060", "resign": "0.0030", "alert": "0.0030", "quit": "0.0091", "refin": "0.0030", "postpon": "0.0030", "stabil": "0.0030", "stress": "0.0030", "liquid": "0.0030", "antitrust": "0.0242", "stronger": "0.0030", "su": "0.0030", "inform": "0.0030", "deni": "0.0030", "achiev": "0.0030"}, "20": {"recess": "0.0110", "opposit": "0.0028", "lack": "0.0055", "protest": "0.0028", "surpass": "0.0028", "fear": "0.0055", "suffer": "0.0083", "fine": "0.0110", "accus": "0.0083", "cut": "0.0220", "depend": "0.0028", "except": "0.0028", "late": "0.0055", "arrest": "0.0028", "bailout": "0.0028", "volatil": "0.0055", "disrupt": "0.0028", "complaint": "0.0055", "good": "0.0028", "greater": "0.0028", "disclos": "0.0110", "rebound": "0.0028", "stop": "0.0110", "break": "0.0055", "worst": "0.0055", "know": "0.0028", "press": "0.0055", "loss": "0.0028", "bar": "0.0083", "success": "0.0055", "lost": "0.0110", "outperform": "0.0028", "drop": "0.0303", "negat": "0.0028", "resolv": "0.0055", "defens": "0.0028", "benefit": "0.0110", "integr": "0.0055", "lose": "0.0055", "popular": "0.0028", "collaps": "0.0028", "crisi": "0.0055", "prevent": "0.0055", "confid": "0.0055", "slower": "0.0028", "shut": "0.0028", "slowdown": "0.0028", "strongest": "0.0028", "cost": "0.0110", "opportun": "0.0138", "fail": "0.0110", "close": "0.0138", "precipit": "0.0028", "concern": "0.0138", "lead": "0.0028", "profit": "0.0193", "defend": "0.0028", "abl": "0.0055", "bad": "0.0028", "favor": "0.0055", "restructur": "0.0055", "outstand": "0.0055", "deficit": "0.0028", "progress": "0.0028", "boost": "0.0220", "correct": "0.0083", "encourag": "0.0055", "investig": "0.0028", "advanc": "0.0165", "weak": "0.0028", "ban": "0.0028", "slow": "0.0083", "excess": "0.0028", "disput": "0.0138", "strong": "0.0055", "great": "0.0028", "deterior": "0.0028", "unemploy": "0.0055", "contract": "0.0110", "threat": "0.0055", "improv": "0.0028", "allianc": "0.0083", "suspend": "0.0055", "effici": "0.0055", "declin": "0.0468", "win": "0.0138", "bankruptci": "0.0138", "shortag": "0.0028", "cancel": "0.0055", "stabl": "0.0055", "miss": "0.0028", "drought": "0.0028", "damag": "0.0028", "bolster": "0.0028", "better": "0.0165", "question": "0.0083", "construct": "0.0083", "doubt": "0.0110", "downgrad": "0.0028", "threaten": "0.0055", "unexpect": "0.0028", "forc": "0.0083", "hurt": "0.0055", "warn": "0.0028", "gain": "0.0358", "termin": "0.0055", "eas": "0.0055", "highest": "0.0138", "fraud": "0.0028", "default": "0.0110", "seiz": "0.0055", "will": "0.0028", "limit": "0.0083", "posit": "0.0028", "problem": "0.0028", "claim": "0.0028", "weaker": "0.0028", "advantag": "0.0028", "strengthen": "0.0055", "challeng": "0.0110", "premier": "0.0028", "worri": "0.0028", "alleg": "0.0028", "critic": "0.0028", "attract": "0.0055", "sever": "0.0083", "halt": "0.0083", "strength": "0.0028", "delay": "0.0055", "fire": "0.0055", "boom": "0.0028", "reject": "0.0028", "weaken": "0.0055", "difficult": "0.0028", "tighten": "0.0028", "effect": "0.0138", "resign": "0.0055", "alert": "0.0028", "quit": "0.0028", "refin": "0.0028", "postpon": "0.0028", "stabil": "0.0028", "stress": "0.0028", "liquid": "0.0083", "antitrust": "0.0303", "stronger": "0.0028", "su": "0.0028", "inform": "0.0055", "deni": "0.0055", "achiev": "0.0055"}}, "IBOV": {"1": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "2": {"recess": "0.0040", "opposit": "0.0010", "lack": "0.0030", "protest": "0.0020", "surpass": "0.0010", "fear": "0.0010", "suffer": "0.0020", "fine": "0.0010", "accus": "0.0010", "cut": "0.0141", "depend": "0.0060", "except": "0.0030", "late": "0.0080", "arrest": "0.0010", "bailout": "0.0040", "volatil": "0.0080", "disrupt": "0.0020", "complaint": "0.0010", "good": "0.0121", "greater": "0.0050", "disclos": "0.0050", "rebound": "0.0171", "stop": "0.0030", "break": "0.0020", "worst": "0.0030", "know": "0.0010", "press": "0.0040", "loss": "0.0080", "bar": "0.0020", "success": "0.0040", "lost": "0.0121", "outperform": "0.0020", "drop": "0.0583", "negat": "0.0040", "resolv": "0.0010", "defens": "0.0040", "benefit": "0.0060", "integr": "0.0020", "lose": "0.0080", "popular": "0.0010", "collaps": "0.0050", "crisi": "0.0342", "prevent": "0.0020", "confid": "0.0070", "slower": "0.0040", "shut": "0.0010", "slowdown": "0.0020", "strongest": "0.0010", "cost": "0.0392", "opportun": "0.0040", "fail": "0.0121", "close": "0.0201", "precipit": "0.0010", "concern": "0.0332", "lead": "0.0131", "profit": "0.0251", "defend": "0.0020", "abl": "0.0020", "bad": "0.0010", "favor": "0.0060", "restructur": "0.0010", "outstand": "0.0040", "deficit": "0.0070", "progress": "0.0030", "boost": "0.0261", "correct": "0.0020", "encourag": "0.0010", "investig": "0.0020", "advanc": "0.0111", "weak": "0.0070", "ban": "0.0141", "slow": "0.0181", "excess": "0.0020", "disput": "0.0020", "strong": "0.0090", "great": "0.0010", "deterior": "0.0050", "unemploy": "0.0121", "contract": "0.0281", "threat": "0.0010", "improv": "0.0131", "allianc": "0.0010", "suspend": "0.0030", "effici": "0.0040", "declin": "0.0543", "win": "0.0030", "bankruptci": "0.0020", "shortag": "0.0010", "cancel": "0.0030", "stabl": "0.0121", "miss": "0.0030", "drought": "0.0010", "damag": "0.0030", "bolster": "0.0010", "better": "0.0070", "question": "0.0060", "construct": "0.0181", "doubt": "0.0030", "downgrad": "0.0020", "threaten": "0.0040", "unexpect": "0.0010", "forc": "0.0060", "hurt": "0.0050", "warn": "0.0010", "gain": "0.0352", "termin": "0.0030", "eas": "0.0010", "highest": "0.0080", "fraud": "0.0010", "default": "0.0070", "seiz": "0.0010", "will": "0.0040", "limit": "0.0080", "posit": "0.0101", "problem": "0.0040", "claim": "0.0020", "weaker": "0.0040", "advantag": "0.0080", "strengthen": "0.0121", "challeng": "0.0030", "premier": "0.0010", "worri": "0.0010", "alleg": "0.0010", "critic": "0.0020", "attract": "0.0020", "sever": "0.0040", "halt": "0.0050", "strength": "0.0020", "delay": "0.0171", "fire": "0.0030", "boom": "0.0020", "reject": "0.0010", "weaken": "0.0101", "difficult": "0.0050", "tighten": "0.0090", "effect": "0.0141", "resign": "0.0040", "alert": "0.0010", "quit": "0.0060", "refin": "0.0040", "postpon": "0.0040", "stabil": "0.0070", "stress": "0.0040", "liquid": "0.0060", "antitrust": "0.0010", "stronger": "0.0020", "su": "0.0010", "inform": "0.0080", "deni": "0.0010", "achiev": "0.0020"}, "3": {"recess": "0.0033", "opposit": "0.0033", "lack": "0.0017", "protest": "0.0016", "surpass": "0.0024", "fear": "0.0013", "suffer": "0.0014", "fine": "0.0008", "accus": "0.0011", "cut": "0.0321", "depend": "0.0054", "except": "0.0028", "late": "0.0060", "arrest": "0.0003", "bailout": "0.0044", "volatil": "0.0024", "disrupt": "0.0009", "complaint": "0.0008", "good": "0.0145", "greater": "0.0046", "disclos": "0.0014", "rebound": "0.0043", "stop": "0.0032", "break": "0.0028", "worst": "0.0036", "know": "0.0035", "press": "0.0077", "loss": "0.0112", "bar": "0.0011", "success": "0.0052", "lost": "0.0117", "outperform": "0.0024", "drop": "0.0507", "negat": "0.0027", "resolv": "0.0008", "defens": "0.0019", "benefit": "0.0071", "integr": "0.0032", "lose": "0.0074", "popular": "0.0005", "collaps": "0.0013", "crisi": "0.0126", "prevent": "0.0027", "confid": "0.0062", "slower": "0.0016", "shut": "0.0033", "slowdown": "0.0036", "strongest": "0.0016", "cost": "0.0362", "opportun": "0.0054", "fail": "0.0128", "close": "0.0283", "precipit": "0.0002", "concern": "0.0278", "lead": "0.0123", "profit": "0.0348", "defend": "0.0011", "abl": "0.0043", "bad": "0.0019", "favor": "0.0041", "restructur": "0.0024", "outstand": "0.0058", "deficit": "0.0063", "progress": "0.0014", "boost": "0.0319", "correct": "0.0019", "encourag": "0.0013", "investig": "0.0036", "advanc": "0.0223", "weak": "0.0030", "ban": "0.0036", "slow": "0.0126", "excess": "0.0013", "disput": "0.0032", "strong": "0.0092", "great": "0.0009", "deterior": "0.0013", "unemploy": "0.0052", "contract": "0.0306", "threat": "0.0014", "improv": "0.0052", "allianc": "0.0002", "suspend": "0.0014", "effici": "0.0011", "declin": "0.0769", "win": "0.0082", "bankruptci": "0.0008", "shortag": "0.0019", "cancel": "0.0022", "stabl": "0.0025", "miss": "0.0041", "drought": "0.0017", "damag": "0.0025", "bolster": "0.0043", "better": "0.0046", "question": "0.0024", "construct": "0.0112", "doubt": "0.0014", "downgrad": "0.0033", "threaten": "0.0024", "unexpect": "0.0032", "forc": "0.0073", "hurt": "0.0044", "warn": "0.0022", "gain": "0.0714", "termin": "0.0039", "eas": "0.0073", "highest": "0.0180", "fraud": "0.0009", "default": "0.0084", "seiz": "0.0019", "will": "0.0008", "limit": "0.0068", "posit": "0.0167", "problem": "0.0025", "claim": "0.0028", "weaker": "0.0025", "advantag": "0.0062", "strengthen": "0.0084", "challeng": "0.0036", "premier": "0.0027", "worri": "0.0009", "alleg": "0.0017", "critic": "0.0025", "attract": "0.0066", "sever": "0.0036", "halt": "0.0028", "strength": "0.0017", "delay": "0.0100", "fire": "0.0032", "boom": "0.0005", "reject": "0.0051", "weaken": "0.0082", "difficult": "0.0036", "tighten": "0.0054", "effect": "0.0044", "resign": "0.0013", "alert": "0.0024", "quit": "0.0030", "refin": "0.0111", "postpon": "0.0044", "stabil": "0.0006", "stress": "0.0011", "liquid": "0.0021", "antitrust": "0.0022", "stronger": "0.0024", "su": "0.0028", "inform": "0.0076", "deni": "0.0022", "achiev": "0.0014"}, "4": {"recess": "0.0048", "opposit": "0.0043", "lack": "0.0035", "protest": "0.0033", "surpass": "0.0035", "fear": "0.0007", "suffer": "0.0017", "fine": "0.0028", "accus": "0.0020", "cut": "0.0262", "depend": "0.0037", "except": "0.0019", "late": "0.0043", "arrest": "0.0020", "bailout": "0.0030", "volatil": "0.0039", "disrupt": "0.0020", "complaint": "0.0013", "good": "0.0138", "greater": "0.0026", "disclos": "0.0017", "rebound": "0.0059", "stop": "0.0035", "break": "0.0017", "worst": "0.0043", "know": "0.0032", "press": "0.0071", "loss": "0.0108", "bar": "0.0022", "success": "0.0041", "lost": "0.0102", "outperform": "0.0015", "drop": "0.0454", "negat": "0.0032", "resolv": "0.0013", "defens": "0.0024", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0026", "lose": "0.0061", "popular": "0.0009", "collaps": "0.0006", "crisi": "0.0177", "prevent": "0.0043", "confid": "0.0045", "slower": "0.0030", "shut": "0.0015", "slowdown": "0.0037", "strongest": "0.0026", "cost": "0.0396", "opportun": "0.0050", "fail": "0.0082", "close": "0.0266", "precipit": "0.0080", "concern": "0.0255", "lead": "0.0117", "profit": "0.0236", "defend": "0.0011", "abl": "0.0046", "bad": "0.0024", "favor": "0.0050", "restructur": "0.0019", "outstand": "0.0028", "deficit": "0.0089", "progress": "0.0022", "boost": "0.0299", "correct": "0.0030", "encourag": "0.0015", "investig": "0.0011", "advanc": "0.0322", "weak": "0.0028", "ban": "0.0026", "slow": "0.0190", "excess": "0.0024", "disput": "0.0032", "strong": "0.0074", "great": "0.0039", "deterior": "0.0017", "unemploy": "0.0035", "contract": "0.0366", "threat": "0.0022", "improv": "0.0076", "allianc": "0.0022", "suspend": "0.0026", "effici": "0.0030", "declin": "0.0558", "win": "0.0065", "bankruptci": "0.0004", "shortag": "0.0041", "cancel": "0.0017", "stabl": "0.0033", "miss": "0.0035", "drought": "0.0028", "damag": "0.0022", "bolster": "0.0037", "better": "0.0054", "question": "0.0032", "construct": "0.0089", "doubt": "0.0030", "downgrad": "0.0022", "threaten": "0.0020", "unexpect": "0.0035", "forc": "0.0076", "hurt": "0.0033", "warn": "0.0017", "gain": "0.0825", "termin": "0.0022", "eas": "0.0084", "highest": "0.0160", "fraud": "0.0006", "default": "0.0073", "seiz": "0.0013", "will": "0.0011", "limit": "0.0113", "posit": "0.0134", "problem": "0.0050", "claim": "0.0024", "weaker": "0.0019", "advantag": "0.0032", "strengthen": "0.0141", "challeng": "0.0041", "premier": "0.0020", "worri": "0.0019", "alleg": "0.0017", "critic": "0.0039", "attract": "0.0078", "sever": "0.0033", "halt": "0.0041", "strength": "0.0026", "delay": "0.0043", "fire": "0.0022", "boom": "0.0011", "reject": "0.0022", "weaken": "0.0078", "difficult": "0.0019", "tighten": "0.0056", "effect": "0.0054", "resign": "0.0035", "alert": "0.0019", "quit": "0.0032", "refin": "0.0069", "postpon": "0.0030", "stabil": "0.0030", "stress": "0.0002", "liquid": "0.0028", "antitrust": "0.0022", "stronger": "0.0022", "su": "0.0009", "inform": "0.0084", "deni": "0.0032", "achiev": "0.0017"}, "5": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "6": {"recess": "0.0031", "opposit": "0.0031", "lack": "0.0054", "protest": "0.0045", "surpass": "0.0036", "fear": "0.0027", "suffer": "0.0022", "fine": "0.0009", "accus": "0.0013", "cut": "0.0234", "depend": "0.0027", "except": "0.0018", "late": "0.0040", "arrest": "0.0009", "bailout": "0.0049", "volatil": "0.0040", "disrupt": "0.0027", "complaint": "0.0004", "good": "0.0121", "greater": "0.0031", "disclos": "0.0018", "rebound": "0.0121", "stop": "0.0022", "break": "0.0027", "worst": "0.0027", "know": "0.0036", "press": "0.0049", "loss": "0.0126", "bar": "0.0009", "success": "0.0027", "lost": "0.0162", "outperform": "0.0022", "drop": "0.0589", "negat": "0.0045", "resolv": "0.0009", "defens": "0.0022", "benefit": "0.0085", "integr": "0.0009", "lose": "0.0036", "popular": "0.0009", "collaps": "0.0049", "crisi": "0.0153", "prevent": "0.0018", "confid": "0.0058", "slower": "0.0036", "shut": "0.0045", "slowdown": "0.0018", "strongest": "0.0009", "cost": "0.0427", "opportun": "0.0076", "fail": "0.0144", "close": "0.0252", "precipit": "0.0004", "concern": "0.0360", "lead": "0.0094", "profit": "0.0423", "defend": "0.0013", "abl": "0.0027", "bad": "0.0022", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0018", "outstand": "0.0027", "deficit": "0.0058", "progress": "0.0022", "boost": "0.0247", "correct": "0.0022", "encourag": "0.0013", "investig": "0.0018", "advanc": "0.0157", "weak": "0.0036", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0126", "excess": "0.0013", "disput": "0.0013", "strong": "0.0058", "great": "0.0027", "deterior": "0.0027", "unemploy": "0.0058", "contract": "0.0396", "threat": "0.0031", "improv": "0.0112", "allianc": "0.0009", "suspend": "0.0004", "effici": "0.0009", "declin": "0.0589", "win": "0.0063", "bankruptci": "0.0031", "shortag": "0.0004", "cancel": "0.0036", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0045", "drought": "0.0004", "damag": "0.0031", "bolster": "0.0013", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0058", "construct": "0.0117", "doubt": "0.0040", "downgrad": "0.0049", "threaten": "0.0018", "unexpect": "0.0027", "forc": "0.0045", "hurt": "0.0076", "warn": "0.0013", "gain": "0.0432", "termin": "0.0013", "eas": "0.0072", "highest": "0.0166", "fraud": "0.0009", "default": "0.0121", "seiz": "0.0013", "will": "0.0031", "limit": "0.0085", "posit": "0.0135", "problem": "0.0031", "claim": "0.0013", "weaker": "0.0022", "advantag": "0.0063", "strengthen": "0.0130", "challeng": "0.0018", "premier": "0.0040", "worri": "0.0004", "alleg": "0.0018", "critic": "0.0027", "attract": "0.0058", "sever": "0.0031", "halt": "0.0049", "strength": "0.0031", "delay": "0.0076", "fire": "0.0036", "boom": "0.0022", "reject": "0.0018", "weaken": "0.0099", "difficult": "0.0018", "tighten": "0.0036", "effect": "0.0063", "resign": "0.0031", "alert": "0.0027", "quit": "0.0036", "refin": "0.0049", "postpon": "0.0027", "stabil": "0.0036", "stress": "0.0013", "liquid": "0.0036", "antitrust": "0.0009", "stronger": "0.0031", "su": "0.0004", "inform": "0.0090", "deni": "0.0009", "achiev": "0.0013"}, "7": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "8": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "9": {"recess": "0.0012", "opposit": "0.0024", "lack": "0.0084", "protest": "0.0036", "surpass": "0.0036", "fear": "0.0048", "suffer": "0.0012", "fine": "0.0012", "accus": "0.0024", "cut": "0.0358", "depend": "0.0072", "except": "0.0012", "late": "0.0048", "arrest": "0.0012", "bailout": "0.0060", "volatil": "0.0036", "disrupt": "0.0012", "complaint": "0.0012", "good": "0.0048", "greater": "0.0036", "disclos": "0.0012", "rebound": "0.0024", "stop": "0.0024", "break": "0.0012", "worst": "0.0012", "know": "0.0060", "press": "0.0084", "loss": "0.0191", "bar": "0.0024", "success": "0.0048", "lost": "0.0227", "outperform": "0.0036", "drop": "0.0609", "negat": "0.0048", "resolv": "0.0024", "defens": "0.0012", "benefit": "0.0060", "integr": "0.0012", "lose": "0.0036", "popular": "0.0012", "collaps": "0.0024", "crisi": "0.0131", "prevent": "0.0048", "confid": "0.0048", "slower": "0.0012", "shut": "0.0024", "slowdown": "0.0024", "strongest": "0.0012", "cost": "0.0227", "opportun": "0.0084", "fail": "0.0143", "close": "0.0167", "precipit": "0.0012", "concern": "0.0323", "lead": "0.0084", "profit": "0.0215", "defend": "0.0036", "abl": "0.0048", "bad": "0.0036", "favor": "0.0060", "restructur": "0.0024", "outstand": "0.0036", "deficit": "0.0119", "progress": "0.0012", "boost": "0.0191", "correct": "0.0012", "encourag": "0.0024", "investig": "0.0012", "advanc": "0.0108", "weak": "0.0012", "ban": "0.0024", "slow": "0.0096", "excess": "0.0012", "disput": "0.0072", "strong": "0.0060", "great": "0.0024", "deterior": "0.0024", "unemploy": "0.0012", "contract": "0.0215", "threat": "0.0012", "improv": "0.0048", "allianc": "0.0024", "suspend": "0.0012", "effici": "0.0036", "declin": "0.0394", "win": "0.0191", "bankruptci": "0.0538", "shortag": "0.0012", "cancel": "0.0012", "stabl": "0.0024", "miss": "0.0024", "drought": "0.0012", "damag": "0.0012", "bolster": "0.0048", "better": "0.0036", "question": "0.0048", "construct": "0.0048", "doubt": "0.0072", "downgrad": "0.0036", "threaten": "0.0036", "unexpect": "0.0024", "forc": "0.0096", "hurt": "0.0060", "warn": "0.0024", "gain": "0.0370", "termin": "0.0072", "eas": "0.0024", "highest": "0.0084", "fraud": "0.0012", "default": "0.0119", "seiz": "0.0024", "will": "0.0036", "limit": "0.0096", "posit": "0.0203", "problem": "0.0048", "claim": "0.0179", "weaker": "0.0012", "advantag": "0.0060", "strengthen": "0.0167", "challeng": "0.0060", "premier": "0.0060", "worri": "0.0012", "alleg": "0.0024", "critic": "0.0012", "attract": "0.0143", "sever": "0.0048", "halt": "0.0072", "strength": "0.0036", "delay": "0.0084", "fire": "0.0036", "boom": "0.0036", "reject": "0.0012", "weaken": "0.0048", "difficult": "0.0036", "tighten": "0.0024", "effect": "0.0048", "resign": "0.0024", "alert": "0.0012", "quit": "0.0036", "refin": "0.0036", "postpon": "0.0048", "stabil": "0.0048", "stress": "0.0012", "liquid": "0.0060", "antitrust": "0.0012", "stronger": "0.0072", "su": "0.0012", "inform": "0.0036", "deni": "0.0012", "achiev": "0.0012"}, "10": {"recess": "0.0029", "opposit": "0.0017", "lack": "0.0019", "protest": "0.0006", "surpass": "0.0016", "fear": "0.0016", "suffer": "0.0018", "fine": "0.0021", "accus": "0.0004", "cut": "0.0285", "depend": "0.0049", "except": "0.0018", "late": "0.0029", "arrest": "0.0010", "bailout": "0.0041", "volatil": "0.0030", "disrupt": "0.0035", "complaint": "0.0016", "good": "0.0114", "greater": "0.0033", "disclos": "0.0018", "rebound": "0.0064", "stop": "0.0023", "break": "0.0022", "worst": "0.0028", "know": "0.0026", "press": "0.0055", "loss": "0.0129", "bar": "0.0015", "success": "0.0024", "lost": "0.0141", "outperform": "0.0013", "drop": "0.0496", "negat": "0.0029", "resolv": "0.0016", "defens": "0.0022", "benefit": "0.0058", "integr": "0.0026", "lose": "0.0058", "popular": "0.0010", "collaps": "0.0019", "crisi": "0.0081", "prevent": "0.0041", "confid": "0.0062", "slower": "0.0019", "shut": "0.0039", "slowdown": "0.0023", "strongest": "0.0015", "cost": "0.0383", "opportun": "0.0050", "fail": "0.0109", "close": "0.0269", "precipit": "0.0001", "concern": "0.0315", "lead": "0.0117", "profit": "0.0377", "defend": "0.0010", "abl": "0.0058", "bad": "0.0019", "favor": "0.0029", "restructur": "0.0016", "outstand": "0.0057", "deficit": "0.0063", "progress": "0.0039", "boost": "0.0277", "correct": "0.0021", "encourag": "0.0021", "investig": "0.0035", "advanc": "0.0260", "weak": "0.0024", "ban": "0.0033", "slow": "0.0106", "excess": "0.0018", "disput": "0.0024", "strong": "0.0063", "great": "0.0021", "deterior": "0.0005", "unemploy": "0.0027", "contract": "0.0263", "threat": "0.0019", "improv": "0.0092", "allianc": "0.0013", "suspend": "0.0030", "effici": "0.0013", "declin": "0.0720", "win": "0.0075", "bankruptci": "0.0040", "shortag": "0.0013", "cancel": "0.0049", "stabl": "0.0017", "miss": "0.0034", "drought": "0.0012", "damag": "0.0057", "bolster": "0.0032", "better": "0.0049", "question": "0.0027", "construct": "0.0092", "doubt": "0.0010", "downgrad": "0.0023", "threaten": "0.0033", "unexpect": "0.0021", "forc": "0.0077", "hurt": "0.0051", "warn": "0.0016", "gain": "0.0748", "termin": "0.0038", "eas": "0.0043", "highest": "0.0217", "fraud": "0.0010", "default": "0.0071", "seiz": "0.0011", "will": "0.0021", "limit": "0.0081", "posit": "0.0168", "problem": "0.0044", "claim": "0.0045", "weaker": "0.0022", "advantag": "0.0041", "strengthen": "0.0091", "challeng": "0.0019", "premier": "0.0026", "worri": "0.0017", "alleg": "0.0019", "critic": "0.0036", "attract": "0.0072", "sever": "0.0036", "halt": "0.0038", "strength": "0.0021", "delay": "0.0073", "fire": "0.0030", "boom": "0.0019", "reject": "0.0058", "weaken": "0.0086", "difficult": "0.0027", "tighten": "0.0056", "effect": "0.0047", "resign": "0.0012", "alert": "0.0026", "quit": "0.0015", "refin": "0.0201", "postpon": "0.0033", "stabil": "0.0023", "stress": "0.0005", "liquid": "0.0029", "antitrust": "0.0044", "stronger": "0.0028", "su": "0.0032", "inform": "0.0074", "deni": "0.0026", "achiev": "0.0013"}, "11": {"recess": "0.0045", "opposit": "0.0027", "lack": "0.0033", "protest": "0.0040", "surpass": "0.0027", "fear": "0.0029", "suffer": "0.0018", "fine": "0.0009", "accus": "0.0009", "cut": "0.0201", "depend": "0.0049", "except": "0.0011", "late": "0.0071", "arrest": "0.0004", "bailout": "0.0018", "volatil": "0.0036", "disrupt": "0.0040", "complaint": "0.0016", "good": "0.0125", "greater": "0.0047", "disclos": "0.0020", "rebound": "0.0089", "stop": "0.0031", "break": "0.0016", "worst": "0.0042", "know": "0.0022", "press": "0.0069", "loss": "0.0183", "bar": "0.0007", "success": "0.0031", "lost": "0.0165", "outperform": "0.0018", "drop": "0.0548", "negat": "0.0033", "resolv": "0.0013", "defens": "0.0016", "benefit": "0.0074", "integr": "0.0013", "lose": "0.0036", "popular": "0.0009", "collaps": "0.0031", "crisi": "0.0165", "prevent": "0.0047", "confid": "0.0062", "slower": "0.0033", "shut": "0.0025", "slowdown": "0.0016", "strongest": "0.0009", "cost": "0.0372", "opportun": "0.0029", "fail": "0.0096", "close": "0.0214", "precipit": "0.0002", "concern": "0.0290", "lead": "0.0132", "profit": "0.0354", "defend": "0.0016", "abl": "0.0053", "bad": "0.0031", "favor": "0.0031", "restructur": "0.0016", "outstand": "0.0020", "deficit": "0.0058", "progress": "0.0018", "boost": "0.0292", "correct": "0.0025", "encourag": "0.0018", "investig": "0.0033", "advanc": "0.0325", "weak": "0.0036", "ban": "0.0053", "slow": "0.0140", "excess": "0.0016", "disput": "0.0020", "strong": "0.0107", "great": "0.0009", "deterior": "0.0009", "unemploy": "0.0031", "contract": "0.0292", "threat": "0.0013", "improv": "0.0056", "allianc": "0.0009", "suspend": "0.0038", "effici": "0.0009", "declin": "0.0620", "win": "0.0051", "bankruptci": "0.0009", "shortag": "0.0025", "cancel": "0.0027", "stabl": "0.0029", "miss": "0.0047", "drought": "0.0018", "damag": "0.0022", "bolster": "0.0042", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0040", "construct": "0.0069", "doubt": "0.0022", "downgrad": "0.0027", "threaten": "0.0025", "unexpect": "0.0013", "forc": "0.0058", "hurt": "0.0058", "warn": "0.0020", "gain": "0.0780", "termin": "0.0016", "eas": "0.0040", "highest": "0.0210", "fraud": "0.0022", "default": "0.0096", "seiz": "0.0007", "will": "0.0018", "limit": "0.0080", "posit": "0.0140", "problem": "0.0065", "claim": "0.0016", "weaker": "0.0016", "advantag": "0.0042", "strengthen": "0.0100", "challeng": "0.0018", "premier": "0.0025", "worri": "0.0016", "alleg": "0.0011", "critic": "0.0020", "attract": "0.0058", "sever": "0.0042", "halt": "0.0049", "strength": "0.0027", "delay": "0.0138", "fire": "0.0029", "boom": "0.0020", "reject": "0.0038", "weaken": "0.0071", "difficult": "0.0036", "tighten": "0.0051", "effect": "0.0058", "resign": "0.0009", "alert": "0.0009", "quit": "0.0022", "refin": "0.0123", "postpon": "0.0029", "stabil": "0.0018", "stress": "0.0009", "liquid": "0.0025", "antitrust": "0.0018", "stronger": "0.0053", "su": "0.0018", "inform": "0.0060", "deni": "0.0016", "achiev": "0.0009"}, "12": {"recess": "0.0039", "opposit": "0.0032", "lack": "0.0014", "protest": "0.0016", "surpass": "0.0023", "fear": "0.0018", "suffer": "0.0007", "fine": "0.0007", "accus": "0.0005", "cut": "0.0274", "depend": "0.0045", "except": "0.0020", "late": "0.0052", "arrest": "0.0011", "bailout": "0.0036", "volatil": "0.0020", "disrupt": "0.0039", "complaint": "0.0009", "good": "0.0125", "greater": "0.0029", "disclos": "0.0014", "rebound": "0.0084", "stop": "0.0025", "break": "0.0025", "worst": "0.0045", "know": "0.0034", "press": "0.0063", "loss": "0.0109", "bar": "0.0007", "success": "0.0039", "lost": "0.0156", "outperform": "0.0018", "drop": "0.0492", "negat": "0.0014", "resolv": "0.0016", "defens": "0.0018", "benefit": "0.0068", "integr": "0.0020", "lose": "0.0057", "popular": "0.0007", "collaps": "0.0009", "crisi": "0.0168", "prevent": "0.0043", "confid": "0.0061", "slower": "0.0018", "shut": "0.0039", "slowdown": "0.0027", "strongest": "0.0014", "cost": "0.0365", "opportun": "0.0057", "fail": "0.0125", "close": "0.0270", "precipit": "0.0005", "concern": "0.0345", "lead": "0.0152", "profit": "0.0379", "defend": "0.0014", "abl": "0.0059", "bad": "0.0009", "favor": "0.0050", "restructur": "0.0007", "outstand": "0.0029", "deficit": "0.0073", "progress": "0.0023", "boost": "0.0324", "correct": "0.0023", "encourag": "0.0014", "investig": "0.0057", "advanc": "0.0186", "weak": "0.0020", "ban": "0.0027", "slow": "0.0156", "excess": "0.0036", "disput": "0.0034", "strong": "0.0066", "great": "0.0020", "deterior": "0.0007", "unemploy": "0.0025", "contract": "0.0295", "threat": "0.0018", "improv": "0.0104", "allianc": "0.0020", "suspend": "0.0045", "effici": "0.0011", "declin": "0.0689", "win": "0.0068", "bankruptci": "0.0077", "shortag": "0.0020", "cancel": "0.0050", "stabl": "0.0020", "miss": "0.0059", "drought": "0.0007", "damag": "0.0023", "bolster": "0.0027", "better": "0.0034", "question": "0.0023", "construct": "0.0109", "doubt": "0.0016", "downgrad": "0.0018", "threaten": "0.0027", "unexpect": "0.0020", "forc": "0.0125", "hurt": "0.0057", "warn": "0.0014", "gain": "0.0673", "termin": "0.0036", "eas": "0.0041", "highest": "0.0177", "fraud": "0.0011", "default": "0.0088", "seiz": "0.0032", "will": "0.0009", "limit": "0.0057", "posit": "0.0109", "problem": "0.0054", "claim": "0.0061", "weaker": "0.0020", "advantag": "0.0052", "strengthen": "0.0086", "challeng": "0.0027", "premier": "0.0025", "worri": "0.0016", "alleg": "0.0011", "critic": "0.0027", "attract": "0.0043", "sever": "0.0032", "halt": "0.0048", "strength": "0.0025", "delay": "0.0066", "fire": "0.0034", "boom": "0.0020", "reject": "0.0045", "weaken": "0.0050", "difficult": "0.0045", "tighten": "0.0034", "effect": "0.0025", "resign": "0.0011", "alert": "0.0009", "quit": "0.0027", "refin": "0.0136", "postpon": "0.0023", "stabil": "0.0029", "stress": "0.0007", "liquid": "0.0041", "antitrust": "0.0041", "stronger": "0.0027", "su": "0.0032", "inform": "0.0059", "deni": "0.0014", "achiev": "0.0020"}, "13": {"recess": "0.0038", "opposit": "0.0018", "lack": "0.0030", "protest": "0.0020", "surpass": "0.0029", "fear": "0.0013", "suffer": "0.0016", "fine": "0.0019", "accus": "0.0010", "cut": "0.0314", "depend": "0.0033", "except": "0.0015", "late": "0.0046", "arrest": "0.0007", "bailout": "0.0054", "volatil": "0.0031", "disrupt": "0.0025", "complaint": "0.0011", "good": "0.0137", "greater": "0.0022", "disclos": "0.0022", "rebound": "0.0055", "stop": "0.0023", "break": "0.0023", "worst": "0.0032", "know": "0.0026", "press": "0.0053", "loss": "0.0154", "bar": "0.0014", "success": "0.0022", "lost": "0.0144", "outperform": "0.0014", "drop": "0.0477", "negat": "0.0025", "resolv": "0.0009", "defens": "0.0014", "benefit": "0.0069", "integr": "0.0023", "lose": "0.0066", "popular": "0.0014", "collaps": "0.0020", "crisi": "0.0122", "prevent": "0.0043", "confid": "0.0055", "slower": "0.0021", "shut": "0.0042", "slowdown": "0.0025", "strongest": "0.0024", "cost": "0.0406", "opportun": "0.0054", "fail": "0.0095", "close": "0.0275", "precipit": "0.0029", "concern": "0.0301", "lead": "0.0128", "profit": "0.0374", "defend": "0.0010", "abl": "0.0057", "bad": "0.0020", "favor": "0.0027", "restructur": "0.0013", "outstand": "0.0047", "deficit": "0.0068", "progress": "0.0011", "boost": "0.0278", "correct": "0.0021", "encourag": "0.0019", "investig": "0.0021", "advanc": "0.0266", "weak": "0.0025", "ban": "0.0015", "slow": "0.0128", "excess": "0.0016", "disput": "0.0026", "strong": "0.0068", "great": "0.0024", "deterior": "0.0007", "unemploy": "0.0036", "contract": "0.0326", "threat": "0.0021", "improv": "0.0080", "allianc": "0.0019", "suspend": "0.0022", "effici": "0.0018", "declin": "0.0634", "win": "0.0085", "bankruptci": "0.0038", "shortag": "0.0016", "cancel": "0.0033", "stabl": "0.0026", "miss": "0.0047", "drought": "0.0024", "damag": "0.0040", "bolster": "0.0035", "better": "0.0047", "question": "0.0023", "construct": "0.0073", "doubt": "0.0012", "downgrad": "0.0036", "threaten": "0.0032", "unexpect": "0.0020", "forc": "0.0079", "hurt": "0.0058", "warn": "0.0020", "gain": "0.0746", "termin": "0.0038", "eas": "0.0041", "highest": "0.0212", "fraud": "0.0012", "default": "0.0095", "seiz": "0.0013", "will": "0.0014", "limit": "0.0088", "posit": "0.0186", "problem": "0.0036", "claim": "0.0027", "weaker": "0.0023", "advantag": "0.0035", "strengthen": "0.0104", "challeng": "0.0034", "premier": "0.0020", "worri": "0.0016", "alleg": "0.0012", "critic": "0.0021", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0037", "halt": "0.0027", "strength": "0.0015", "delay": "0.0074", "fire": "0.0032", "boom": "0.0009", "reject": "0.0030", "weaken": "0.0069", "difficult": "0.0019", "tighten": "0.0062", "effect": "0.0053", "resign": "0.0010", "alert": "0.0026", "quit": "0.0026", "refin": "0.0159", "postpon": "0.0038", "stabil": "0.0025", "stress": "0.0008", "liquid": "0.0027", "antitrust": "0.0019", "stronger": "0.0027", "su": "0.0013", "inform": "0.0056", "deni": "0.0026", "achiev": "0.0018"}, "14": {"recess": "0.0027", "opposit": "0.0019", "lack": "0.0022", "protest": "0.0016", "surpass": "0.0016", "fear": "0.0012", "suffer": "0.0024", "fine": "0.0013", "accus": "0.0017", "cut": "0.0283", "depend": "0.0048", "except": "0.0015", "late": "0.0043", "arrest": "0.0008", "bailout": "0.0025", "volatil": "0.0021", "disrupt": "0.0028", "complaint": "0.0024", "good": "0.0135", "greater": "0.0033", "disclos": "0.0015", "rebound": "0.0068", "stop": "0.0025", "break": "0.0016", "worst": "0.0035", "know": "0.0027", "press": "0.0072", "loss": "0.0100", "bar": "0.0018", "success": "0.0038", "lost": "0.0133", "outperform": "0.0023", "drop": "0.0470", "negat": "0.0030", "resolv": "0.0014", "defens": "0.0017", "benefit": "0.0065", "integr": "0.0022", "lose": "0.0065", "popular": "0.0004", "collaps": "0.0012", "crisi": "0.0117", "prevent": "0.0039", "confid": "0.0057", "slower": "0.0018", "shut": "0.0035", "slowdown": "0.0028", "strongest": "0.0021", "cost": "0.0372", "opportun": "0.0058", "fail": "0.0111", "close": "0.0275", "precipit": "0.0001", "concern": "0.0263", "lead": "0.0120", "profit": "0.0320", "defend": "0.0018", "abl": "0.0050", "bad": "0.0025", "favor": "0.0036", "restructur": "0.0009", "outstand": "0.0048", "deficit": "0.0063", "progress": "0.0016", "boost": "0.0325", "correct": "0.0011", "encourag": "0.0023", "investig": "0.0031", "advanc": "0.0268", "weak": "0.0025", "ban": "0.0022", "slow": "0.0136", "excess": "0.0016", "disput": "0.0025", "strong": "0.0080", "great": "0.0021", "deterior": "0.0003", "unemploy": "0.0029", "contract": "0.0304", "threat": "0.0016", "improv": "0.0084", "allianc": "0.0015", "suspend": "0.0039", "effici": "0.0015", "declin": "0.0779", "win": "0.0078", "bankruptci": "0.0044", "shortag": "0.0024", "cancel": "0.0024", "stabl": "0.0020", "miss": "0.0045", "drought": "0.0015", "damag": "0.0028", "bolster": "0.0042", "better": "0.0045", "question": "0.0029", "construct": "0.0132", "doubt": "0.0012", "downgrad": "0.0035", "threaten": "0.0022", "unexpect": "0.0018", "forc": "0.0106", "hurt": "0.0036", "warn": "0.0019", "gain": "0.0738", "termin": "0.0017", "eas": "0.0058", "highest": "0.0207", "fraud": "0.0024", "default": "0.0087", "seiz": "0.0008", "will": "0.0018", "limit": "0.0084", "posit": "0.0106", "problem": "0.0039", "claim": "0.0064", "weaker": "0.0020", "advantag": "0.0044", "strengthen": "0.0099", "challeng": "0.0030", "premier": "0.0026", "worri": "0.0020", "alleg": "0.0021", "critic": "0.0026", "attract": "0.0057", "sever": "0.0036", "halt": "0.0038", "strength": "0.0025", "delay": "0.0092", "fire": "0.0032", "boom": "0.0020", "reject": "0.0045", "weaken": "0.0076", "difficult": "0.0026", "tighten": "0.0046", "effect": "0.0040", "resign": "0.0011", "alert": "0.0016", "quit": "0.0016", "refin": "0.0126", "postpon": "0.0018", "stabil": "0.0015", "stress": "0.0005", "liquid": "0.0029", "antitrust": "0.0035", "stronger": "0.0022", "su": "0.0054", "inform": "0.0097", "deni": "0.0030", "achiev": "0.0016"}, "15": {"recess": "0.0026", "opposit": "0.0035", "lack": "0.0038", "protest": "0.0031", "surpass": "0.0017", "fear": "0.0015", "suffer": "0.0028", "fine": "0.0018", "accus": "0.0021", "cut": "0.0256", "depend": "0.0047", "except": "0.0024", "late": "0.0047", "arrest": "0.0011", "bailout": "0.0028", "volatil": "0.0046", "disrupt": "0.0024", "complaint": "0.0013", "good": "0.0126", "greater": "0.0033", "disclos": "0.0031", "rebound": "0.0070", "stop": "0.0028", "break": "0.0021", "worst": "0.0033", "know": "0.0051", "press": "0.0071", "loss": "0.0115", "bar": "0.0013", "success": "0.0025", "lost": "0.0129", "outperform": "0.0038", "drop": "0.0442", "negat": "0.0022", "resolv": "0.0021", "defens": "0.0014", "benefit": "0.0082", "integr": "0.0032", "lose": "0.0050", "popular": "0.0007", "collaps": "0.0019", "crisi": "0.0101", "prevent": "0.0040", "confid": "0.0058", "slower": "0.0015", "shut": "0.0018", "slowdown": "0.0028", "strongest": "0.0014", "cost": "0.0396", "opportun": "0.0065", "fail": "0.0149", "close": "0.0235", "precipit": "0.0003", "concern": "0.0260", "lead": "0.0124", "profit": "0.0345", "defend": "0.0010", "abl": "0.0038", "bad": "0.0024", "favor": "0.0050", "restructur": "0.0017", "outstand": "0.0029", "deficit": "0.0078", "progress": "0.0007", "boost": "0.0285", "correct": "0.0022", "encourag": "0.0013", "investig": "0.0031", "advanc": "0.0259", "weak": "0.0028", "ban": "0.0021", "slow": "0.0115", "excess": "0.0013", "disput": "0.0038", "strong": "0.0063", "great": "0.0026", "deterior": "0.0017", "unemploy": "0.0043", "contract": "0.0310", "threat": "0.0008", "improv": "0.0079", "allianc": "0.0008", "suspend": "0.0017", "effici": "0.0018", "declin": "0.0659", "win": "0.0068", "bankruptci": "0.0121", "shortag": "0.0015", "cancel": "0.0033", "stabl": "0.0029", "miss": "0.0042", "drought": "0.0013", "damag": "0.0025", "bolster": "0.0031", "better": "0.0058", "question": "0.0024", "construct": "0.0097", "doubt": "0.0021", "downgrad": "0.0043", "threaten": "0.0019", "unexpect": "0.0015", "forc": "0.0070", "hurt": "0.0051", "warn": "0.0011", "gain": "0.0770", "termin": "0.0031", "eas": "0.0058", "highest": "0.0227", "fraud": "0.0017", "default": "0.0108", "seiz": "0.0013", "will": "0.0019", "limit": "0.0070", "posit": "0.0138", "problem": "0.0047", "claim": "0.0056", "weaker": "0.0026", "advantag": "0.0051", "strengthen": "0.0089", "challeng": "0.0021", "premier": "0.0015", "worri": "0.0018", "alleg": "0.0035", "critic": "0.0035", "attract": "0.0083", "sever": "0.0039", "halt": "0.0044", "strength": "0.0018", "delay": "0.0082", "fire": "0.0026", "boom": "0.0017", "reject": "0.0043", "weaken": "0.0085", "difficult": "0.0019", "tighten": "0.0033", "effect": "0.0039", "resign": "0.0015", "alert": "0.0019", "quit": "0.0025", "refin": "0.0153", "postpon": "0.0026", "stabil": "0.0014", "stress": "0.0004", "liquid": "0.0035", "antitrust": "0.0013", "stronger": "0.0028", "su": "0.0050", "inform": "0.0061", "deni": "0.0014", "achiev": "0.0013"}, "16": {"recess": "0.0038", "opposit": "0.0022", "lack": "0.0024", "protest": "0.0029", "surpass": "0.0027", "fear": "0.0007", "suffer": "0.0015", "fine": "0.0018", "accus": "0.0010", "cut": "0.0293", "depend": "0.0035", "except": "0.0033", "late": "0.0051", "arrest": "0.0009", "bailout": "0.0028", "volatil": "0.0031", "disrupt": "0.0027", "complaint": "0.0013", "good": "0.0120", "greater": "0.0034", "disclos": "0.0029", "rebound": "0.0048", "stop": "0.0027", "break": "0.0019", "worst": "0.0037", "know": "0.0033", "press": "0.0065", "loss": "0.0108", "bar": "0.0005", "success": "0.0026", "lost": "0.0114", "outperform": "0.0022", "drop": "0.0454", "negat": "0.0030", "resolv": "0.0013", "defens": "0.0016", "benefit": "0.0065", "integr": "0.0024", "lose": "0.0052", "popular": "0.0009", "collaps": "0.0016", "crisi": "0.0100", "prevent": "0.0033", "confid": "0.0071", "slower": "0.0018", "shut": "0.0028", "slowdown": "0.0029", "strongest": "0.0016", "cost": "0.0373", "opportun": "0.0050", "fail": "0.0094", "close": "0.0262", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0265", "lead": "0.0136", "profit": "0.0343", "defend": "0.0013", "abl": "0.0055", "bad": "0.0020", "favor": "0.0056", "restructur": "0.0025", "outstand": "0.0038", "deficit": "0.0087", "progress": "0.0032", "boost": "0.0287", "correct": "0.0025", "encourag": "0.0017", "investig": "0.0037", "advanc": "0.0253", "weak": "0.0024", "ban": "0.0035", "slow": "0.0125", "excess": "0.0013", "disput": "0.0027", "strong": "0.0084", "great": "0.0033", "deterior": "0.0016", "unemploy": "0.0032", "contract": "0.0280", "threat": "0.0012", "improv": "0.0090", "allianc": "0.0013", "suspend": "0.0024", "effici": "0.0021", "declin": "0.0698", "win": "0.0056", "bankruptci": "0.0102", "shortag": "0.0024", "cancel": "0.0042", "stabl": "0.0024", "miss": "0.0030", "drought": "0.0103", "damag": "0.0035", "bolster": "0.0037", "better": "0.0057", "question": "0.0026", "construct": "0.0108", "doubt": "0.0013", "downgrad": "0.0033", "threaten": "0.0020", "unexpect": "0.0021", "forc": "0.0066", "hurt": "0.0052", "warn": "0.0013", "gain": "0.0705", "termin": "0.0039", "eas": "0.0061", "highest": "0.0155", "fraud": "0.0020", "default": "0.0103", "seiz": "0.0013", "will": "0.0010", "limit": "0.0072", "posit": "0.0106", "problem": "0.0044", "claim": "0.0051", "weaker": "0.0016", "advantag": "0.0038", "strengthen": "0.0088", "challeng": "0.0035", "premier": "0.0012", "worri": "0.0019", "alleg": "0.0021", "critic": "0.0033", "attract": "0.0068", "sever": "0.0048", "halt": "0.0041", "strength": "0.0016", "delay": "0.0090", "fire": "0.0021", "boom": "0.0011", "reject": "0.0031", "weaken": "0.0080", "difficult": "0.0018", "tighten": "0.0054", "effect": "0.0047", "resign": "0.0007", "alert": "0.0021", "quit": "0.0027", "refin": "0.0149", "postpon": "0.0046", "stabil": "0.0015", "stress": "0.0006", "liquid": "0.0049", "antitrust": "0.0039", "stronger": "0.0035", "su": "0.0038", "inform": "0.0079", "deni": "0.0021", "achiev": "0.0012"}, "17": {"recess": "0.0026", "opposit": "0.0031", "lack": "0.0018", "protest": "0.0026", "surpass": "0.0029", "fear": "0.0005", "suffer": "0.0012", "fine": "0.0008", "accus": "0.0010", "cut": "0.0227", "depend": "0.0031", "except": "0.0015", "late": "0.0044", "arrest": "0.0005", "bailout": "0.0017", "volatil": "0.0029", "disrupt": "0.0055", "complaint": "0.0005", "good": "0.0113", "greater": "0.0031", "disclos": "0.0028", "rebound": "0.0063", "stop": "0.0022", "break": "0.0023", "worst": "0.0036", "know": "0.0042", "press": "0.0055", "loss": "0.0102", "bar": "0.0009", "success": "0.0022", "lost": "0.0124", "outperform": "0.0014", "drop": "0.0477", "negat": "0.0019", "resolv": "0.0018", "defens": "0.0023", "benefit": "0.0076", "integr": "0.0026", "lose": "0.0095", "popular": "0.0014", "collaps": "0.0012", "crisi": "0.0074", "prevent": "0.0040", "confid": "0.0081", "slower": "0.0029", "shut": "0.0079", "slowdown": "0.0029", "strongest": "0.0026", "cost": "0.0375", "opportun": "0.0044", "fail": "0.0093", "close": "0.0265", "precipit": "0.0064", "concern": "0.0255", "lead": "0.0141", "profit": "0.0438", "defend": "0.0006", "abl": "0.0041", "bad": "0.0022", "favor": "0.0056", "restructur": "0.0023", "outstand": "0.0047", "deficit": "0.0082", "progress": "0.0017", "boost": "0.0343", "correct": "0.0017", "encourag": "0.0020", "investig": "0.0010", "advanc": "0.0270", "weak": "0.0014", "ban": "0.0023", "slow": "0.0150", "excess": "0.0012", "disput": "0.0019", "strong": "0.0064", "great": "0.0026", "deterior": "0.0009", "unemploy": "0.0042", "contract": "0.0256", "threat": "0.0013", "improv": "0.0102", "allianc": "0.0017", "suspend": "0.0013", "effici": "0.0015", "declin": "0.0737", "win": "0.0050", "bankruptci": "0.0013", "shortag": "0.0020", "cancel": "0.0023", "stabl": "0.0024", "miss": "0.0055", "drought": "0.0079", "damag": "0.0031", "bolster": "0.0045", "better": "0.0056", "question": "0.0020", "construct": "0.0095", "doubt": "0.0019", "downgrad": "0.0026", "threaten": "0.0022", "unexpect": "0.0027", "forc": "0.0087", "hurt": "0.0058", "warn": "0.0031", "gain": "0.0703", "termin": "0.0028", "eas": "0.0076", "highest": "0.0195", "fraud": "0.0004", "default": "0.0099", "seiz": "0.0010", "will": "0.0013", "limit": "0.0092", "posit": "0.0123", "problem": "0.0044", "claim": "0.0032", "weaker": "0.0014", "advantag": "0.0031", "strengthen": "0.0129", "challeng": "0.0031", "premier": "0.0022", "worri": "0.0010", "alleg": "0.0013", "critic": "0.0031", "attract": "0.0055", "sever": "0.0042", "halt": "0.0031", "strength": "0.0026", "delay": "0.0076", "fire": "0.0032", "boom": "0.0014", "reject": "0.0040", "weaken": "0.0073", "difficult": "0.0033", "tighten": "0.0037", "effect": "0.0029", "resign": "0.0014", "alert": "0.0023", "quit": "0.0026", "refin": "0.0163", "postpon": "0.0017", "stabil": "0.0031", "stress": "0.0015", "liquid": "0.0022", "antitrust": "0.0017", "stronger": "0.0038", "su": "0.0028", "inform": "0.0074", "deni": "0.0015", "achiev": "0.0019"}, "18": {"recess": "0.0056", "opposit": "0.0024", "lack": "0.0016", "protest": "0.0027", "surpass": "0.0024", "fear": "0.0024", "suffer": "0.0008", "fine": "0.0027", "accus": "0.0019", "cut": "0.0276", "depend": "0.0037", "except": "0.0021", "late": "0.0040", "arrest": "0.0011", "bailout": "0.0021", "volatil": "0.0053", "disrupt": "0.0019", "complaint": "0.0021", "good": "0.0096", "greater": "0.0027", "disclos": "0.0034", "rebound": "0.0080", "stop": "0.0040", "break": "0.0029", "worst": "0.0056", "know": "0.0021", "press": "0.0053", "loss": "0.0122", "bar": "0.0011", "success": "0.0027", "lost": "0.0135", "outperform": "0.0021", "drop": "0.0464", "negat": "0.0032", "resolv": "0.0016", "defens": "0.0016", "benefit": "0.0085", "integr": "0.0024", "lose": "0.0045", "popular": "0.0016", "collaps": "0.0029", "crisi": "0.0196", "prevent": "0.0053", "confid": "0.0050", "slower": "0.0032", "shut": "0.0034", "slowdown": "0.0027", "strongest": "0.0011", "cost": "0.0414", "opportun": "0.0034", "fail": "0.0109", "close": "0.0162", "precipit": "0.0005", "concern": "0.0265", "lead": "0.0154", "profit": "0.0387", "defend": "0.0027", "abl": "0.0056", "bad": "0.0034", "favor": "0.0045", "restructur": "0.0021", "outstand": "0.0045", "deficit": "0.0056", "progress": "0.0077", "boost": "0.0273", "correct": "0.0050", "encourag": "0.0013", "investig": "0.0037", "advanc": "0.0292", "weak": "0.0013", "ban": "0.0011", "slow": "0.0096", "excess": "0.0011", "disput": "0.0029", "strong": "0.0082", "great": "0.0019", "deterior": "0.0016", "unemploy": "0.0029", "contract": "0.0371", "threat": "0.0013", "improv": "0.0074", "allianc": "0.0008", "suspend": "0.0032", "effici": "0.0019", "declin": "0.0581", "win": "0.0098", "bankruptci": "0.0130", "shortag": "0.0024", "cancel": "0.0034", "stabl": "0.0016", "miss": "0.0048", "drought": "0.0011", "damag": "0.0024", "bolster": "0.0042", "better": "0.0053", "question": "0.0021", "construct": "0.0088", "doubt": "0.0019", "downgrad": "0.0040", "threaten": "0.0029", "unexpect": "0.0029", "forc": "0.0045", "hurt": "0.0074", "warn": "0.0008", "gain": "0.0740", "termin": "0.0027", "eas": "0.0056", "highest": "0.0159", "fraud": "0.0021", "default": "0.0077", "seiz": "0.0011", "will": "0.0013", "limit": "0.0077", "posit": "0.0072", "problem": "0.0037", "claim": "0.0061", "weaker": "0.0016", "advantag": "0.0034", "strengthen": "0.0085", "challeng": "0.0050", "premier": "0.0021", "worri": "0.0021", "alleg": "0.0029", "critic": "0.0040", "attract": "0.0064", "sever": "0.0056", "halt": "0.0048", "strength": "0.0016", "delay": "0.0088", "fire": "0.0008", "boom": "0.0008", "reject": "0.0032", "weaken": "0.0082", "difficult": "0.0013", "tighten": "0.0056", "effect": "0.0029", "resign": "0.0011", "alert": "0.0024", "quit": "0.0021", "refin": "0.0122", "postpon": "0.0032", "stabil": "0.0029", "stress": "0.0011", "liquid": "0.0048", "antitrust": "0.0016", "stronger": "0.0037", "su": "0.0027", "inform": "0.0058", "deni": "0.0013", "achiev": "0.0008"}, "19": {"recess": "0.0056", "opposit": "0.0016", "lack": "0.0056", "protest": "0.0008", "surpass": "0.0008", "fear": "0.0040", "suffer": "0.0016", "fine": "0.0024", "accus": "0.0008", "cut": "0.0167", "depend": "0.0040", "except": "0.0024", "late": "0.0064", "arrest": "0.0008", "bailout": "0.0008", "volatil": "0.0056", "disrupt": "0.0016", "complaint": "0.0024", "good": "0.0119", "greater": "0.0008", "disclos": "0.0032", "rebound": "0.0095", "stop": "0.0048", "break": "0.0032", "worst": "0.0032", "know": "0.0024", "press": "0.0040", "loss": "0.0175", "bar": "0.0024", "success": "0.0024", "lost": "0.0159", "outperform": "0.0016", "drop": "0.0635", "negat": "0.0008", "resolv": "0.0016", "defens": "0.0040", "benefit": "0.0071", "integr": "0.0016", "lose": "0.0071", "popular": "0.0008", "collaps": "0.0064", "crisi": "0.0191", "prevent": "0.0040", "confid": "0.0079", "slower": "0.0008", "shut": "0.0040", "slowdown": "0.0040", "strongest": "0.0008", "cost": "0.0246", "opportun": "0.0079", "fail": "0.0071", "close": "0.0230", "precipit": "0.0008", "concern": "0.0365", "lead": "0.0111", "profit": "0.0349", "defend": "0.0024", "abl": "0.0040", "bad": "0.0064", "favor": "0.0071", "restructur": "0.0008", "outstand": "0.0016", "deficit": "0.0032", "progress": "0.0016", "boost": "0.0175", "correct": "0.0048", "encourag": "0.0008", "investig": "0.0064", "advanc": "0.0207", "weak": "0.0048", "ban": "0.0032", "slow": "0.0143", "excess": "0.0024", "disput": "0.0024", "strong": "0.0087", "great": "0.0016", "deterior": "0.0032", "unemploy": "0.0079", "contract": "0.0230", "threat": "0.0032", "improv": "0.0087", "allianc": "0.0008", "suspend": "0.0024", "effici": "0.0016", "declin": "0.0723", "win": "0.0103", "bankruptci": "0.0008", "shortag": "0.0016", "cancel": "0.0095", "stabl": "0.0008", "miss": "0.0103", "drought": "0.0016", "damag": "0.0016", "bolster": "0.0024", "better": "0.0056", "question": "0.0032", "construct": "0.0056", "doubt": "0.0024", "downgrad": "0.0048", "threaten": "0.0040", "unexpect": "0.0024", "forc": "0.0064", "hurt": "0.0040", "warn": "0.0024", "gain": "0.0620", "termin": "0.0016", "eas": "0.0056", "highest": "0.0135", "fraud": "0.0016", "default": "0.0048", "seiz": "0.0016", "will": "0.0008", "limit": "0.0056", "posit": "0.0095", "problem": "0.0040", "claim": "0.0016", "weaker": "0.0056", "advantag": "0.0040", "strengthen": "0.0103", "challeng": "0.0024", "premier": "0.0079", "worri": "0.0032", "alleg": "0.0032", "critic": "0.0040", "attract": "0.0095", "sever": "0.0040", "halt": "0.0040", "strength": "0.0008", "delay": "0.0119", "fire": "0.0056", "boom": "0.0016", "reject": "0.0079", "weaken": "0.0135", "difficult": "0.0024", "tighten": "0.0016", "effect": "0.0040", "resign": "0.0008", "alert": "0.0032", "quit": "0.0016", "refin": "0.0056", "postpon": "0.0016", "stabil": "0.0056", "stress": "0.0016", "liquid": "0.0016", "antitrust": "0.0008", "stronger": "0.0032", "su": "0.0008", "inform": "0.0048", "deni": "0.0032", "achiev": "0.0040"}, "20": {"recess": "0.0041", "opposit": "0.0008", "lack": "0.0025", "protest": "0.0025", "surpass": "0.0017", "fear": "0.0017", "suffer": "0.0017", "fine": "0.0025", "accus": "0.0017", "cut": "0.0331", "depend": "0.0041", "except": "0.0041", "late": "0.0050", "arrest": "0.0017", "bailout": "0.0050", "volatil": "0.0025", "disrupt": "0.0017", "complaint": "0.0017", "good": "0.0116", "greater": "0.0033", "disclos": "0.0008", "rebound": "0.0099", "stop": "0.0017", "break": "0.0008", "worst": "0.0025", "know": "0.0058", "press": "0.0074", "loss": "0.0058", "bar": "0.0008", "success": "0.0033", "lost": "0.0116", "outperform": "0.0033", "drop": "0.0504", "negat": "0.0058", "resolv": "0.0008", "defens": "0.0008", "benefit": "0.0074", "integr": "0.0041", "lose": "0.0041", "popular": "0.0008", "collaps": "0.0017", "crisi": "0.0273", "prevent": "0.0058", "confid": "0.0066", "slower": "0.0025", "shut": "0.0041", "slowdown": "0.0025", "strongest": "0.0008", "cost": "0.0430", "opportun": "0.0099", "fail": "0.0124", "close": "0.0240", "precipit": "0.0008", "concern": "0.0306", "lead": "0.0107", "profit": "0.0174", "defend": "0.0050", "abl": "0.0041", "bad": "0.0033", "favor": "0.0041", "restructur": "0.0008", "outstand": "0.0033", "deficit": "0.0132", "progress": "0.0025", "boost": "0.0231", "correct": "0.0033", "encourag": "0.0017", "investig": "0.0017", "advanc": "0.0140", "weak": "0.0041", "ban": "0.0041", "slow": "0.0140", "excess": "0.0033", "disput": "0.0025", "strong": "0.0074", "great": "0.0017", "deterior": "0.0017", "unemploy": "0.0025", "contract": "0.0397", "threat": "0.0008", "improv": "0.0074", "allianc": "0.0008", "suspend": "0.0017", "effici": "0.0008", "declin": "0.0802", "win": "0.0050", "bankruptci": "0.0008", "shortag": "0.0058", "cancel": "0.0041", "stabl": "0.0008", "miss": "0.0066", "drought": "0.0017", "damag": "0.0008", "bolster": "0.0033", "better": "0.0025", "question": "0.0017", "construct": "0.0149", "doubt": "0.0033", "downgrad": "0.0050", "threaten": "0.0025", "unexpect": "0.0033", "forc": "0.0124", "hurt": "0.0041", "warn": "0.0025", "gain": "0.0545", "termin": "0.0033", "eas": "0.0041", "highest": "0.0091", "fraud": "0.0008", "default": "0.0124", "seiz": "0.0041", "will": "0.0008", "limit": "0.0074", "posit": "0.0083", "problem": "0.0050", "claim": "0.0017", "weaker": "0.0041", "advantag": "0.0041", "strengthen": "0.0107", "challeng": "0.0017", "premier": "0.0066", "worri": "0.0017", "alleg": "0.0017", "critic": "0.0017", "attract": "0.0050", "sever": "0.0017", "halt": "0.0025", "strength": "0.0050", "delay": "0.0050", "fire": "0.0058", "boom": "0.0017", "reject": "0.0025", "weaken": "0.0058", "difficult": "0.0025", "tighten": "0.0083", "effect": "0.0025", "resign": "0.0017", "alert": "0.0033", "quit": "0.0008", "refin": "0.0099", "postpon": "0.0025", "stabil": "0.0033", "stress": "0.0008", "liquid": "0.0041", "antitrust": "0.0033", "stronger": "0.0066", "su": "0.0033", "inform": "0.0066", "deni": "0.0025", "achiev": "0.0050"}}, "CHILE65": {"1": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0101", "lack": "0.0034", "protest": "0.0034", "surpass": "0.0034", "fear": "0.0034", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0034", "accus": "0.0034", "cut": "0.0168", "depend": "0.0034", "except": "0.0034", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0034", "bailout": "0.0168", "volatil": "0.0034", "disrupt": "0.0034", "complaint": "0.0034", "good": "0.0034", "greater": "0.0034", "disclos": "0.0034", "rebound": "0.0101", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0034", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0034", "press": "0.0034", "loss": "0.0168", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0034", "outperform": "0.0034", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0034", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0101", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0034", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0168", "collaps": "0.0168", "crisi": "0.0168", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0168", "slower": "0.0034", "shut": "0.0034", "slowdown": "0.0034", "strongest": "0.0034", "cost": "0.0201", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0101", "close": "0.0134", "precipit": "0.0034", "concern": "0.0168", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0101", "defend": "0.0034", "abl": "0.0034", "bad": "0.0034", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0034", "deficit": "0.0034", "progress": "0.0034", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0034", "encourag": "0.0034", "investig": "0.0034", "advanc": "0.0168", "weak": "0.0034", "ban": "0.0034", "slow": "0.0034", "excess": "0.0034", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0034", "deterior": "0.0034", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0034", "improv": "0.0034", "allianc": "0.0034", "suspend": "0.0034", "effici": "0.0034", "declin": "0.0302", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0034", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0034", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0034", "drought": "0.0034", "damag": "0.0101", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0101", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0034", "doubt": "0.0034", "downgrad": "0.0034", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0034", "forc": "0.0403", "hurt": "0.0034", "warn": "0.0034", "gain": "0.0403", "termin": "0.0034", "eas": "0.0034", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0034", "default": "0.0101", "seiz": "0.0168", "will": "0.0034", "limit": "0.0034", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0034", "claim": "0.0034", "weaker": "0.0034", "advantag": "0.0034", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0034", "premier": "0.0034", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0034", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0034", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0034", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0101", "boom": "0.0034", "reject": "0.0034", "weaken": "0.0034", "difficult": "0.0034", "tighten": "0.0134", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0134", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0034", "postpon": "0.0034", "stabil": "0.0034", "stress": "0.0101", "liquid": "0.0034", "antitrust": "0.0034", "stronger": "0.0034", "su": "0.0034", "inform": "0.0034", "deni": "0.0235", "achiev": "0.0034"}, "2": {"recess": "0.0035", "opposit": "0.0038", "lack": "0.0031", "protest": "0.0031", "surpass": "0.0012", "fear": "0.0015", "suffer": "0.0012", "fine": "0.0023", "accus": "0.0050", "cut": "0.0150", "depend": "0.0015", "except": "0.0023", "late": "0.0081", "arrest": "0.0015", "bailout": "0.0054", "volatil": "0.0054", "disrupt": "0.0019", "complaint": "0.0046", "good": "0.0084", "greater": "0.0054", "disclos": "0.0092", "rebound": "0.0058", "stop": "0.0054", "break": "0.0031", "worst": "0.0046", "know": "0.0038", "press": "0.0061", "loss": "0.0096", "bar": "0.0038", "success": "0.0035", "lost": "0.0154", "outperform": "0.0038", "drop": "0.0357", "negat": "0.0038", "resolv": "0.0019", "defens": "0.0058", "benefit": "0.0058", "integr": "0.0031", "lose": "0.0073", "popular": "0.0050", "collaps": "0.0038", "crisi": "0.0230", "prevent": "0.0027", "confid": "0.0119", "slower": "0.0038", "shut": "0.0023", "slowdown": "0.0015", "strongest": "0.0027", "cost": "0.0234", "opportun": "0.0031", "fail": "0.0111", "close": "0.0223", "precipit": "0.0004", "concern": "0.0334", "lead": "0.0188", "profit": "0.0219", "defend": "0.0027", "abl": "0.0054", "bad": "0.0038", "favor": "0.0061", "restructur": "0.0061", "outstand": "0.0042", "deficit": "0.0146", "progress": "0.0012", "boost": "0.0184", "correct": "0.0008", "encourag": "0.0023", "investig": "0.0100", "advanc": "0.0154", "weak": "0.0046", "ban": "0.0115", "slow": "0.0154", "excess": "0.0019", "disput": "0.0019", "strong": "0.0038", "great": "0.0031", "deterior": "0.0031", "unemploy": "0.0061", "contract": "0.0142", "threat": "0.0012", "improv": "0.0123", "allianc": "0.0027", "suspend": "0.0008", "effici": "0.0038", "declin": "0.0787", "win": "0.0027", "bankruptci": "0.0027", "shortag": "0.0004", "cancel": "0.0023", "stabl": "0.0069", "miss": "0.0015", "drought": "0.0004", "damag": "0.0031", "bolster": "0.0038", "better": "0.0035", "question": "0.0042", "construct": "0.0096", "doubt": "0.0015", "downgrad": "0.0058", "threaten": "0.0031", "unexpect": "0.0012", "forc": "0.0069", "hurt": "0.0008", "warn": "0.0031", "gain": "0.0373", "termin": "0.0027", "eas": "0.0031", "highest": "0.0111", "fraud": "0.0035", "default": "0.0173", "seiz": "0.0046", "will": "0.0019", "limit": "0.0058", "posit": "0.0115", "problem": "0.0046", "claim": "0.0046", "weaker": "0.0012", "advantag": "0.0023", "strengthen": "0.0077", "challeng": "0.0054", "premier": "0.0004", "worri": "0.0015", "alleg": "0.0031", "critic": "0.0035", "attract": "0.0069", "sever": "0.0058", "halt": "0.0015", "strength": "0.0019", "delay": "0.0065", "fire": "0.0023", "boom": "0.0027", "reject": "0.0019", "weaken": "0.0069", "difficult": "0.0023", "tighten": "0.0046", "effect": "0.0069", "resign": "0.0073", "alert": "0.0035", "quit": "0.0046", "refin": "0.0088", "postpon": "0.0134", "stabil": "0.0054", "stress": "0.0054", "liquid": "0.0096", "antitrust": "0.0019", "stronger": "0.0031", "su": "0.0031", "inform": "0.0100", "deni": "0.0054", "achiev": "0.0031"}, "3": {"recess": "0.0026", "opposit": "0.0030", "lack": "0.0024", "protest": "0.0046", "surpass": "0.0011", "fear": "0.0007", "suffer": "0.0015", "fine": "0.0013", "accus": "0.0031", "cut": "0.0229", "depend": "0.0033", "except": "0.0022", "late": "0.0072", "arrest": "0.0026", "bailout": "0.0093", "volatil": "0.0033", "disrupt": "0.0013", "complaint": "0.0024", "good": "0.0083", "greater": "0.0039", "disclos": "0.0033", "rebound": "0.0033", "stop": "0.0035", "break": "0.0011", "worst": "0.0056", "know": "0.0030", "press": "0.0087", "loss": "0.0174", "bar": "0.0030", "success": "0.0044", "lost": "0.0168", "outperform": "0.0019", "drop": "0.0472", "negat": "0.0037", "resolv": "0.0013", "defens": "0.0035", "benefit": "0.0046", "integr": "0.0028", "lose": "0.0063", "popular": "0.0030", "collaps": "0.0009", "crisi": "0.0213", "prevent": "0.0039", "confid": "0.0076", "slower": "0.0013", "shut": "0.0011", "slowdown": "0.0019", "strongest": "0.0039", "cost": "0.0305", "opportun": "0.0037", "fail": "0.0089", "close": "0.0276", "precipit": "0.0002", "concern": "0.0289", "lead": "0.0124", "profit": "0.0357", "defend": "0.0009", "abl": "0.0028", "bad": "0.0057", "favor": "0.0030", "restructur": "0.0028", "outstand": "0.0052", "deficit": "0.0087", "progress": "0.0011", "boost": "0.0205", "correct": "0.0028", "encourag": "0.0026", "investig": "0.0043", "advanc": "0.0226", "weak": "0.0031", "ban": "0.0035", "slow": "0.0142", "excess": "0.0009", "disput": "0.0031", "strong": "0.0072", "great": "0.0020", "deterior": "0.0013", "unemploy": "0.0037", "contract": "0.0128", "threat": "0.0019", "improv": "0.0080", "allianc": "0.0039", "suspend": "0.0015", "effici": "0.0020", "declin": "0.0774", "win": "0.0070", "bankruptci": "0.0028", "shortag": "0.0006", "cancel": "0.0017", "stabl": "0.0026", "miss": "0.0035", "drought": "0.0002", "damag": "0.0026", "bolster": "0.0035", "better": "0.0048", "question": "0.0044", "construct": "0.0122", "doubt": "0.0026", "downgrad": "0.0046", "threaten": "0.0035", "unexpect": "0.0037", "forc": "0.0074", "hurt": "0.0052", "warn": "0.0052", "gain": "0.0644", "termin": "0.0007", "eas": "0.0093", "highest": "0.0161", "fraud": "0.0015", "default": "0.0133", "seiz": "0.0015", "will": "0.0007", "limit": "0.0085", "posit": "0.0104", "problem": "0.0059", "claim": "0.0083", "weaker": "0.0019", "advantag": "0.0019", "strengthen": "0.0089", "challeng": "0.0030", "premier": "0.0022", "worri": "0.0015", "alleg": "0.0035", "critic": "0.0020", "attract": "0.0070", "sever": "0.0043", "halt": "0.0033", "strength": "0.0030", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0046", "boom": "0.0011", "reject": "0.0052", "weaken": "0.0087", "difficult": "0.0024", "tighten": "0.0030", "effect": "0.0048", "resign": "0.0019", "alert": "0.0024", "quit": "0.0033", "refin": "0.0059", "postpon": "0.0022", "stabil": "0.0024", "stress": "0.0050", "liquid": "0.0059", "antitrust": "0.0020", "stronger": "0.0022", "su": "0.0011", "inform": "0.0109", "deni": "0.0052", "achiev": "0.0013"}, "4": {"recess": "0.0061", "opposit": "0.0070", "lack": "0.0035", "protest": "0.0026", "surpass": "0.0022", "fear": "0.0017", "suffer": "0.0026", "fine": "0.0035", "accus": "0.0017", "cut": "0.0293", "depend": "0.0044", "except": "0.0013", "late": "0.0044", "arrest": "0.0004", "bailout": "0.0039", "volatil": "0.0039", "disrupt": "0.0009", "complaint": "0.0017", "good": "0.0127", "greater": "0.0035", "disclos": "0.0092", "rebound": "0.0048", "stop": "0.0052", "break": "0.0009", "worst": "0.0048", "know": "0.0070", "press": "0.0057", "loss": "0.0170", "bar": "0.0013", "success": "0.0017", "lost": "0.0153", "outperform": "0.0026", "drop": "0.0406", "negat": "0.0039", "resolv": "0.0009", "defens": "0.0013", "benefit": "0.0035", "integr": "0.0031", "lose": "0.0057", "popular": "0.0044", "collaps": "0.0044", "crisi": "0.0284", "prevent": "0.0035", "confid": "0.0079", "slower": "0.0013", "shut": "0.0044", "slowdown": "0.0009", "strongest": "0.0026", "cost": "0.0328", "opportun": "0.0039", "fail": "0.0079", "close": "0.0183", "precipit": "0.0004", "concern": "0.0367", "lead": "0.0109", "profit": "0.0280", "defend": "0.0031", "abl": "0.0039", "bad": "0.0061", "favor": "0.0044", "restructur": "0.0057", "outstand": "0.0048", "deficit": "0.0149", "progress": "0.0013", "boost": "0.0192", "correct": "0.0039", "encourag": "0.0013", "investig": "0.0026", "advanc": "0.0192", "weak": "0.0074", "ban": "0.0052", "slow": "0.0144", "excess": "0.0022", "disput": "0.0017", "strong": "0.0022", "great": "0.0017", "deterior": "0.0035", "unemploy": "0.0017", "contract": "0.0183", "threat": "0.0031", "improv": "0.0087", "allianc": "0.0022", "suspend": "0.0009", "effici": "0.0009", "declin": "0.0529", "win": "0.0022", "bankruptci": "0.0039", "shortag": "0.0009", "cancel": "0.0017", "stabl": "0.0009", "miss": "0.0035", "drought": "0.0009", "damag": "0.0031", "bolster": "0.0039", "better": "0.0048", "question": "0.0039", "construct": "0.0026", "doubt": "0.0017", "downgrad": "0.0066", "threaten": "0.0031", "unexpect": "0.0044", "forc": "0.0100", "hurt": "0.0035", "warn": "0.0035", "gain": "0.0507", "termin": "0.0026", "eas": "0.0100", "highest": "0.0232", "fraud": "0.0026", "default": "0.0197", "seiz": "0.0039", "will": "0.0017", "limit": "0.0114", "posit": "0.0109", "problem": "0.0100", "claim": "0.0013", "weaker": "0.0004", "advantag": "0.0022", "strengthen": "0.0061", "challeng": "0.0022", "premier": "0.0017", "worri": "0.0048", "alleg": "0.0022", "critic": "0.0035", "attract": "0.0061", "sever": "0.0057", "halt": "0.0039", "strength": "0.0022", "delay": "0.0092", "fire": "0.0017", "boom": "0.0052", "reject": "0.0013", "weaken": "0.0100", "difficult": "0.0031", "tighten": "0.0026", "effect": "0.0061", "resign": "0.0013", "alert": "0.0031", "quit": "0.0035", "refin": "0.0070", "postpon": "0.0096", "stabil": "0.0039", "stress": "0.0079", "liquid": "0.0048", "antitrust": "0.0022", "stronger": "0.0048", "su": "0.0017", "inform": "0.0066", "deni": "0.0031", "achiev": "0.0009"}, "5": {"recess": "0.0040", "opposit": "0.0038", "lack": "0.0020", "protest": "0.0036", "surpass": "0.0021", "fear": "0.0024", "suffer": "0.0023", "fine": "0.0017", "accus": "0.0022", "cut": "0.0229", "depend": "0.0033", "except": "0.0015", "late": "0.0053", "arrest": "0.0015", "bailout": "0.0083", "volatil": "0.0034", "disrupt": "0.0012", "complaint": "0.0037", "good": "0.0116", "greater": "0.0030", "disclos": "0.0061", "rebound": "0.0063", "stop": "0.0030", "break": "0.0025", "worst": "0.0042", "know": "0.0030", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0153", "bar": "0.0015", "success": "0.0025", "lost": "0.0140", "outperform": "0.0020", "drop": "0.0481", "negat": "0.0030", "resolv": "0.0016", "defens": "0.0019", "benefit": "0.0066", "integr": "0.0030", "lose": "0.0061", "popular": "0.0021", "collaps": "0.0013", "crisi": "0.0210", "prevent": "0.0032", "confid": "0.0077", "slower": "0.0020", "shut": "0.0016", "slowdown": "0.0018", "strongest": "0.0034", "cost": "0.0343", "opportun": "0.0032", "fail": "0.0098", "close": "0.0215", "precipit": "0.0001", "concern": "0.0281", "lead": "0.0140", "profit": "0.0263", "defend": "0.0027", "abl": "0.0028", "bad": "0.0056", "favor": "0.0044", "restructur": "0.0050", "outstand": "0.0070", "deficit": "0.0118", "progress": "0.0011", "boost": "0.0246", "correct": "0.0022", "encourag": "0.0016", "investig": "0.0058", "advanc": "0.0171", "weak": "0.0026", "ban": "0.0022", "slow": "0.0127", "excess": "0.0016", "disput": "0.0025", "strong": "0.0053", "great": "0.0014", "deterior": "0.0018", "unemploy": "0.0057", "contract": "0.0155", "threat": "0.0018", "improv": "0.0084", "allianc": "0.0031", "suspend": "0.0023", "effici": "0.0014", "declin": "0.0941", "win": "0.0039", "bankruptci": "0.0024", "shortag": "0.0011", "cancel": "0.0029", "stabl": "0.0037", "miss": "0.0034", "drought": "0.0005", "damag": "0.0046", "bolster": "0.0027", "better": "0.0050", "question": "0.0036", "construct": "0.0116", "doubt": "0.0012", "downgrad": "0.0052", "threaten": "0.0039", "unexpect": "0.0030", "forc": "0.0076", "hurt": "0.0041", "warn": "0.0022", "gain": "0.0586", "termin": "0.0009", "eas": "0.0084", "highest": "0.0155", "fraud": "0.0025", "default": "0.0142", "seiz": "0.0029", "will": "0.0013", "limit": "0.0071", "posit": "0.0106", "problem": "0.0063", "claim": "0.0098", "weaker": "0.0013", "advantag": "0.0025", "strengthen": "0.0093", "challeng": "0.0033", "premier": "0.0007", "worri": "0.0012", "alleg": "0.0022", "critic": "0.0019", "attract": "0.0061", "sever": "0.0040", "halt": "0.0029", "strength": "0.0016", "delay": "0.0076", "fire": "0.0043", "boom": "0.0017", "reject": "0.0027", "weaken": "0.0065", "difficult": "0.0023", "tighten": "0.0027", "effect": "0.0041", "resign": "0.0009", "alert": "0.0038", "quit": "0.0034", "refin": "0.0128", "postpon": "0.0038", "stabil": "0.0024", "stress": "0.0055", "liquid": "0.0031", "antitrust": "0.0013", "stronger": "0.0026", "su": "0.0035", "inform": "0.0087", "deni": "0.0046", "achiev": "0.0019"}, "6": {"recess": "0.0047", "opposit": "0.0031", "lack": "0.0016", "protest": "0.0033", "surpass": "0.0013", "fear": "0.0018", "suffer": "0.0026", "fine": "0.0016", "accus": "0.0010", "cut": "0.0238", "depend": "0.0028", "except": "0.0023", "late": "0.0061", "arrest": "0.0009", "bailout": "0.0075", "volatil": "0.0030", "disrupt": "0.0013", "complaint": "0.0047", "good": "0.0129", "greater": "0.0040", "disclos": "0.0073", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0036", "break": "0.0024", "worst": "0.0046", "know": "0.0030", "press": "0.0074", "loss": "0.0142", "bar": "0.0010", "success": "0.0018", "lost": "0.0165", "outperform": "0.0010", "drop": "0.0451", "negat": "0.0036", "resolv": "0.0017", "defens": "0.0018", "benefit": "0.0058", "integr": "0.0018", "lose": "0.0053", "popular": "0.0016", "collaps": "0.0021", "crisi": "0.0172", "prevent": "0.0046", "confid": "0.0054", "slower": "0.0017", "shut": "0.0016", "slowdown": "0.0020", "strongest": "0.0027", "cost": "0.0304", "opportun": "0.0028", "fail": "0.0085", "close": "0.0235", "precipit": "0.0001", "concern": "0.0263", "lead": "0.0148", "profit": "0.0322", "defend": "0.0016", "abl": "0.0036", "bad": "0.0083", "favor": "0.0038", "restructur": "0.0065", "outstand": "0.0077", "deficit": "0.0104", "progress": "0.0010", "boost": "0.0229", "correct": "0.0027", "encourag": "0.0016", "investig": "0.0023", "advanc": "0.0202", "weak": "0.0030", "ban": "0.0028", "slow": "0.0115", "excess": "0.0013", "disput": "0.0024", "strong": "0.0071", "great": "0.0013", "deterior": "0.0021", "unemploy": "0.0050", "contract": "0.0158", "threat": "0.0011", "improv": "0.0083", "allianc": "0.0030", "suspend": "0.0023", "effici": "0.0014", "declin": "0.0859", "win": "0.0055", "bankruptci": "0.0021", "shortag": "0.0007", "cancel": "0.0018", "stabl": "0.0046", "miss": "0.0043", "drought": "0.0007", "damag": "0.0047", "bolster": "0.0028", "better": "0.0055", "question": "0.0037", "construct": "0.0122", "doubt": "0.0023", "downgrad": "0.0064", "threaten": "0.0036", "unexpect": "0.0037", "forc": "0.0077", "hurt": "0.0040", "warn": "0.0016", "gain": "0.0610", "termin": "0.0006", "eas": "0.0071", "highest": "0.0202", "fraud": "0.0013", "default": "0.0155", "seiz": "0.0011", "will": "0.0023", "limit": "0.0084", "posit": "0.0121", "problem": "0.0065", "claim": "0.0061", "weaker": "0.0017", "advantag": "0.0023", "strengthen": "0.0100", "challeng": "0.0040", "premier": "0.0010", "worri": "0.0021", "alleg": "0.0014", "critic": "0.0014", "attract": "0.0063", "sever": "0.0036", "halt": "0.0038", "strength": "0.0018", "delay": "0.0090", "fire": "0.0021", "boom": "0.0011", "reject": "0.0034", "weaken": "0.0073", "difficult": "0.0023", "tighten": "0.0038", "effect": "0.0058", "resign": "0.0020", "alert": "0.0030", "quit": "0.0020", "refin": "0.0121", "postpon": "0.0038", "stabil": "0.0031", "stress": "0.0048", "liquid": "0.0050", "antitrust": "0.0014", "stronger": "0.0016", "su": "0.0009", "inform": "0.0107", "deni": "0.0044", "achiev": "0.0016"}, "7": {"recess": "0.0070", "opposit": "0.0007", "lack": "0.0017", "protest": "0.0017", "surpass": "0.0017", "fear": "0.0023", "suffer": "0.0010", "fine": "0.0044", "accus": "0.0060", "cut": "0.0161", "depend": "0.0017", "except": "0.0023", "late": "0.0077", "arrest": "0.0027", "bailout": "0.0060", "volatil": "0.0037", "disrupt": "0.0020", "complaint": "0.0040", "good": "0.0147", "greater": "0.0020", "disclos": "0.0090", "rebound": "0.0090", "stop": "0.0057", "break": "0.0030", "worst": "0.0044", "know": "0.0050", "press": "0.0054", "loss": "0.0158", "bar": "0.0020", "success": "0.0013", "lost": "0.0154", "outperform": "0.0020", "drop": "0.0352", "negat": "0.0030", "resolv": "0.0010", "defens": "0.0023", "benefit": "0.0047", "integr": "0.0030", "lose": "0.0044", "popular": "0.0027", "collaps": "0.0030", "crisi": "0.0188", "prevent": "0.0023", "confid": "0.0050", "slower": "0.0027", "shut": "0.0010", "slowdown": "0.0010", "strongest": "0.0057", "cost": "0.0285", "opportun": "0.0027", "fail": "0.0050", "close": "0.0218", "precipit": "0.0003", "concern": "0.0258", "lead": "0.0137", "profit": "0.0208", "defend": "0.0027", "abl": "0.0030", "bad": "0.0077", "favor": "0.0050", "restructur": "0.0037", "outstand": "0.0060", "deficit": "0.0151", "progress": "0.0007", "boost": "0.0241", "correct": "0.0044", "encourag": "0.0023", "investig": "0.0141", "advanc": "0.0258", "weak": "0.0027", "ban": "0.0010", "slow": "0.0144", "excess": "0.0013", "disput": "0.0020", "strong": "0.0064", "great": "0.0020", "deterior": "0.0020", "unemploy": "0.0087", "contract": "0.0111", "threat": "0.0007", "improv": "0.0107", "allianc": "0.0007", "suspend": "0.0020", "effici": "0.0007", "declin": "0.0798", "win": "0.0044", "bankruptci": "0.0020", "shortag": "0.0013", "cancel": "0.0013", "stabl": "0.0020", "miss": "0.0034", "drought": "0.0007", "damag": "0.0054", "bolster": "0.0047", "better": "0.0037", "question": "0.0034", "construct": "0.0101", "doubt": "0.0027", "downgrad": "0.0030", "threaten": "0.0020", "unexpect": "0.0040", "forc": "0.0044", "hurt": "0.0023", "warn": "0.0030", "gain": "0.0627", "termin": "0.0010", "eas": "0.0087", "highest": "0.0168", "fraud": "0.0040", "default": "0.0147", "seiz": "0.0027", "will": "0.0020", "limit": "0.0050", "posit": "0.0111", "problem": "0.0054", "claim": "0.0090", "weaker": "0.0017", "advantag": "0.0023", "strengthen": "0.0117", "challeng": "0.0027", "premier": "0.0003", "worri": "0.0034", "alleg": "0.0030", "critic": "0.0010", "attract": "0.0044", "sever": "0.0047", "halt": "0.0020", "strength": "0.0020", "delay": "0.0131", "fire": "0.0027", "boom": "0.0017", "reject": "0.0020", "weaken": "0.0097", "difficult": "0.0013", "tighten": "0.0047", "effect": "0.0044", "resign": "0.0010", "alert": "0.0044", "quit": "0.0020", "refin": "0.0121", "postpon": "0.0034", "stabil": "0.0040", "stress": "0.0161", "liquid": "0.0034", "antitrust": "0.0013", "stronger": "0.0020", "su": "0.0050", "inform": "0.0114", "deni": "0.0050", "achiev": "0.0007"}, "8": {"recess": "0.0050", "opposit": "0.0035", "lack": "0.0028", "protest": "0.0014", "surpass": "0.0007", "fear": "0.0021", "suffer": "0.0014", "fine": "0.0014", "accus": "0.0043", "cut": "0.0234", "depend": "0.0050", "except": "0.0043", "late": "0.0035", "arrest": "0.0043", "bailout": "0.0057", "volatil": "0.0050", "disrupt": "0.0021", "complaint": "0.0035", "good": "0.0170", "greater": "0.0035", "disclos": "0.0043", "rebound": "0.0028", "stop": "0.0021", "break": "0.0028", "worst": "0.0071", "know": "0.0028", "press": "0.0057", "loss": "0.0142", "bar": "0.0028", "success": "0.0064", "lost": "0.0114", "outperform": "0.0014", "drop": "0.0397", "negat": "0.0043", "resolv": "0.0014", "defens": "0.0035", "benefit": "0.0057", "integr": "0.0014", "lose": "0.0099", "popular": "0.0035", "collaps": "0.0021", "crisi": "0.0121", "prevent": "0.0028", "confid": "0.0078", "slower": "0.0028", "shut": "0.0007", "slowdown": "0.0043", "strongest": "0.0028", "cost": "0.0334", "opportun": "0.0050", "fail": "0.0085", "close": "0.0170", "precipit": "0.0007", "concern": "0.0177", "lead": "0.0099", "profit": "0.0206", "defend": "0.0064", "abl": "0.0021", "bad": "0.0014", "favor": "0.0050", "restructur": "0.0092", "outstand": "0.0064", "deficit": "0.0135", "progress": "0.0043", "boost": "0.0241", "correct": "0.0014", "encourag": "0.0014", "investig": "0.0078", "advanc": "0.0192", "weak": "0.0007", "ban": "0.0035", "slow": "0.0106", "excess": "0.0014", "disput": "0.0021", "strong": "0.0064", "great": "0.0028", "deterior": "0.0057", "unemploy": "0.0071", "contract": "0.0170", "threat": "0.0021", "improv": "0.0078", "allianc": "0.0028", "suspend": "0.0021", "effici": "0.0028", "declin": "0.0681", "win": "0.0064", "bankruptci": "0.0050", "shortag": "0.0007", "cancel": "0.0014", "stabl": "0.0014", "miss": "0.0028", "drought": "0.0007", "damag": "0.0071", "bolster": "0.0043", "better": "0.0057", "question": "0.0057", "construct": "0.0106", "doubt": "0.0014", "downgrad": "0.0071", "threaten": "0.0021", "unexpect": "0.0057", "forc": "0.0092", "hurt": "0.0021", "warn": "0.0050", "gain": "0.0696", "termin": "0.0021", "eas": "0.0114", "highest": "0.0156", "fraud": "0.0057", "default": "0.0170", "seiz": "0.0021", "will": "0.0007", "limit": "0.0043", "posit": "0.0106", "problem": "0.0043", "claim": "0.0064", "weaker": "0.0050", "advantag": "0.0014", "strengthen": "0.0071", "challeng": "0.0035", "premier": "0.0014", "worri": "0.0021", "alleg": "0.0085", "critic": "0.0028", "attract": "0.0057", "sever": "0.0021", "halt": "0.0028", "strength": "0.0014", "delay": "0.0035", "fire": "0.0057", "boom": "0.0028", "reject": "0.0050", "weaken": "0.0028", "difficult": "0.0028", "tighten": "0.0043", "effect": "0.0057", "resign": "0.0007", "alert": "0.0021", "quit": "0.0028", "refin": "0.0057", "postpon": "0.0028", "stabil": "0.0028", "stress": "0.0007", "liquid": "0.0057", "antitrust": "0.0007", "stronger": "0.0028", "su": "0.0121", "inform": "0.0078", "deni": "0.0121", "achiev": "0.0028"}, "9": {"recess": "0.0042", "opposit": "0.0025", "lack": "0.0032", "protest": "0.0039", "surpass": "0.0011", "fear": "0.0011", "suffer": "0.0021", "fine": "0.0014", "accus": "0.0018", "cut": "0.0221", "depend": "0.0049", "except": "0.0011", "late": "0.0056", "arrest": "0.0025", "bailout": "0.0123", "volatil": "0.0039", "disrupt": "0.0011", "complaint": "0.0021", "good": "0.0091", "greater": "0.0032", "disclos": "0.0074", "rebound": "0.0039", "stop": "0.0042", "break": "0.0032", "worst": "0.0056", "know": "0.0021", "press": "0.0053", "loss": "0.0204", "bar": "0.0028", "success": "0.0025", "lost": "0.0130", "outperform": "0.0018", "drop": "0.0456", "negat": "0.0053", "resolv": "0.0014", "defens": "0.0042", "benefit": "0.0060", "integr": "0.0007", "lose": "0.0035", "popular": "0.0032", "collaps": "0.0042", "crisi": "0.0207", "prevent": "0.0056", "confid": "0.0060", "slower": "0.0021", "shut": "0.0011", "slowdown": "0.0014", "strongest": "0.0039", "cost": "0.0291", "opportun": "0.0063", "fail": "0.0119", "close": "0.0253", "precipit": "0.0004", "concern": "0.0323", "lead": "0.0162", "profit": "0.0193", "defend": "0.0025", "abl": "0.0042", "bad": "0.0042", "favor": "0.0042", "restructur": "0.0077", "outstand": "0.0018", "deficit": "0.0109", "progress": "0.0021", "boost": "0.0197", "correct": "0.0035", "encourag": "0.0011", "investig": "0.0042", "advanc": "0.0228", "weak": "0.0018", "ban": "0.0021", "slow": "0.0098", "excess": "0.0032", "disput": "0.0014", "strong": "0.0060", "great": "0.0039", "deterior": "0.0021", "unemploy": "0.0028", "contract": "0.0147", "threat": "0.0021", "improv": "0.0084", "allianc": "0.0046", "suspend": "0.0018", "effici": "0.0011", "declin": "0.0713", "win": "0.0063", "bankruptci": "0.0025", "shortag": "0.0011", "cancel": "0.0035", "stabl": "0.0035", "miss": "0.0042", "drought": "0.0004", "damag": "0.0060", "bolster": "0.0021", "better": "0.0039", "question": "0.0049", "construct": "0.0119", "doubt": "0.0025", "downgrad": "0.0070", "threaten": "0.0035", "unexpect": "0.0025", "forc": "0.0063", "hurt": "0.0042", "warn": "0.0021", "gain": "0.0653", "termin": "0.0014", "eas": "0.0081", "highest": "0.0126", "fraud": "0.0014", "default": "0.0176", "seiz": "0.0021", "will": "0.0007", "limit": "0.0056", "posit": "0.0095", "problem": "0.0056", "claim": "0.0077", "weaker": "0.0011", "advantag": "0.0032", "strengthen": "0.0063", "challeng": "0.0028", "premier": "0.0007", "worri": "0.0032", "alleg": "0.0014", "critic": "0.0025", "attract": "0.0070", "sever": "0.0056", "halt": "0.0025", "strength": "0.0007", "delay": "0.0123", "fire": "0.0070", "boom": "0.0011", "reject": "0.0035", "weaken": "0.0074", "difficult": "0.0007", "tighten": "0.0053", "effect": "0.0088", "resign": "0.0011", "alert": "0.0035", "quit": "0.0032", "refin": "0.0095", "postpon": "0.0049", "stabil": "0.0053", "stress": "0.0098", "liquid": "0.0028", "antitrust": "0.0021", "stronger": "0.0032", "su": "0.0032", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0032", "achiev": "0.0007"}, "10": {"recess": "0.0040", "opposit": "0.0047", "lack": "0.0047", "protest": "0.0064", "surpass": "0.0033", "fear": "0.0023", "suffer": "0.0013", "fine": "0.0037", "accus": "0.0047", "cut": "0.0264", "depend": "0.0027", "except": "0.0017", "late": "0.0060", "arrest": "0.0020", "bailout": "0.0104", "volatil": "0.0043", "disrupt": "0.0013", "complaint": "0.0047", "good": "0.0087", "greater": "0.0020", "disclos": "0.0084", "rebound": "0.0027", "stop": "0.0037", "break": "0.0047", "worst": "0.0033", "know": "0.0027", "press": "0.0064", "loss": "0.0141", "bar": "0.0027", "success": "0.0020", "lost": "0.0147", "outperform": "0.0010", "drop": "0.0425", "negat": "0.0017", "resolv": "0.0030", "defens": "0.0037", "benefit": "0.0037", "integr": "0.0013", "lose": "0.0023", "popular": "0.0047", "collaps": "0.0027", "crisi": "0.0268", "prevent": "0.0020", "confid": "0.0047", "slower": "0.0010", "shut": "0.0007", "slowdown": "0.0013", "strongest": "0.0017", "cost": "0.0271", "opportun": "0.0043", "fail": "0.0134", "close": "0.0234", "precipit": "0.0003", "concern": "0.0314", "lead": "0.0130", "profit": "0.0241", "defend": "0.0017", "abl": "0.0040", "bad": "0.0030", "favor": "0.0057", "restructur": "0.0054", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0107", "progress": "0.0013", "boost": "0.0211", "correct": "0.0023", "encourag": "0.0023", "investig": "0.0030", "advanc": "0.0228", "weak": "0.0040", "ban": "0.0020", "slow": "0.0100", "excess": "0.0007", "disput": "0.0017", "strong": "0.0037", "great": "0.0020", "deterior": "0.0020", "unemploy": "0.0023", "contract": "0.0154", "threat": "0.0033", "improv": "0.0060", "allianc": "0.0017", "suspend": "0.0030", "effici": "0.0007", "declin": "0.0769", "win": "0.0047", "bankruptci": "0.0027", "shortag": "0.0007", "cancel": "0.0030", "stabl": "0.0010", "miss": "0.0037", "drought": "0.0007", "damag": "0.0030", "bolster": "0.0054", "better": "0.0057", "question": "0.0043", "construct": "0.0084", "doubt": "0.0037", "downgrad": "0.0070", "threaten": "0.0054", "unexpect": "0.0047", "forc": "0.0070", "hurt": "0.0020", "warn": "0.0043", "gain": "0.0589", "termin": "0.0023", "eas": "0.0060", "highest": "0.0214", "fraud": "0.0007", "default": "0.0147", "seiz": "0.0003", "will": "0.0013", "limit": "0.0077", "posit": "0.0127", "problem": "0.0050", "claim": "0.0080", "weaker": "0.0027", "advantag": "0.0013", "strengthen": "0.0090", "challeng": "0.0023", "premier": "0.0017", "worri": "0.0027", "alleg": "0.0057", "critic": "0.0017", "attract": "0.0054", "sever": "0.0010", "halt": "0.0020", "strength": "0.0027", "delay": "0.0057", "fire": "0.0020", "boom": "0.0013", "reject": "0.0027", "weaken": "0.0120", "difficult": "0.0023", "tighten": "0.0037", "effect": "0.0070", "resign": "0.0020", "alert": "0.0027", "quit": "0.0033", "refin": "0.0144", "postpon": "0.0090", "stabil": "0.0027", "stress": "0.0060", "liquid": "0.0077", "antitrust": "0.0007", "stronger": "0.0060", "su": "0.0037", "inform": "0.0050", "deni": "0.0064", "achiev": "0.0010"}, "11": {"recess": "0.0067", "opposit": "0.0067", "lack": "0.0067", "protest": "0.0067", "surpass": "0.0067", "fear": "0.0067", "suffer": "0.0067", "fine": "0.0067", "accus": "0.0067", "cut": "0.0067", "depend": "0.0067", "except": "0.0067", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0067", "bailout": "0.0067", "volatil": "0.0067", "disrupt": "0.0067", "complaint": "0.0067", "good": "0.0067", "greater": "0.0067", "disclos": "0.0067", "rebound": "0.0067", "stop": "0.0067", "break": "0.0067", "worst": "0.0067", "know": "0.0067", "press": "0.0067", "loss": "0.0067", "bar": "0.0067", "success": "0.0067", "lost": "0.0067", "outperform": "0.0067", "drop": "0.0067", "negat": "0.0067", "resolv": "0.0067", "defens": "0.0067", "benefit": "0.0067", "integr": "0.0067", "lose": "0.0067", "popular": "0.0067", "collaps": "0.0067", "crisi": "0.0067", "prevent": "0.0067", "confid": "0.0067", "slower": "0.0067", "shut": "0.0067", "slowdown": "0.0067", "strongest": "0.0067", "cost": "0.0067", "opportun": "0.0067", "fail": "0.0067", "close": "0.0067", "precipit": "0.0067", "concern": "0.0067", "lead": "0.0067", "profit": "0.0067", "defend": "0.0067", "abl": "0.0067", "bad": "0.0067", "favor": "0.0067", "restructur": "0.0067", "outstand": "0.0067", "deficit": "0.0067", "progress": "0.0067", "boost": "0.0067", "correct": "0.0067", "encourag": "0.0067", "investig": "0.0067", "advanc": "0.0067", "weak": "0.0067", "ban": "0.0067", "slow": "0.0067", "excess": "0.0067", "disput": "0.0067", "strong": "0.0067", "great": "0.0067", "deterior": "0.0067", "unemploy": "0.0067", "contract": "0.0067", "threat": "0.0067", "improv": "0.0067", "allianc": "0.0067", "suspend": "0.0067", "effici": "0.0067", "declin": "0.0067", "win": "0.0067", "bankruptci": "0.0067", "shortag": "0.0067", "cancel": "0.0067", "stabl": "0.0067", "miss": "0.0067", "drought": "0.0067", "damag": "0.0067", "bolster": "0.0067", "better": "0.0067", "question": "0.0067", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0067", "downgrad": "0.0067", "threaten": "0.0067", "unexpect": "0.0067", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0067", "warn": "0.0067", "gain": "0.0067", "termin": "0.0067", "eas": "0.0067", "highest": "0.0067", "fraud": "0.0067", "default": "0.0067", "seiz": "0.0067", "will": "0.0067", "limit": "0.0067", "posit": "0.0067", "problem": "0.0067", "claim": "0.0067", "weaker": "0.0067", "advantag": "0.0067", "strengthen": "0.0067", "challeng": "0.0067", "premier": "0.0067", "worri": "0.0067", "alleg": "0.0067", "critic": "0.0067", "attract": "0.0067", "sever": "0.0067", "halt": "0.0067", "strength": "0.0067", "delay": "0.0067", "fire": "0.0067", "boom": "0.0067", "reject": "0.0067", "weaken": "0.0067", "difficult": "0.0067", "tighten": "0.0067", "effect": "0.0067", "resign": "0.0067", "alert": "0.0067", "quit": "0.0067", "refin": "0.0067", "postpon": "0.0067", "stabil": "0.0067", "stress": "0.0067", "liquid": "0.0067", "antitrust": "0.0067", "stronger": "0.0067", "su": "0.0067", "inform": "0.0067", "deni": "0.0067", "achiev": "0.0067"}, "12": {"recess": "0.0036", "opposit": "0.0050", "lack": "0.0028", "protest": "0.0069", "surpass": "0.0017", "fear": "0.0014", "suffer": "0.0014", "fine": "0.0028", "accus": "0.0036", "cut": "0.0234", "depend": "0.0039", "except": "0.0014", "late": "0.0050", "arrest": "0.0066", "bailout": "0.0041", "volatil": "0.0022", "disrupt": "0.0006", "complaint": "0.0044", "good": "0.0069", "greater": "0.0033", "disclos": "0.0047", "rebound": "0.0055", "stop": "0.0030", "break": "0.0033", "worst": "0.0039", "know": "0.0022", "press": "0.0061", "loss": "0.0149", "bar": "0.0025", "success": "0.0019", "lost": "0.0152", "outperform": "0.0030", "drop": "0.0455", "negat": "0.0028", "resolv": "0.0028", "defens": "0.0022", "benefit": "0.0055", "integr": "0.0019", "lose": "0.0061", "popular": "0.0019", "collaps": "0.0022", "crisi": "0.0187", "prevent": "0.0052", "confid": "0.0099", "slower": "0.0022", "shut": "0.0011", "slowdown": "0.0022", "strongest": "0.0033", "cost": "0.0251", "opportun": "0.0044", "fail": "0.0119", "close": "0.0229", "precipit": "0.0003", "concern": "0.0204", "lead": "0.0124", "profit": "0.0226", "defend": "0.0033", "abl": "0.0050", "bad": "0.0028", "favor": "0.0058", "restructur": "0.0058", "outstand": "0.0094", "deficit": "0.0113", "progress": "0.0008", "boost": "0.0174", "correct": "0.0017", "encourag": "0.0019", "investig": "0.0061", "advanc": "0.0179", "weak": "0.0017", "ban": "0.0050", "slow": "0.0088", "excess": "0.0017", "disput": "0.0022", "strong": "0.0028", "great": "0.0017", "deterior": "0.0025", "unemploy": "0.0039", "contract": "0.0149", "threat": "0.0008", "improv": "0.0058", "allianc": "0.0028", "suspend": "0.0019", "effici": "0.0008", "declin": "0.0956", "win": "0.0063", "bankruptci": "0.0044", "shortag": "0.0006", "cancel": "0.0028", "stabl": "0.0030", "miss": "0.0033", "drought": "0.0006", "damag": "0.0047", "bolster": "0.0041", "better": "0.0047", "question": "0.0039", "construct": "0.0130", "doubt": "0.0028", "downgrad": "0.0066", "threaten": "0.0033", "unexpect": "0.0028", "forc": "0.0083", "hurt": "0.0036", "warn": "0.0025", "gain": "0.0631", "termin": "0.0011", "eas": "0.0063", "highest": "0.0130", "fraud": "0.0052", "default": "0.0110", "seiz": "0.0025", "will": "0.0019", "limit": "0.0055", "posit": "0.0083", "problem": "0.0072", "claim": "0.0132", "weaker": "0.0006", "advantag": "0.0008", "strengthen": "0.0074", "challeng": "0.0033", "premier": "0.0019", "worri": "0.0022", "alleg": "0.0047", "critic": "0.0044", "attract": "0.0036", "sever": "0.0039", "halt": "0.0039", "strength": "0.0025", "delay": "0.0063", "fire": "0.0036", "boom": "0.0017", "reject": "0.0030", "weaken": "0.0080", "difficult": "0.0019", "tighten": "0.0058", "effect": "0.0072", "resign": "0.0047", "alert": "0.0039", "quit": "0.0028", "refin": "0.0124", "postpon": "0.0047", "stabil": "0.0041", "stress": "0.0096", "liquid": "0.0077", "antitrust": "0.0030", "stronger": "0.0017", "su": "0.0041", "inform": "0.0083", "deni": "0.0041", "achiev": "0.0008"}, "13": {"recess": "0.0049", "opposit": "0.0027", "lack": "0.0021", "protest": "0.0082", "surpass": "0.0012", "fear": "0.0021", "suffer": "0.0015", "fine": "0.0009", "accus": "0.0034", "cut": "0.0489", "depend": "0.0031", "except": "0.0015", "late": "0.0067", "arrest": "0.0018", "bailout": "0.0122", "volatil": "0.0052", "disrupt": "0.0015", "complaint": "0.0012", "good": "0.0064", "greater": "0.0043", "disclos": "0.0104", "rebound": "0.0061", "stop": "0.0037", "break": "0.0046", "worst": "0.0046", "know": "0.0027", "press": "0.0058", "loss": "0.0156", "bar": "0.0012", "success": "0.0015", "lost": "0.0134", "outperform": "0.0015", "drop": "0.0443", "negat": "0.0024", "resolv": "0.0015", "defens": "0.0027", "benefit": "0.0043", "integr": "0.0009", "lose": "0.0064", "popular": "0.0034", "collaps": "0.0015", "crisi": "0.0168", "prevent": "0.0037", "confid": "0.0064", "slower": "0.0021", "shut": "0.0012", "slowdown": "0.0024", "strongest": "0.0052", "cost": "0.0308", "opportun": "0.0027", "fail": "0.0104", "close": "0.0275", "precipit": "0.0003", "concern": "0.0351", "lead": "0.0128", "profit": "0.0272", "defend": "0.0009", "abl": "0.0073", "bad": "0.0064", "favor": "0.0027", "restructur": "0.0061", "outstand": "0.0055", "deficit": "0.0202", "progress": "0.0009", "boost": "0.0168", "correct": "0.0009", "encourag": "0.0018", "investig": "0.0021", "advanc": "0.0171", "weak": "0.0024", "ban": "0.0015", "slow": "0.0125", "excess": "0.0006", "disput": "0.0015", "strong": "0.0052", "great": "0.0018", "deterior": "0.0021", "unemploy": "0.0027", "contract": "0.0153", "threat": "0.0021", "improv": "0.0082", "allianc": "0.0009", "suspend": "0.0043", "effici": "0.0006", "declin": "0.0711", "win": "0.0034", "bankruptci": "0.0012", "shortag": "0.0015", "cancel": "0.0018", "stabl": "0.0015", "miss": "0.0037", "drought": "0.0003", "damag": "0.0034", "bolster": "0.0034", "better": "0.0049", "question": "0.0027", "construct": "0.0067", "doubt": "0.0018", "downgrad": "0.0046", "threaten": "0.0024", "unexpect": "0.0061", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0055", "warn": "0.0021", "gain": "0.0537", "termin": "0.0021", "eas": "0.0082", "highest": "0.0238", "fraud": "0.0018", "default": "0.0165", "seiz": "0.0015", "will": "0.0018", "limit": "0.0064", "posit": "0.0104", "problem": "0.0070", "claim": "0.0018", "weaker": "0.0021", "advantag": "0.0018", "strengthen": "0.0082", "challeng": "0.0040", "premier": "0.0018", "worri": "0.0012", "alleg": "0.0027", "critic": "0.0015", "attract": "0.0061", "sever": "0.0018", "halt": "0.0034", "strength": "0.0024", "delay": "0.0055", "fire": "0.0018", "boom": "0.0021", "reject": "0.0040", "weaken": "0.0113", "difficult": "0.0027", "tighten": "0.0037", "effect": "0.0064", "resign": "0.0009", "alert": "0.0024", "quit": "0.0031", "refin": "0.0159", "postpon": "0.0134", "stabil": "0.0024", "stress": "0.0024", "liquid": "0.0027", "antitrust": "0.0012", "stronger": "0.0055", "su": "0.0015", "inform": "0.0037", "deni": "0.0037", "achiev": "0.0018"}, "14": {"recess": "0.0024", "opposit": "0.0028", "lack": "0.0021", "protest": "0.0031", "surpass": "0.0009", "fear": "0.0009", "suffer": "0.0017", "fine": "0.0031", "accus": "0.0017", "cut": "0.0225", "depend": "0.0026", "except": "0.0007", "late": "0.0036", "arrest": "0.0024", "bailout": "0.0085", "volatil": "0.0021", "disrupt": "0.0012", "complaint": "0.0028", "good": "0.0097", "greater": "0.0019", "disclos": "0.0026", "rebound": "0.0074", "stop": "0.0024", "break": "0.0009", "worst": "0.0045", "know": "0.0017", "press": "0.0036", "loss": "0.0116", "bar": "0.0026", "success": "0.0019", "lost": "0.0123", "outperform": "0.0017", "drop": "0.0453", "negat": "0.0045", "resolv": "0.0012", "defens": "0.0019", "benefit": "0.0047", "integr": "0.0024", "lose": "0.0047", "popular": "0.0038", "collaps": "0.0017", "crisi": "0.0214", "prevent": "0.0040", "confid": "0.0074", "slower": "0.0019", "shut": "0.0009", "slowdown": "0.0014", "strongest": "0.0036", "cost": "0.0408", "opportun": "0.0031", "fail": "0.0133", "close": "0.0254", "precipit": "0.0002", "concern": "0.0244", "lead": "0.0152", "profit": "0.0180", "defend": "0.0014", "abl": "0.0033", "bad": "0.0028", "favor": "0.0036", "restructur": "0.0036", "outstand": "0.0078", "deficit": "0.0114", "progress": "0.0012", "boost": "0.0240", "correct": "0.0033", "encourag": "0.0014", "investig": "0.0031", "advanc": "0.0216", "weak": "0.0038", "ban": "0.0024", "slow": "0.0126", "excess": "0.0012", "disput": "0.0026", "strong": "0.0055", "great": "0.0050", "deterior": "0.0024", "unemploy": "0.0055", "contract": "0.0183", "threat": "0.0019", "improv": "0.0055", "allianc": "0.0038", "suspend": "0.0012", "effici": "0.0017", "declin": "0.0930", "win": "0.0043", "bankruptci": "0.0019", "shortag": "0.0017", "cancel": "0.0031", "stabl": "0.0012", "miss": "0.0033", "drought": "0.0009", "damag": "0.0043", "bolster": "0.0045", "better": "0.0052", "question": "0.0019", "construct": "0.0214", "doubt": "0.0017", "downgrad": "0.0069", "threaten": "0.0036", "unexpect": "0.0036", "forc": "0.0090", "hurt": "0.0047", "warn": "0.0043", "gain": "0.0667", "termin": "0.0009", "eas": "0.0052", "highest": "0.0159", "fraud": "0.0009", "default": "0.0145", "seiz": "0.0021", "will": "0.0007", "limit": "0.0069", "posit": "0.0123", "problem": "0.0043", "claim": "0.0093", "weaker": "0.0014", "advantag": "0.0033", "strengthen": "0.0066", "challeng": "0.0036", "premier": "0.0017", "worri": "0.0012", "alleg": "0.0036", "critic": "0.0038", "attract": "0.0057", "sever": "0.0057", "halt": "0.0024", "strength": "0.0021", "delay": "0.0050", "fire": "0.0028", "boom": "0.0017", "reject": "0.0047", "weaken": "0.0083", "difficult": "0.0028", "tighten": "0.0071", "effect": "0.0028", "resign": "0.0047", "alert": "0.0033", "quit": "0.0033", "refin": "0.0121", "postpon": "0.0028", "stabil": "0.0028", "stress": "0.0045", "liquid": "0.0036", "antitrust": "0.0019", "stronger": "0.0038", "su": "0.0019", "inform": "0.0097", "deni": "0.0033", "achiev": "0.0026"}, "15": {"recess": "0.0045", "opposit": "0.0032", "lack": "0.0018", "protest": "0.0018", "surpass": "0.0017", "fear": "0.0019", "suffer": "0.0030", "fine": "0.0010", "accus": "0.0013", "cut": "0.0209", "depend": "0.0027", "except": "0.0018", "late": "0.0056", "arrest": "0.0022", "bailout": "0.0080", "volatil": "0.0050", "disrupt": "0.0016", "complaint": "0.0012", "good": "0.0118", "greater": "0.0028", "disclos": "0.0062", "rebound": "0.0078", "stop": "0.0027", "break": "0.0014", "worst": "0.0052", "know": "0.0025", "press": "0.0035", "loss": "0.0180", "bar": "0.0008", "success": "0.0026", "lost": "0.0146", "outperform": "0.0016", "drop": "0.0453", "negat": "0.0043", "resolv": "0.0010", "defens": "0.0027", "benefit": "0.0048", "integr": "0.0031", "lose": "0.0045", "popular": "0.0022", "collaps": "0.0019", "crisi": "0.0221", "prevent": "0.0031", "confid": "0.0089", "slower": "0.0016", "shut": "0.0016", "slowdown": "0.0021", "strongest": "0.0048", "cost": "0.0322", "opportun": "0.0041", "fail": "0.0094", "close": "0.0242", "precipit": "0.0001", "concern": "0.0284", "lead": "0.0140", "profit": "0.0366", "defend": "0.0019", "abl": "0.0039", "bad": "0.0087", "favor": "0.0040", "restructur": "0.0037", "outstand": "0.0044", "deficit": "0.0112", "progress": "0.0008", "boost": "0.0243", "correct": "0.0019", "encourag": "0.0013", "investig": "0.0026", "advanc": "0.0227", "weak": "0.0018", "ban": "0.0018", "slow": "0.0107", "excess": "0.0014", "disput": "0.0012", "strong": "0.0071", "great": "0.0026", "deterior": "0.0018", "unemploy": "0.0036", "contract": "0.0145", "threat": "0.0017", "improv": "0.0105", "allianc": "0.0018", "suspend": "0.0013", "effici": "0.0006", "declin": "0.0796", "win": "0.0043", "bankruptci": "0.0018", "shortag": "0.0017", "cancel": "0.0018", "stabl": "0.0027", "miss": "0.0030", "drought": "0.0012", "damag": "0.0034", "bolster": "0.0047", "better": "0.0045", "question": "0.0025", "construct": "0.0106", "doubt": "0.0027", "downgrad": "0.0078", "threaten": "0.0026", "unexpect": "0.0035", "forc": "0.0067", "hurt": "0.0039", "warn": "0.0018", "gain": "0.0739", "termin": "0.0008", "eas": "0.0105", "highest": "0.0202", "fraud": "0.0016", "default": "0.0165", "seiz": "0.0009", "will": "0.0016", "limit": "0.0076", "posit": "0.0140", "problem": "0.0052", "claim": "0.0052", "weaker": "0.0012", "advantag": "0.0036", "strengthen": "0.0111", "challeng": "0.0035", "premier": "0.0017", "worri": "0.0016", "alleg": "0.0021", "critic": "0.0017", "attract": "0.0068", "sever": "0.0036", "halt": "0.0026", "strength": "0.0025", "delay": "0.0080", "fire": "0.0035", "boom": "0.0014", "reject": "0.0026", "weaken": "0.0076", "difficult": "0.0012", "tighten": "0.0039", "effect": "0.0054", "resign": "0.0008", "alert": "0.0031", "quit": "0.0021", "refin": "0.0112", "postpon": "0.0036", "stabil": "0.0041", "stress": "0.0027", "liquid": "0.0039", "antitrust": "0.0009", "stronger": "0.0052", "su": "0.0012", "inform": "0.0056", "deni": "0.0031", "achiev": "0.0016"}, "16": {"recess": "0.0056", "opposit": "0.0056", "lack": "0.0056", "protest": "0.0056", "surpass": "0.0056", "fear": "0.0056", "suffer": "0.0056", "fine": "0.0056", "accus": "0.0056", "cut": "0.0056", "depend": "0.0056", "except": "0.0056", "late": "0.0056", "arrest": "0.0056", "bailout": "0.0056", "volatil": "0.0056", "disrupt": "0.0056", "complaint": "0.0056", "good": "0.0056", "greater": "0.0169", "disclos": "0.0056", "rebound": "0.0056", "stop": "0.0056", "break": "0.0056", "worst": "0.0056", "know": "0.0056", "press": "0.0056", "loss": "0.0056", "bar": "0.0056", "success": "0.0056", "lost": "0.0056", "outperform": "0.0056", "drop": "0.0056", "negat": "0.0056", "resolv": "0.0056", "defens": "0.0056", "benefit": "0.0056", "integr": "0.0056", "lose": "0.0056", "popular": "0.0056", "collaps": "0.0056", "crisi": "0.0056", "prevent": "0.0056", "confid": "0.0169", "slower": "0.0056", "shut": "0.0056", "slowdown": "0.0056", "strongest": "0.0056", "cost": "0.0056", "opportun": "0.0056", "fail": "0.0056", "close": "0.0169", "precipit": "0.0056", "concern": "0.0169", "lead": "0.0056", "profit": "0.0169", "defend": "0.0056", "abl": "0.0056", "bad": "0.0056", "favor": "0.0056", "restructur": "0.0056", "outstand": "0.0056", "deficit": "0.0056", "progress": "0.0056", "boost": "0.0056", "correct": "0.0056", "encourag": "0.0056", "investig": "0.0056", "advanc": "0.0281", "weak": "0.0056", "ban": "0.0056", "slow": "0.0056", "excess": "0.0056", "disput": "0.0056", "strong": "0.0169", "great": "0.0056", "deterior": "0.0056", "unemploy": "0.0056", "contract": "0.0056", "threat": "0.0056", "improv": "0.0169", "allianc": "0.0056", "suspend": "0.0056", "effici": "0.0056", "declin": "0.0056", "win": "0.0056", "bankruptci": "0.0056", "shortag": "0.0056", "cancel": "0.0056", "stabl": "0.0056", "miss": "0.0056", "drought": "0.0056", "damag": "0.0056", "bolster": "0.0056", "better": "0.0056", "question": "0.0056", "construct": "0.0056", "doubt": "0.0056", "downgrad": "0.0056", "threaten": "0.0112", "unexpect": "0.0056", "forc": "0.0056", "hurt": "0.0056", "warn": "0.0056", "gain": "0.0449", "termin": "0.0056", "eas": "0.0112", "highest": "0.0112", "fraud": "0.0056", "default": "0.0056", "seiz": "0.0056", "will": "0.0056", "limit": "0.0056", "posit": "0.0056", "problem": "0.0056", "claim": "0.0056", "weaker": "0.0056", "advantag": "0.0056", "strengthen": "0.0056", "challeng": "0.0056", "premier": "0.0056", "worri": "0.0056", "alleg": "0.0056", "critic": "0.0056", "attract": "0.0056", "sever": "0.0056", "halt": "0.0056", "strength": "0.0056", "delay": "0.0056", "fire": "0.0056", "boom": "0.0056", "reject": "0.0056", "weaken": "0.0056", "difficult": "0.0056", "tighten": "0.0056", "effect": "0.0056", "resign": "0.0056", "alert": "0.0056", "quit": "0.0056", "refin": "0.0056", "postpon": "0.0056", "stabil": "0.0056", "stress": "0.0056", "liquid": "0.0056", "antitrust": "0.0056", "stronger": "0.0056", "su": "0.0056", "inform": "0.0056", "deni": "0.0056", "achiev": "0.0056"}, "17": {"recess": "0.0016", "opposit": "0.0057", "lack": "0.0010", "protest": "0.0073", "surpass": "0.0021", "fear": "0.0016", "suffer": "0.0010", "fine": "0.0021", "accus": "0.0021", "cut": "0.0167", "depend": "0.0047", "except": "0.0021", "late": "0.0078", "arrest": "0.0078", "bailout": "0.0057", "volatil": "0.0042", "disrupt": "0.0016", "complaint": "0.0010", "good": "0.0125", "greater": "0.0047", "disclos": "0.0026", "rebound": "0.0047", "stop": "0.0031", "break": "0.0021", "worst": "0.0031", "know": "0.0037", "press": "0.0063", "loss": "0.0209", "bar": "0.0026", "success": "0.0037", "lost": "0.0136", "outperform": "0.0016", "drop": "0.0360", "negat": "0.0016", "resolv": "0.0026", "defens": "0.0031", "benefit": "0.0042", "integr": "0.0026", "lose": "0.0078", "popular": "0.0037", "collaps": "0.0021", "crisi": "0.0172", "prevent": "0.0042", "confid": "0.0083", "slower": "0.0021", "shut": "0.0026", "slowdown": "0.0010", "strongest": "0.0031", "cost": "0.0350", "opportun": "0.0073", "fail": "0.0130", "close": "0.0256", "precipit": "0.0005", "concern": "0.0214", "lead": "0.0120", "profit": "0.0292", "defend": "0.0042", "abl": "0.0089", "bad": "0.0052", "favor": "0.0042", "restructur": "0.0026", "outstand": "0.0052", "deficit": "0.0110", "progress": "0.0016", "boost": "0.0188", "correct": "0.0016", "encourag": "0.0005", "investig": "0.0068", "advanc": "0.0303", "weak": "0.0037", "ban": "0.0037", "slow": "0.0115", "excess": "0.0005", "disput": "0.0026", "strong": "0.0094", "great": "0.0037", "deterior": "0.0026", "unemploy": "0.0016", "contract": "0.0156", "threat": "0.0021", "improv": "0.0083", "allianc": "0.0005", "suspend": "0.0016", "effici": "0.0005", "declin": "0.0657", "win": "0.0068", "bankruptci": "0.0016", "shortag": "0.0005", "cancel": "0.0042", "stabl": "0.0016", "miss": "0.0042", "drought": "0.0005", "damag": "0.0026", "bolster": "0.0063", "better": "0.0063", "question": "0.0021", "construct": "0.0110", "doubt": "0.0010", "downgrad": "0.0010", "threaten": "0.0021", "unexpect": "0.0016", "forc": "0.0094", "hurt": "0.0078", "warn": "0.0010", "gain": "0.0751", "termin": "0.0005", "eas": "0.0078", "highest": "0.0193", "fraud": "0.0037", "default": "0.0115", "seiz": "0.0026", "will": "0.0010", "limit": "0.0068", "posit": "0.0141", "problem": "0.0094", "claim": "0.0099", "weaker": "0.0005", "advantag": "0.0021", "strengthen": "0.0057", "challeng": "0.0026", "premier": "0.0016", "worri": "0.0016", "alleg": "0.0068", "critic": "0.0021", "attract": "0.0063", "sever": "0.0052", "halt": "0.0047", "strength": "0.0042", "delay": "0.0047", "fire": "0.0037", "boom": "0.0016", "reject": "0.0037", "weaken": "0.0031", "difficult": "0.0021", "tighten": "0.0021", "effect": "0.0068", "resign": "0.0016", "alert": "0.0037", "quit": "0.0037", "refin": "0.0089", "postpon": "0.0026", "stabil": "0.0037", "stress": "0.0057", "liquid": "0.0042", "antitrust": "0.0010", "stronger": "0.0026", "su": "0.0005", "inform": "0.0083", "deni": "0.0042", "achiev": "0.0037"}, "18": {"recess": "0.0047", "opposit": "0.0041", "lack": "0.0032", "protest": "0.0086", "surpass": "0.0007", "fear": "0.0014", "suffer": "0.0020", "fine": "0.0009", "accus": "0.0020", "cut": "0.0284", "depend": "0.0023", "except": "0.0014", "late": "0.0074", "arrest": "0.0016", "bailout": "0.0063", "volatil": "0.0052", "disrupt": "0.0018", "complaint": "0.0018", "good": "0.0074", "greater": "0.0041", "disclos": "0.0088", "rebound": "0.0077", "stop": "0.0041", "break": "0.0036", "worst": "0.0045", "know": "0.0029", "press": "0.0050", "loss": "0.0126", "bar": "0.0016", "success": "0.0020", "lost": "0.0137", "outperform": "0.0018", "drop": "0.0361", "negat": "0.0041", "resolv": "0.0018", "defens": "0.0032", "benefit": "0.0043", "integr": "0.0005", "lose": "0.0050", "popular": "0.0029", "collaps": "0.0018", "crisi": "0.0228", "prevent": "0.0043", "confid": "0.0081", "slower": "0.0023", "shut": "0.0020", "slowdown": "0.0016", "strongest": "0.0054", "cost": "0.0295", "opportun": "0.0027", "fail": "0.0079", "close": "0.0196", "precipit": "0.0002", "concern": "0.0279", "lead": "0.0165", "profit": "0.0216", "defend": "0.0023", "abl": "0.0070", "bad": "0.0070", "favor": "0.0041", "restructur": "0.0068", "outstand": "0.0081", "deficit": "0.0140", "progress": "0.0009", "boost": "0.0180", "correct": "0.0014", "encourag": "0.0025", "investig": "0.0038", "advanc": "0.0174", "weak": "0.0043", "ban": "0.0025", "slow": "0.0117", "excess": "0.0020", "disput": "0.0016", "strong": "0.0052", "great": "0.0018", "deterior": "0.0027", "unemploy": "0.0050", "contract": "0.0146", "threat": "0.0025", "improv": "0.0101", "allianc": "0.0034", "suspend": "0.0014", "effici": "0.0018", "declin": "0.0771", "win": "0.0072", "bankruptci": "0.0027", "shortag": "0.0018", "cancel": "0.0027", "stabl": "0.0014", "miss": "0.0041", "drought": "0.0005", "damag": "0.0029", "bolster": "0.0050", "better": "0.0056", "question": "0.0038", "construct": "0.0065", "doubt": "0.0011", "downgrad": "0.0054", "threaten": "0.0041", "unexpect": "0.0027", "forc": "0.0068", "hurt": "0.0041", "warn": "0.0016", "gain": "0.0604", "termin": "0.0018", "eas": "0.0079", "highest": "0.0156", "fraud": "0.0036", "default": "0.0146", "seiz": "0.0029", "will": "0.0014", "limit": "0.0065", "posit": "0.0113", "problem": "0.0072", "claim": "0.0070", "weaker": "0.0020", "advantag": "0.0020", "strengthen": "0.0115", "challeng": "0.0025", "premier": "0.0023", "worri": "0.0011", "alleg": "0.0014", "critic": "0.0025", "attract": "0.0095", "sever": "0.0052", "halt": "0.0032", "strength": "0.0025", "delay": "0.0088", "fire": "0.0018", "boom": "0.0045", "reject": "0.0043", "weaken": "0.0072", "difficult": "0.0025", "tighten": "0.0036", "effect": "0.0050", "resign": "0.0020", "alert": "0.0041", "quit": "0.0043", "refin": "0.0133", "postpon": "0.0137", "stabil": "0.0032", "stress": "0.0061", "liquid": "0.0052", "antitrust": "0.0002", "stronger": "0.0036", "su": "0.0036", "inform": "0.0054", "deni": "0.0045", "achiev": "0.0016"}, "19": {"recess": "0.0059", "opposit": "0.0036", "lack": "0.0019", "protest": "0.0018", "surpass": "0.0012", "fear": "0.0018", "suffer": "0.0011", "fine": "0.0026", "accus": "0.0037", "cut": "0.0203", "depend": "0.0048", "except": "0.0021", "late": "0.0064", "arrest": "0.0041", "bailout": "0.0055", "volatil": "0.0029", "disrupt": "0.0004", "complaint": "0.0039", "good": "0.0112", "greater": "0.0025", "disclos": "0.0062", "rebound": "0.0079", "stop": "0.0040", "break": "0.0025", "worst": "0.0051", "know": "0.0026", "press": "0.0064", "loss": "0.0133", "bar": "0.0028", "success": "0.0025", "lost": "0.0110", "outperform": "0.0015", "drop": "0.0414", "negat": "0.0032", "resolv": "0.0010", "defens": "0.0032", "benefit": "0.0050", "integr": "0.0032", "lose": "0.0043", "popular": "0.0019", "collaps": "0.0035", "crisi": "0.0189", "prevent": "0.0022", "confid": "0.0086", "slower": "0.0017", "shut": "0.0015", "slowdown": "0.0015", "strongest": "0.0029", "cost": "0.0312", "opportun": "0.0046", "fail": "0.0102", "close": "0.0219", "precipit": "0.0001", "concern": "0.0226", "lead": "0.0138", "profit": "0.0298", "defend": "0.0019", "abl": "0.0043", "bad": "0.0066", "favor": "0.0041", "restructur": "0.0048", "outstand": "0.0069", "deficit": "0.0116", "progress": "0.0014", "boost": "0.0232", "correct": "0.0026", "encourag": "0.0010", "investig": "0.0079", "advanc": "0.0261", "weak": "0.0032", "ban": "0.0017", "slow": "0.0098", "excess": "0.0011", "disput": "0.0025", "strong": "0.0058", "great": "0.0029", "deterior": "0.0010", "unemploy": "0.0041", "contract": "0.0145", "threat": "0.0011", "improv": "0.0108", "allianc": "0.0019", "suspend": "0.0012", "effici": "0.0008", "declin": "0.0803", "win": "0.0061", "bankruptci": "0.0017", "shortag": "0.0007", "cancel": "0.0019", "stabl": "0.0037", "miss": "0.0054", "drought": "0.0007", "damag": "0.0043", "bolster": "0.0029", "better": "0.0048", "question": "0.0039", "construct": "0.0117", "doubt": "0.0025", "downgrad": "0.0062", "threaten": "0.0036", "unexpect": "0.0022", "forc": "0.0072", "hurt": "0.0028", "warn": "0.0039", "gain": "0.0697", "termin": "0.0010", "eas": "0.0075", "highest": "0.0196", "fraud": "0.0014", "default": "0.0163", "seiz": "0.0028", "will": "0.0018", "limit": "0.0065", "posit": "0.0094", "problem": "0.0044", "claim": "0.0086", "weaker": "0.0008", "advantag": "0.0021", "strengthen": "0.0087", "challeng": "0.0021", "premier": "0.0010", "worri": "0.0012", "alleg": "0.0036", "critic": "0.0015", "attract": "0.0032", "sever": "0.0033", "halt": "0.0035", "strength": "0.0025", "delay": "0.0095", "fire": "0.0032", "boom": "0.0011", "reject": "0.0023", "weaken": "0.0084", "difficult": "0.0014", "tighten": "0.0047", "effect": "0.0054", "resign": "0.0028", "alert": "0.0040", "quit": "0.0029", "refin": "0.0127", "postpon": "0.0018", "stabil": "0.0048", "stress": "0.0113", "liquid": "0.0062", "antitrust": "0.0011", "stronger": "0.0018", "su": "0.0036", "inform": "0.0087", "deni": "0.0059", "achiev": "0.0012"}, "20": {"recess": "0.0047", "opposit": "0.0024", "lack": "0.0020", "protest": "0.0038", "surpass": "0.0017", "fear": "0.0017", "suffer": "0.0020", "fine": "0.0038", "accus": "0.0035", "cut": "0.0283", "depend": "0.0024", "except": "0.0018", "late": "0.0042", "arrest": "0.0029", "bailout": "0.0102", "volatil": "0.0041", "disrupt": "0.0026", "complaint": "0.0050", "good": "0.0101", "greater": "0.0029", "disclos": "0.0056", "rebound": "0.0060", "stop": "0.0026", "break": "0.0038", "worst": "0.0051", "know": "0.0015", "press": "0.0056", "loss": "0.0157", "bar": "0.0018", "success": "0.0023", "lost": "0.0149", "outperform": "0.0009", "drop": "0.0449", "negat": "0.0029", "resolv": "0.0030", "defens": "0.0021", "benefit": "0.0041", "integr": "0.0018", "lose": "0.0048", "popular": "0.0023", "collaps": "0.0030", "crisi": "0.0217", "prevent": "0.0035", "confid": "0.0068", "slower": "0.0023", "shut": "0.0015", "slowdown": "0.0024", "strongest": "0.0057", "cost": "0.0363", "opportun": "0.0050", "fail": "0.0122", "close": "0.0209", "precipit": "0.0002", "concern": "0.0265", "lead": "0.0115", "profit": "0.0247", "defend": "0.0041", "abl": "0.0029", "bad": "0.0042", "favor": "0.0047", "restructur": "0.0035", "outstand": "0.0033", "deficit": "0.0092", "progress": "0.0009", "boost": "0.0235", "correct": "0.0014", "encourag": "0.0021", "investig": "0.0066", "advanc": "0.0200", "weak": "0.0027", "ban": "0.0011", "slow": "0.0118", "excess": "0.0008", "disput": "0.0024", "strong": "0.0048", "great": "0.0017", "deterior": "0.0011", "unemploy": "0.0023", "contract": "0.0154", "threat": "0.0015", "improv": "0.0071", "allianc": "0.0011", "suspend": "0.0024", "effici": "0.0006", "declin": "0.0793", "win": "0.0059", "bankruptci": "0.0051", "shortag": "0.0006", "cancel": "0.0032", "stabl": "0.0021", "miss": "0.0038", "drought": "0.0003", "damag": "0.0047", "bolster": "0.0042", "better": "0.0045", "question": "0.0042", "construct": "0.0107", "doubt": "0.0033", "downgrad": "0.0066", "threaten": "0.0036", "unexpect": "0.0035", "forc": "0.0083", "hurt": "0.0035", "warn": "0.0038", "gain": "0.0618", "termin": "0.0009", "eas": "0.0096", "highest": "0.0131", "fraud": "0.0014", "default": "0.0139", "seiz": "0.0021", "will": "0.0015", "limit": "0.0075", "posit": "0.0140", "problem": "0.0051", "claim": "0.0127", "weaker": "0.0011", "advantag": "0.0024", "strengthen": "0.0081", "challeng": "0.0041", "premier": "0.0009", "worri": "0.0027", "alleg": "0.0065", "critic": "0.0024", "attract": "0.0048", "sever": "0.0039", "halt": "0.0035", "strength": "0.0017", "delay": "0.0053", "fire": "0.0032", "boom": "0.0021", "reject": "0.0018", "weaken": "0.0090", "difficult": "0.0014", "tighten": "0.0033", "effect": "0.0068", "resign": "0.0014", "alert": "0.0024", "quit": "0.0026", "refin": "0.0101", "postpon": "0.0023", "stabil": "0.0033", "stress": "0.0081", "liquid": "0.0045", "antitrust": "0.0029", "stronger": "0.0032", "su": "0.0063", "inform": "0.0087", "deni": "0.0051", "achiev": "0.0012"}}}